[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 04 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.26,0:00:50.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.11,0:00:53.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.07,0:00:58.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.57,0:01:16.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.69,0:01:22.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.05,0:01:28.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.13,0:01:33.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.08,0:01:38.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.72,0:01:41.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.38,0:01:46.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.26,0:01:50.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.13,0:01:53.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.12,0:01:57.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.74,0:01:58.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.72,0:02:01.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.50,0:02:04.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.21,0:02:06.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.76,0:02:12.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.26,0:00:50.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.11,0:00:53.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.07,0:00:58.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情  飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.57,0:01:16.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.69,0:01:22.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.05,0:01:28.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定  不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.13,0:01:33.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.08,0:01:38.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西  就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.72,0:01:41.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧  很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.38,0:01:46.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.26,0:01:50.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.13,0:01:53.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.12,0:01:57.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.74,0:01:58.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.72,0:02:01.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.50,0:02:04.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.21,0:02:06.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.76,0:02:12.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中  直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天  就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界  怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线  我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧  只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3  越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.30,0:00:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎  我的黄金周！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.64,0:00:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于见到你了  我值得依靠的伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.15,0:00:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  好想念你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.59,0:00:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  红羽那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.71,0:00:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然因为方便食品太过便利所以讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.54,0:00:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就像彻底否定了人类的才智一样嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.76,0:00:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啦来啦  现在就来开门
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.60,0:00:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问是哪位…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.87,0:00:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.56,0:00:41.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人  如果能让我住下的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.84,0:00:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就给您满满的服务哦  喵~
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.68,0:02:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要一直盯着看啊…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.16,0:02:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.28,0:02:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.66,0:02:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.46,0:02:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  能请你收养昴喵吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.78,0:02:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.02,0:02:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假日的一大清早就来搞什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.69,0:02:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实呢  昨天昴被赶出家了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.38,0:02:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事  原因呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.35,0:02:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何必这么在意呢  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.85,0:02:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,详细经过什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.60,0:02:55.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别笑着蒙混过去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.43,0:03:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  就是这样  昴没有其他地方可去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.33,0:03:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.87,0:03:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.75,0:03:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不是哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.20,0:03:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的声音可不是我发出的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.00,0:03:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴她啊  被赶出家后一下子就弄丢了钱包
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.21,0:03:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  迫不得已只能…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.02,0:03:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.85,0:03:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了刚刚的不是我！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.55,0:03:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.10,0:03:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家～  都在哪呢～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.05,0:03:37.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全走散了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.05,0:03:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.46,0:03:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没想白住哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.97,0:03:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里留宿期间  我就当这个家的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.71,0:03:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎的管家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.31,0:03:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.90,0:03:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.88,0:03:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和你父母打个招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.60,0:03:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.76,0:03:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母亲去了国外不在家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.56,0:04:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽去参加社团的集训了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.21,0:04:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要后天才回来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.98,0:04:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  怎么回事！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.54,0:04:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可没听大小姐提过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.42,0:04:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也就是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.18,0:04:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹回来之前  那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.42,0:04:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要和次郎独处…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.68,0:04:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总  总之
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.49,0:04:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于这点过后再慢慢讨论
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.00,0:04:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃完这个我就去睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.49,0:04:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去  去睡！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.98,0:04:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.39,0:04:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实我是说了要当你的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.66,0:04:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可马上就提出这种…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.36,0:04:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,H的要求我无法答应…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.87,0:04:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.73,0:04:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在要去补觉  你随意！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.23,0:04:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,补觉…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.06,0:04:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在可是刚过早上9点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.11,0:04:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要这么惊讶吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.14,0:04:49.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在假日睡回笼觉很普通吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.79,0:04:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太懒散了…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.52,0:04:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纠正主人的生活也是管家的职责
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.70,0:04:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由我来矫正你那扭曲的本性！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.47,0:05:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然能和熊先生较量  集训还真是来对了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.63,0:05:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多就到此为止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.23,0:05:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.55,0:05:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对体力还是很有自信的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.87,0:05:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过还真少见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.15,0:05:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通人家里竟然有道场
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.34,0:05:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  因为父母工作的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.12,0:05:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  刚才我看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.16,0:05:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,积了很多要洗的衣服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.95,0:05:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  烧洗澡水的同时顺便解决掉好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.39,0:05:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不用做  这是管家的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.06,0:05:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  真不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.73,0:05:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用介意
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.07,0:06:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个  你还是在这里休息会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.52,0:06:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.87,0:06:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多洗澡水该烧好…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.82,0:06:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.75,0:06:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是  不是的  次郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.71,0:06:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不是很在意「男生的气味都是什么样的呢」这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.00,0:06:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先别管洗衣服的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.50,0:06:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能先洗澡吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.54,0:06:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新活过来就是这种感觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.05,0:06:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天久违地出了不少汗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.97,0:06:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水温怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.14,0:06:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉挺不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.26,0:06:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.06,0:06:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我进来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.54,0:06:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你在  在干什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.08,0:06:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么干什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.44,0:07:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为主人擦背不是管家应尽的义务吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.10,0:07:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不要一直盯着看啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.79,0:07:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说  说起来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.89,0:07:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎的背真宽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.64,0:07:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算  算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.01,0:07:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是从小就锻炼过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.93,0:07:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.19,0:07:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这是好事情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.36,0:07:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.81,0:07:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}哥哥  我回来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.28,0:07:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事  红羽妹妹不是后天回来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.92,0:07:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  原来在洗澡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.90,0:07:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽  怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.19,0:07:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是应该后天回来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.32,0:07:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来是这样的啦  不过被强制遣返了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.37,0:07:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强制遣返？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.77,0:07:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.55,0:07:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我手臂骨折了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.87,0:07:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.45,0:07:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次你又做了什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.54,0:08:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  在山里和熊先生突然相遇了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.48,0:08:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  难道…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.37,0:08:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀  真强啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.35,0:08:09.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是废了一只手  我还真是幸运
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.27,0:08:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生说痊愈需要两周
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.06,0:08:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  不过我觉得和平时一样  三天就差不多了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.85,0:08:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  真不得了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.30,0:08:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要勉强自己  回房间好好休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.31,0:08:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  奇怪了怎么哥哥这么温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.38,0:08:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.74,0:08:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是关心你的身体…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.14,0:08:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.60,0:08:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么这么早就洗澡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.81,0:08:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么特别的意义啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.36,0:08:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为稍微出了点汗…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.61,0:08:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.42,0:08:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是为什么这里有叠得整整齐齐的女式内衣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.82,0:08:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.18,0:08:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要锁门呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.07,0:08:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫  先进浴池再说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.45,0:09:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哪里的谁在色诱哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.00,0:09:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀  红羽妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.76,0:09:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近  近近近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.44,0:09:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.28,0:09:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.92,0:09:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来被你击倒了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.03,0:09:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.10,0:09:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咿呀  真害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.88,0:09:26.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会倒在浴室呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.28,0:09:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  能在家里被近卫前辈所救
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.80,0:09:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然前辈  是我的王子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.99,0:09:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  你干嘛打扮成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.41,0:09:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈  真讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.02,0:09:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我平时不就这么穿嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.93,0:09:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈  别只是今天  请一直住下哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.75,0:09:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.39,0:09:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是说方便食品太便利所以讨厌吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.82,0:09:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最喜欢杯面了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.54,0:09:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到近卫前辈也是呢  我们真合得来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.83,0:10:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然是今天第一次吃  但出乎预料的好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.22,0:10:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.46,0:10:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从刚刚开始你的脸色就很不得了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.41,0:10:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.17,0:10:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥太喜欢杯面了  一直是这么紧张的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.26,0:10:13.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  所以不用介意的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.51,0:10:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.18,0:10:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点发冷
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.46,0:10:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦  是不是因为刚洗完澡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.51,0:10:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.79,0:10:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为H是不对的！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.06,0:10:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是流  马上就会说话的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.43,0:10:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.27,0:10:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么欢乐的事情  只有我被排斥在外
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.85,0:10:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得太过分了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.78,0:10:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.74,0:10:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心  我也没想白住
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.53,0:10:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以从今天起我就当你的女仆吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.31,0:10:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.39,0:10:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请尽管吩咐吧  主人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.15,0:11:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我回去  现在就回去！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.82,0:11:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得真过分呢  明明一下子就答应昴了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.09,0:11:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.21,0:11:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个家已经有近卫这个管家了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.20,0:11:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要女仆！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.65,0:11:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.96,0:11:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就一决胜负吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.84,0:11:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.23,0:11:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管家对女仆
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.51,0:11:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁能让主人得到满足
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.40,0:11:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是战争哦  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.89,0:11:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.80,0:11:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一回合  是姐姐大人的TKO胜利
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.59,0:11:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看样子对我的揉肩服务很满意呢  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.44,0:11:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照这个气势  下回合也会赢的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.94,0:11:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学  来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.31,0:11:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.77,0:11:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  下面轮到昴了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.50,0:12:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏你想得出来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.08,0:12:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学  你最好有所觉悟
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.75,0:12:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.20,0:12:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,mouth  to  mouth
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.38,0:12:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.09,0:12:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.23,0:12:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  喂  振作一点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.70,0:12:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好  快点扶他上床…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.27,0:12:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  连哥哥…也死了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.17,0:12:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  次郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.63,0:12:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是感冒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.25,0:12:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥这个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.97,0:12:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  真的很担心你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.95,0:13:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.15,0:13:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就交给昴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.15,0:13:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.86,0:13:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要死掉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.70,0:13:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.51,0:13:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉已经舒服多了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.58,0:13:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎只是普通的感冒  没必要那么夸张啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.97,0:13:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  不要小看感冒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.67,0:13:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  也是啊  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.21,0:13:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有食欲吗  我做了饭
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.41,0:13:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么问题
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.24,0:13:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  是你做的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.41,0:13:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然做得挺辛苦的  不过我认为还算是病号餐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.71,0:13:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃一点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.93,0:13:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  当然…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.98,0:13:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  次郎  啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.43,0:13:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水  水
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.27,0:13:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行啊  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.35,0:13:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了治好感冒  不再多出一点汗的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.55,0:13:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出了好多汗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.07,0:14:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.90,0:14:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我用热毛巾帮你擦汗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.31,0:14:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,口渴了吧  这是特制果汁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.45,0:14:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让次郎睡得好  就用我家世代相传的安眠道具
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.56,0:14:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  所以我说过的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.14,0:14:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然那孩子拼命想要照顾你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.11,0:14:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但经常做无用功
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.99,0:14:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无用功啊…我能不能活到感冒痊愈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.80,0:14:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交换条件
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.31,0:14:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要得到帮助的话  你也要协助我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.48,0:14:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,协助？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.51,0:14:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.86,0:14:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想我来这个家的理由  就明白了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.58,0:14:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是…来和我们尽情地玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.35,0:14:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了把近卫带回去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.54,0:14:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答对了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.89,0:14:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是  为什么带我来这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.07,0:15:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你也有责任  别废话来帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.91,0:15:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,责任？我？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.16,0:15:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在吧  流
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.43,0:15:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奏大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.01,0:15:15.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  还以为是哪里来的肮脏眼镜男
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.91,0:15:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是那时的臭小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.96,0:15:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是你的错…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.26,0:15:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近昴都不叫我爸爸也是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.70,0:15:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,索要早安之吻就用平底锅扔我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.90,0:15:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫无疑问都是你的错！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.91,0:15:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显是你的交流方式有问题！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.87,0:15:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说是次郎同学的错的话只说对了一半
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.75,0:15:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上个月在游乐园不是发生事件了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.14,0:15:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这个大叔揍得很惨
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.75,0:15:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道原因是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.69,0:15:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  就是这个原因
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.70,0:15:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后昴和流就一直处于冷战状态
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.11,0:15:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这次超过了冷战的范畴  发展成了父女吵架
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.90,0:15:55.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「双方各打五十大板」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.73,0:15:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为触怒了我的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.69,0:16:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是被命令「在和好之前不准回来」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.48,0:16:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.76,0:16:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以次郎同学  你就原谅流吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.03,0:16:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来昴也会消气的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.34,0:16:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是想和好  但是为什么要这个臭小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.35,0:16:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离次郎远一点！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.65,0:16:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.06,0:16:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种地方体温会上升的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.64,0:16:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等一下  近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.02,0:16:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦  别对我说教！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.21,0:16:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要擅自跑出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.90,0:16:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道自己是病人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.55,0:16:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴…等一下  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.22,0:16:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌…我最讨厌父亲了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.53,0:16:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.80,0:16:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.23,0:16:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦说讨厌…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.88,0:16:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.45,0:16:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫  已经够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.57,0:16:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也该原谅他了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.54,0:17:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是因为我被揍的事情  已经不用在意了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.76,0:17:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人很担心你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.89,0:17:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.01,0:17:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是次郎的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.67,0:17:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在次郎病好之前我是不会回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.22,0:17:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.13,0:17:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是我的照顾方式不好我道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.21,0:17:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我也很担心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.39,0:17:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.86,0:17:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  连哥哥…也死了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.54,0:17:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥  不要死啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.79,0:17:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.93,0:17:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到哭泣的红羽妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.20,0:17:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想次郎会不会也因为生病死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.89,0:17:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到这些  胸口就感到撕裂般的恐惧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.40,0:17:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈死的时候也是  我…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.11,0:18:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  请让我在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.63,0:18:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话  我会感到不安的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.46,0:18:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.88,0:18:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.11,0:18:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴  快点送医院
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.45,0:18:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.68,0:18:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.05,0:18:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明发过誓不再让这家伙哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.77,0:18:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  勉强把你带出来是我不对
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.28,0:18:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就叫车
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.06,0:18:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚开
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.65,0:18:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没听到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.10,0:18:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那里滚开  凉月
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.53,0:18:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生病什么的  我才不会这样死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.21,0:18:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是说过我从小就受过锻炼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.48,0:19:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.05,0:19:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  不用那么担心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.93,0:19:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用哭  也不用难过
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.52,0:19:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.99,0:19:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  我保证  我不会那么容易就挂的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.32,0:19:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会在你不知道的时候消失的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.90,0:19:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你就放心回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.31,0:19:29.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也为了凉月
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.81,0:19:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让重要的人担心  作为管家是不合格的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.07,0:19:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  你被解雇了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.05,0:19:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  遵命  主人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.34,0:19:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了  我的…管家…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.56,0:20:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  次郎真是个无可救药的大笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.46,0:20:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没有对大病初愈的人讲的台词吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.35,0:20:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自作自受
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.66,0:20:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老老实实接受我的照顾  就不会碰上那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.69,0:20:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.51,0:20:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.18,0:20:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我许下了「不会死」这一诺言
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.93,0:20:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎是重要的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.45,0:20:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不愿意看到朋友死去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.05,0:20:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果你打破约定马上就死掉的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.67,0:20:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是会再哭的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.53,0:20:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我还有点别的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.29,0:20:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别的事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.11,0:20:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实父亲也因为感冒病倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.83,0:20:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然很不情愿但还是去探望一下
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.33,0:20:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.91,0:20:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.89,0:20:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.06,0:20:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢…谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.23,0:20:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.76,0:20:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.83,0:20:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  真少见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.62,0:20:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.49,0:21:02.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个昴居然会对我之外的同学说谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.19,0:21:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看到了那个情形  也是没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.21,0:21:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候  拼命劝说昴的你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.63,0:21:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点不像胆小鬼了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.03,0:21:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算什么  在耍我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.72,0:21:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对你说了「滚开」还怀恨在心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.41,0:21:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.27,0:21:26.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次被男孩子这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.29,0:21:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  果然还是个胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.42,0:21:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么一来我们的共犯关系应该还要持续下去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.82,0:21:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你你你  你突然做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.72,0:21:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你慌什么啊  不就是KISS嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.93,0:21:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带一提  刚才是我的初吻
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.47,0:21:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是说初恋是近卫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.41,0:22:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要误会  我确实深爱着昴
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.16,0:22:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  初恋是初恋
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.40,0:22:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不代表现在还持续着
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.21,0:23:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要那样看着我的裙子！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.63,0:23:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我只是想要你裙子里面的东西而已！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.95,0:23:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里就算你这样说也…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.45,0:23:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很简单的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.05,0:23:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么样  也有「顺序」这种东西的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.69,0:23:55.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  该怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.63,0:23:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太不好意思了  我说不出口…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.02,0:24:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少废话  快说
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.81,0:24:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.47,0:24:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第5话  「请和我交往」


