[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 03 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.26,0:00:36.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.11,0:00:39.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.07,0:00:44.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.57,0:01:02.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.69,0:01:08.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.05,0:01:14.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.13,0:01:19.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.08,0:01:24.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.72,0:01:27.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.38,0:01:32.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.26,0:01:36.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.13,0:01:39.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.12,0:01:43.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.74,0:01:44.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.72,0:01:47.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.50,0:01:50.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.21,0:01:52.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.76,0:01:58.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.26,0:00:36.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.11,0:00:39.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.07,0:00:44.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情  飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.57,0:01:02.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.69,0:01:08.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.05,0:01:14.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定  不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.13,0:01:19.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.08,0:01:24.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西  就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.72,0:01:27.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧  很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.38,0:01:32.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.26,0:01:36.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.13,0:01:39.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.12,0:01:43.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.74,0:01:44.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.72,0:01:47.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.50,0:01:50.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.21,0:01:52.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.76,0:01:58.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中  直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天  就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界  怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线  我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧  只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3  越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.98,0:00:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.38,0:00:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  今天你也来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.42,0:00:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大门要关好啊  太不小心了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.38,0:00:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.38,0:00:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥  洗发水用光了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.33,0:00:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不～
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.37,0:02:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  是在床上
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.34,0:02:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为两个人很般配嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.43,0:02:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算有少少的障碍  只要双方有爱…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.50,0:02:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后红羽就把自己关在房里不肯出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.98,0:02:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道就这么不来上学…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.96,0:02:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  那没事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.55,0:02:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就在那里嘛  你的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.18,0:02:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.83,0:02:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找你好久了哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.61,0:02:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.50,0:02:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈看到我的内衣之后说了什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.27,0:02:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  倒也没说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.64,0:02:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没反应！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.51,0:02:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Boys Love！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.72,0:02:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这样啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.99,0:02:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥在和近卫前辈交往啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.59,0:02:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  昴喜欢你哥哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.48,0:02:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.15,0:02:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.27,0:02:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.96,0:02:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为次郎同学是在和我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.75,0:03:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说谎  我不相信
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.21,0:03:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侧腹的痣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.37,0:03:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的侧腹有痣对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.99,0:03:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为  为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.38,0:03:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是在床上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.26,0:03:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,床…床！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.25,0:03:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.58,0:03:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但  但是哥哥不习惯被女生碰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.44,0:03:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明很快就会流鼻血
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.96,0:03:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算有少少的障碍  只要双方有爱…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.72,0:03:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.91,0:03:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想为你加油
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.42,0:03:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你将来说不定会成为我的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.29,0:03:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多关照哦  红羽妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.14,0:03:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.71,0:03:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.98,0:03:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我也希望昴能和女生好好恋爱  所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.23,0:03:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼拜天去4人约会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.83,0:03:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.45,0:04:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别随便站在我的身后
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.92,0:04:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心  这是防身用的电击枪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.89,0:04:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过好好改造过了  只要对准要害就能完全…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.57,0:04:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么带这种东西来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.52,0:04:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我光是保护大小姐就已经竭尽全力了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.36,0:04:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以给我自己保护好自己
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.40,0:04:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头见
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.28,0:04:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那回头见  近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.07,0:04:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.68,0:04:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.32,0:04:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  你…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.28,0:04:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了  闭上眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.97,0:04:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮你看着  你就在这换吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.28,0:04:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  前途堪忧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.93,0:04:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.16,0:05:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想什么失礼的事吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.76,0:05:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.08,0:05:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.89,0:05:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能教我游泳吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.88,0:05:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不怎么会游
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.91,0:05:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少骗人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.38,0:05:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然可以…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.16,0:05:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的  昴  这里有这么多人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.71,0:05:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  关键时刻次郎同学会保护我的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.38,0:05:36.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然大小姐都这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.01,0:05:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了哦  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.45,0:05:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.21,0:05:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.02,0:05:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊  今天的近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.02,0:05:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有几年没到这里来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.56,0:05:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前来过啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.02,0:05:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  小时候
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.60,0:05:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和昴在这里被绑架了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.45,0:06:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绑架！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.94,0:06:06.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小奏  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.89,0:06:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目的好像是为了赎金哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.73,0:06:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事件很快就被解决  犯人也全都抓到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.01,0:06:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就因为这件事  至今都不让我随便出门
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.37,0:06:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴觉得是自己的责任吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.01,0:06:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认为我之所以被绑架都是她自身的错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.87,0:06:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为管家没能保护好主人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.08,0:06:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫那时候不也是小孩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.26,0:06:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  但自从那件事之后我和昴的距离就远了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.15,0:06:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你的女性恐惧症一样  昴也有弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.85,0:06:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱点？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.04,0:06:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  谈话结束
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.28,0:06:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别心不在焉了  现在你是我的恋人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.53,0:06:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.09,0:06:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.53,0:07:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.31,0:07:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.49,0:07:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展现了很多魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.53,0:07:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才刚刚开始哦  我们来制定作战计划吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.49,0:07:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.77,0:07:41.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴  我有点渴了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.92,0:07:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和次郎同学去买点饮料吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.09,0:07:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.97,0:07:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的  我都不是小孩了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.04,0:07:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.02,0:07:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和红羽妹妹关系真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.27,0:07:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.47,0:08:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真羡慕啊  我昨天还和父亲吵架了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.30,0:08:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.43,0:08:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\fsp-1}我告诉他  「次郎在没人的理科室把我推倒  摸着我的胸流鼻血」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.62,0:08:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\q2\fsp-1}然后他就说  「把那个混蛋眼镜带过来  我要把他大卸八块吊起来」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.96,0:08:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.86,0:08:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了  有人吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.79,0:08:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫  把主管叫来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.23,0:08:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.99,0:08:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女  女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.09,0:08:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彩香
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.79,0:08:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈  妈妈…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.95,0:08:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.95,0:09:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.46,0:09:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.66,0:09:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.83,0:09:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没生气啦  能让我生气的人可真了不起
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.05,0:09:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没生气啦  能让我生气的人可真了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.18,0:09:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,stand by me？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.52,0:09:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  「stand by me」就是呆在我身边的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.74,0:09:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样  很浪漫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.89,0:09:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不懂啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.48,0:09:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈  对5岁的孩子来说难度太高了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.35,0:09:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  近次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.04,0:09:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你名字里的「近」这个汉字就是这个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.81,0:09:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.08,0:09:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你将来可以成为能对某个人说出「stand by me」的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.20,0:09:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某个人？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.50,0:09:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  妈妈或者红羽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.82,0:09:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你认为重要的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.70,0:09:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变强吧  成为能说出「我来保护你  所以呆在我身边」的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.54,0:10:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「stand by me」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.18,0:10:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我和你  坂町次郎和坂町近次郎的约定哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.88,0:10:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  我有遵守着约定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.41,0:10:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.36,0:10:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微在天国的花田里见了见熟人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.31,0:10:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托你别开这种玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.13,0:10:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很担心你的  而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.92,0:10:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.48,0:10:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.48,0:10:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体没事的话  就先回大小姐那里去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.45,0:10:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.60,0:10:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.31,0:10:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  有人说拿给你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.45,0:10:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好你好  听得到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.82,0:11:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.64,0:11:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你还挺冷静的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.46,0:11:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明那么重要的主人都不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.29,0:11:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫昴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.53,0:11:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再问一遍  你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.19,0:11:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只说一遍给我听好了  管家同学
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.73,0:11:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本大爷就是绑架犯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.27,0:11:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在起10分钟内到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.94,0:11:27.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通知警察的话就游戏结束哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.15,0:11:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  我一个人去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.65,0:11:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说蠢话！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.93,0:11:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情变成这样是我的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.89,0:11:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能让次郎遇到危险
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.20,0:11:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.65,0:11:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.76,0:11:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青春啊  友情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.52,0:11:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么贵安  管家同学
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.85,0:11:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.64,0:11:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事  这不就和被女生碰到的我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.91,0:12:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴也有弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.15,0:12:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫  难道你…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.54,0:12:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕刀具吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.58,0:12:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道  绑架事件的时候也…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.63,0:12:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  自从那件事以后就很怕用刀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.47,0:12:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  只是看看身体就会使不上劲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.31,0:12:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我作为管家是一个缺陷品
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.78,0:12:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既不是男生  而且还有刀具恐惧症
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.44,0:12:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让连主人也无法好好保护的我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.98,0:12:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担任大小姐的管家也许本来就不合适
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.82,0:12:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  即便如此
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.21,0:12:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想当大小姐的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.27,0:12:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.58,0:12:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对会把你妹妹救出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.48,0:12:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以在这里等…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.26,0:13:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.21,0:13:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后你说什么我都会答应
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.10,0:13:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.01,0:13:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.62,0:13:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个人的话  在那道门里面
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.92,0:13:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在管家同学醒来之前  你陪我玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.88,0:13:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙的目标是近卫吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.47,0:13:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别死了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.50,0:13:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太得意忘形了  臭小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.98,0:13:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.65,0:13:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  次郎  次郎他…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.83,0:14:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  很耐打嘛  受了刚才那一击居然还能站着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.72,0:14:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没接受过  这样子就会被打倒的那种令人羡慕的教育啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.38,0:14:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.34,0:14:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打的漂亮  但不管来几次我都会站起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.18,0:14:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.51,0:14:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多到结束游戏的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.99,0:14:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我也不想做到这地步的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.23,0:14:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.19,0:14:44.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  已经动不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.63,0:14:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.86,0:14:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近  近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.37,0:14:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  现在开始就是我的工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.96,0:14:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来得真晚啊  管家同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.58,0:15:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不发抖吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.92,0:15:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前在这里的时候  你可是边哭边发抖呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.64,0:15:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被刀子顶着威胁的时候  像只可怜的小羊一样全身打颤呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.94,0:15:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前绑架凉月和近卫的犯人？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.12,0:15:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不是全都被抓到了吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.88,0:15:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不同了  我…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.32,0:15:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是管家
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.81,0:15:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  才不怕那种刀子！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.37,0:15:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.39,0:15:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  那家伙真帅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.66,0:15:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.92,0:15:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.64,0:15:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经吃不下了  嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.64,0:15:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.70,0:16:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.08,0:16:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为我的疏忽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.68,0:16:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让大小姐和红羽妹妹遇上这种危险
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.91,0:16:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有资格当管家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.81,0:16:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是好好地保护我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.17,0:16:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为主人怎么能开除如此优秀的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.95,0:16:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小奏
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.76,0:16:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.47,0:16:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的我  这样不称职的管家也可以陪在小奏身边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.99,0:16:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  当然
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.32,0:16:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后也要一直陪在我身边
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.36,0:16:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为管家
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.92,0:16:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时  作为朋友  一辈子侍奉在我的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.34,0:16:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是命令哦  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.25,0:16:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  遵命  大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.01,0:16:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.69,0:16:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来解决了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.90,0:16:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还想再打吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.99,0:17:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.12,0:17:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫流  昴的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.76,0:17:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且是凉月家的现任当家  也就是我父亲的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.60,0:17:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.19,0:17:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛啊  父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.21,0:17:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.86,0:17:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟  醒了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.89,0:17:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤没什么大碍  我手下留情了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.00,0:17:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗谁啊  你绝对是卯足劲打的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.72,0:17:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不打死你我已经手下留情了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.90,0:17:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.96,0:17:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧  原本剧本里就没打算让那个孩子受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.68,0:17:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剧本啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.04,0:17:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挑明了说  我很讨厌你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.54,0:18:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心  我也讨厌你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.46,0:18:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  挺会说的嘛  臭小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.90,0:18:07.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我说几遍  笨蛋老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.04,0:18:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流  你可以退下了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.46,0:18:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命  奏大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.18,0:18:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流和次郎同学很像啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.39,0:18:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里像了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.12,0:18:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如很关心家人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.36,0:18:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  流的话已经超越了关心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.02,0:18:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点过度保护的味道了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.23,0:18:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但对流来说  昴是唯一的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.77,0:18:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是情有可原的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.55,0:18:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.63,0:18:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴的母亲  在她5岁的时候就去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.47,0:18:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体本来就很虚弱  生下昴之后越来越…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.37,0:18:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前你也说过吧  「女孩子原本是不能成为管家的」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.55,0:18:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我家的人也建议过流再婚  但昴哭着反对
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.35,0:18:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说「我不要新的妈妈」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.94,0:19:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定很害怕  就像自己妈妈的存在会消失一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.94,0:19:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才那么拼命想当管家吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.83,0:19:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你卷进来真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.40,0:19:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想  和同样患有恐惧症的你接触
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.18,0:19:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会有所改善
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.98,0:19:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是今天的绑架事件吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.92,0:19:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵哈哈哈哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.12,0:19:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  回答正确  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.32,0:19:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个声音原来是你吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.00,0:19:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很感激你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.09,0:19:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏你们  昴才可以继续当我的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.04,0:19:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.12,0:19:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有资格说近卫的老爸过度保护
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.26,0:19:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.86,0:19:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我爱着昴嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.71,0:19:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.90,0:19:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的哦  我的初恋是昴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.65,0:19:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为我的管家的朋友  谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.30,0:20:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我进来了  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.20,0:20:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.98,0:20:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过「之后你说什么我都会答应」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.22,0:20:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在打我的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.01,0:20:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不  话虽如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.66,0:20:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好害怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.82,0:20:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是好好地保护了凉月吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.03,0:20:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不是什么缺陷品了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.95,0:20:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  不对不对不对
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.36,0:20:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害怕的才不是那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.89,0:20:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也许再也见不到次郎了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.35,0:20:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被刀刺中…次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.52,0:20:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次在学校交到的朋友…说不定会死…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.34,0:20:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很害怕…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.28,0:20:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.10,0:20:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  就算你道歉  也决不原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.64,0:21:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变强吧  成为能说出「我来保护你  所以呆在我身边」的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.37,0:21:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「stand by me」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.60,0:21:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  约好了  我会变得更强
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.88,0:21:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧  近卫前辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.80,0:21:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从姐姐大人那里听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.28,0:21:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「哥哥现在说不定在逼近卫前辈就范」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.19,0:21:21.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.95,0:21:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月那家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.58,0:21:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明和姐姐大人在交往  居然还在勾引近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.32,0:21:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和大小姐在交往？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.93,0:21:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然对小奏下手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.94,0:21:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被杀的…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.67,0:21:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是有活力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.03,0:21:42.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙  又算计我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.83,0:21:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说得真难听啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.37,0:21:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之跟我来  你是人质
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.99,0:21:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女性恐惧症没关系了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.11,0:21:52.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隔着袖子的话  总能忍耐过去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.57,0:21:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.13,0:21:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.88,0:21:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为你胡言乱语
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.23,0:22:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  我也说了真话哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.47,0:22:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说「初恋是昴」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.25,0:22:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  女孩子好可怕
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.61,0:23:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  近卫  你在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.22,0:23:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了服侍主人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.39,0:23:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.74,0:23:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点也不害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.23,0:23:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我能把关键部位遮起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.04,0:23:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  通通脱掉！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.82,0:24:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.94,0:24:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第4话  「不要一直盯着看啊…」


