[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 11 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.26,0:01:19.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.11,0:01:22.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.07,0:01:27.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.57,0:01:45.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.69,0:01:51.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.05,0:01:57.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.13,0:02:02.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.08,0:02:07.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.72,0:02:10.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.38,0:02:15.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.26,0:02:19.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.13,0:02:22.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.12,0:02:26.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.74,0:02:27.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.72,0:02:30.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.50,0:02:33.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.21,0:02:35.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.76,0:02:41.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.26,0:01:19.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.11,0:01:22.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.07,0:01:27.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情  飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.57,0:01:45.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.69,0:01:51.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.05,0:01:57.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定  不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.13,0:02:02.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.08,0:02:07.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西  就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.72,0:02:10.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧  很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.38,0:02:15.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.26,0:02:19.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.13,0:02:22.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.12,0:02:26.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.74,0:02:27.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.72,0:02:30.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.50,0:02:33.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.21,0:02:35.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.76,0:02:41.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中  直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天  就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界  怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线  我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧  只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3  越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.92,0:00:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴  我进来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.62,0:00:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  大小姐  请稍等
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.68,0:00:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没准备好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.63,0:00:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.94,0:00:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来帮你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.34,0:00:27.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐这边
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.98,0:00:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二学期开始就这么忧郁吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.90,0:00:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没这回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.90,0:00:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.94,0:00:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  心跳得这么快
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.99,0:00:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近发生什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.58,0:00:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要一个人承受的哦  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.37,0:00:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.40,0:00:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道  与次郎同学有关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.67,0:00:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说被问到「今天的内衣是什么样的？」之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.09,0:00:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.36,0:00:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过有烦恼的话要说哦
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.19,0:02:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.20,0:02:52.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今天开始就是新学期！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.93,0:02:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,围巾固！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.27,0:02:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德州四叶草固！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.77,0:02:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波士顿蟹式固！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.19,0:03:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我还有晨练  先走了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.60,0:03:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.98,0:03:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽说已经习惯了  一大早就来好累啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.06,0:03:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.05,0:03:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.68,0:03:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.57,0:03:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还认为我会把你的秘密说出去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.39,0:03:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信次郎…作为好友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.83,0:03:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是…好友
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.52,0:03:32.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.05,0:03:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  很对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.34,0:03:40.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还无法治好次郎的女性恐惧症
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.10,0:03:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么简单就能治好的话就不用烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.13,0:03:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这倒也是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.40,0:03:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「第二学期起得构思更过激的治疗计划才行」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.88,0:03:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐也这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.83,0:03:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…请务必手下留情
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.16,0:03:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.81,0:03:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.42,0:04:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闪开！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.56,0:04:01.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是你啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.83,0:04:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  危险！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.21,0:04:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.81,0:04:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.52,0:04:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回想起给次郎做人工呼吸时的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.60,0:04:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来  我和这家伙…kiss…了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.98,0:04:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.68,0:04:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.80,0:04:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在做什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.25,0:04:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个男人kiss！？  在这种马路上！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.44,0:04:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你在兴奋什么啊  笨蛋胆小鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.15,0:04:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了躲开才这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.10,0:04:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是叫你闪了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.38,0:05:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说你那辆摩托是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.10,0:05:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砍价买的二手车
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.36,0:05:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您没事吧  昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.47,0:05:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么问候的话不一样啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.34,0:05:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没受伤  宇佐美呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.56,0:05:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我不要紧！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.99,0:05:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.54,0:05:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为表歉意请收下这个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.61,0:05:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失陪了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.28,0:05:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.60,0:05:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.16,0:05:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只好吃掉了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.08,0:05:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是刚刚宇佐美叼在嘴里的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.26,0:05:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算不算是间接接吻呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.43,0:05:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧  要迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.65,0:05:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.16,0:05:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.96,0:06:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇迹啊  你竟然会认真做作业
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.19,0:06:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是应该的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.78,0:06:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为在女仆咖啡厅打工的谢礼才让你抄的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.80,0:06:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对对…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.57,0:06:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂你为什么会知道啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.39,0:06:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊  有地狱耳
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.78,0:06:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一说超级恐怖的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.87,0:06:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  马上要上课了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.74,0:06:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.27,0:06:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.87,0:06:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要和昴一起吃午饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.09,0:06:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天加上我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.04,0:06:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  请用
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.69,0:06:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好豪华的便当啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.69,0:06:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别客气尽管吃
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.46,0:06:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把你的那份分出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.68,0:06:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.91,0:06:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  让我来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.41,0:06:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.23,0:06:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  请品尝
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.64,0:06:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.84,0:06:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.06,0:06:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美味！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.31,0:07:02.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,煮烂的肉与饱含奶油回味无穷的酱汁完美融合
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.06,0:07:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,产生了绝妙的口感
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.01,0:07:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎样的料理！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.87,0:07:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是普通的奶油炖肉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.28,0:07:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.99,0:07:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近  近卫！？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.48,0:07:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.86,0:07:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.11,0:07:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好热…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.01,0:07:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月！近卫为什么会这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.41,0:07:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为秘密佐料里包含了白葡萄酒啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.25,0:07:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过加了一滴就变成这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.13,0:07:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过敏感了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.89,0:07:38.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敏感有什么不好～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.32,0:07:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀  被酱汁弄脏了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.66,0:07:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴  帮他擦掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.49,0:07:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了  大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.07,0:07:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.30,0:07:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个酱汁  真美味
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.63,0:08:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.09,0:08:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请  请住手…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.36,0:08:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.14,0:08:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月  想想办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.86,0:08:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要是阻止她的话不就算不上治疗了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.85,0:08:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  我是你的好友不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.83,0:08:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也把你当作最好的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.94,0:08:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.69,0:08:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了不破坏现在的关系
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.10,0:08:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.99,0:08:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了  全是说那种话的次郎不好！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.47,0:08:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种话是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.46,0:08:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  我有话想对你说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.31,0:08:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  对你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.50,0:08:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙想干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.51,0:08:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.75,0:09:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微让她休息一会比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.31,0:09:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我背她到保健室吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.67,0:09:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.62,0:09:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心无杂念  我要心无杂念
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.16,0:09:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚  这家伙想说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.87,0:09:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼福  眼福啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.89,0:09:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚开学就看到好东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.02,0:09:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背着因战斗受伤的少年前进的眼镜男子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.73,0:09:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心中呐喊着「活下去！」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.80,0:09:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别吵！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.04,0:09:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.41,0:09:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫的话  在保健室睡着了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.21,0:09:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.49,0:09:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.21,0:09:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  没什么…啾！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.42,0:09:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.64,0:09:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.79,0:09:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  刚才那可爱的声音是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.59,0:09:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我也听到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.18,0:09:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  凉月？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.38,0:09:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.98,0:09:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道身体不舒服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.71,0:10:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会问这个呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.99,0:10:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你都「啾」了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.79,0:10:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是错觉啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.34,0:10:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细想想  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.35,0:10:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么会发出那种声音呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.70,0:10:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.70,0:10:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太烦了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.75,0:10:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都说没事了啾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.68,0:10:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.71,0:10:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.59,0:10:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是有原因的啾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.23,0:10:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别用这么怜悯的眼神看我…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.85,0:10:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.32,0:10:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.28,0:10:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.53,0:10:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你的声音吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.24,0:10:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人  和刚刚那可爱的声音差远了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.39,0:10:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀  是我的声音啾！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.12,0:10:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.81,0:10:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.19,0:10:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.73,0:10:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊  喉咙有些不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.60,0:10:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧吧  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.05,0:10:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去保健室比较…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.63,0:10:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.19,0:10:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.70,0:10:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.09,0:11:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.56,0:11:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.08,0:11:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.93,0:11:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我有个秘密没对学校里的任何人说过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.14,0:11:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.76,0:11:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.08,0:11:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学  这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.86,0:11:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我唯一的弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.05,0:11:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炼～乳！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.33,0:11:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶～牛～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.11,0:11:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对保健室的老师做了什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.17,0:11:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甩了她两三耳光  就哭着出去了啾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.72,0:11:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是用钞票啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.26,0:11:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.59,0:11:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾啾啾～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.14,0:12:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么刚才的那是？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.92,0:12:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是打嗝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.42,0:12:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打嗝？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.96,0:12:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错啾  我一开始打嗝就停不下来了啾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.53,0:12:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  就像这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.88,0:12:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来只是说话的时候句尾加上「啾」而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.73,0:12:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打嗝的声音似乎很有特色啾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.47,0:12:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常在句尾出现
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.90,0:12:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  为什么那是弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.75,0:12:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.11,0:12:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的我  在周围人的眼里看起来很可爱啾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.07,0:12:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.18,0:12:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原以为你只是直率而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.82,0:12:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你会自卖自夸到那份上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.97,0:12:39.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啰嗦啾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.25,0:12:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  也算很可爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.02,0:12:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.82,0:12:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学  你能不能帮我停下打嗝啾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.77,0:12:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  刚刚想抱凉月！？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.73,0:12:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐的打嗝  是具有魔性的打嗝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.33,0:12:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.15,0:13:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许很难以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.33,0:13:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到大小姐打嗝的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.02,0:13:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是男性  都会被这种魅力附体
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.47,0:13:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.19,0:13:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的  曾经就因为这个  发生过事件
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.03,0:13:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事件？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.27,0:13:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约在十年前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.11,0:13:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时还是小学生的大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.49,0:13:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被邀请去参加某个派对时发生的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.24,0:13:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.89,0:13:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.95,0:13:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由我来帮大小姐停止打嗝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.55,0:13:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后连会场的保镖和警备员都无法收拾事态
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.06,0:13:42.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无奈只能出动警视厅的机动队
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.04,0:13:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月家把这为称为「打嗝之乱」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.81,0:13:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规模多么庞大的笨蛋故事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.63,0:13:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四年之前也发生过类似的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.81,0:13:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候  昴把事件摆平了啾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.18,0:13:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  真不愧是近卫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.22,0:14:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  昴是最棒的管家啾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.79,0:14:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.59,0:14:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.10,0:14:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蹭蹭  好可爱～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.93,0:14:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.02,0:14:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.47,0:14:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不是觉得平时一直很冷静的大小姐发出那样的声音很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.44,0:14:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了  差不多该放开了啾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.71,0:14:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再让我抱一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.16,0:14:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  对不起  现在马上放开
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.18,0:14:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.79,0:14:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎给我闭嘴！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.40,0:14:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你打算从我这里夺走可爱的大小姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.09,0:14:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷不防地说什么啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.21,0:14:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法原谅！把你肃清掉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.10,0:14:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  先冷静一下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.50,0:14:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴  现在你先回家  把停止打嗝的道具拿来啾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.88,0:14:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有那种道具啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.25,0:14:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…现在离开大小姐身边的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.74,0:15:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只会抱着我也帮不上什么忙啾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.53,0:15:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样说也没错
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.02,0:15:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.44,0:15:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在担心昴的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.18,0:15:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她回去真的好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.43,0:15:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来就打算让她回去啾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.15,0:15:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好好想想  道具只要一个电话就可以让别人带来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.30,0:15:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  为什么要…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.28,0:15:35.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要和你单独相处啾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.27,0:15:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学  告诉我啾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.97,0:15:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和昴发生了什么啾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.43,0:15:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴对你的态度的变化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.40,0:15:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该也注意到了啾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.82,0:15:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对昴说了什么啾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.30,0:15:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么也没…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.45,0:15:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.89,0:15:55.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不回答的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.52,0:15:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.10,0:16:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.32,0:16:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止打嗝的道具  从家里拿来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.56,0:16:15.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太快了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.15,0:16:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.50,0:16:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了啊  衣服…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.17,0:16:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且大小姐也…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.22,0:16:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.36,0:16:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是被次郎同学袭击了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.35,0:16:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,袭击的那方是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.39,0:16:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打嗝也停了  回教室吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.98,0:16:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？什么时候停的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.88,0:16:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了哦  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.06,0:16:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么简单就停了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.92,0:16:48.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明说是唯一的弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.36,0:16:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道是故意的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.60,0:16:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子是有很多秘密的啾
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.00,0:16:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过次郎同学真的很温柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.97,0:17:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和你单独相处  稍微有点开心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.42,0:17:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.78,0:17:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.83,0:17:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  又不是认真的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.29,0:17:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.77,0:17:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.06,0:17:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫！凉月！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.47,0:17:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.30,0:17:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.77,0:17:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  能站起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.54,0:17:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.04,0:17:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.19,0:17:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.02,0:17:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凉月同学不妙了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.14,0:17:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.96,0:17:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连医院都有经营啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.40,0:17:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过是脚扭了而已  太夸张了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.98,0:17:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  以防万一  请接受严密检查
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.58,0:18:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.37,0:18:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉  明明和我在一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.30,0:18:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  又不是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.93,0:18:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我没注意
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.43,0:18:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.86,0:18:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会向父亲大人好好说明的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.54,0:18:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  你没什么好在意的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.27,0:18:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去准备点喝的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.76,0:18:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.49,0:18:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来伤得更重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.13,0:18:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.66,0:18:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.84,0:18:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.67,0:18:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你小子在做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.13,0:19:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大  大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.88,0:19:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你也想住院啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.59,0:19:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.97,0:19:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.15,0:19:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉  有我陪着还让大小姐受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.09,0:19:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你回去休息
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.71,0:19:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  今天我要留在医院…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.23,0:19:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说让你回去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.74,0:19:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  大小姐还需要人照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.84,0:19:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.01,0:19:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经不是管家了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.46,0:19:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔  为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.85,0:19:40.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让重要的大小姐受伤  作为管家当然要负责
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.59,0:19:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴  之前你做得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.81,0:19:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.66,0:19:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以够了  休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.65,0:19:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.90,0:19:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让昴辞去管家这件事  我不同意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.39,0:20:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  昴是最棒的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.84,0:20:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  这已经是决定好的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.26,0:20:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲大人那边由我去解释
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.27,0:20:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对会说服他的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.95,0:20:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对昴来说太勉强了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.35,0:20:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  不当管家的话  就没有了女扮男装的必要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.93,0:20:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能以女孩子的身份上学  这也是为昴着想
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.60,0:20:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  您去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.18,0:20:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还用问吗  当然是去父亲大人那里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.37,0:20:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  不用去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.70,0:20:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.52,0:20:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前受了您很多照顾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.24,0:20:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有很多不周到的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.61,0:20:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我能当大小姐的管家真的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.54,0:20:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是…很幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.60,0:20:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学  拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.57,0:21:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.32,0:21:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.41,0:21:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.33,0:21:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么能放开
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.76,0:21:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算倒下我也不会放开的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.39,0:21:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.18,0:21:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要一个人承担全部
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.69,0:21:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难过的心情也好  不甘的心情也好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.37,0:21:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都丢给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.82,0:21:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管什么我都会接受
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.99,0:21:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天早上我可不是白让红羽暴捶的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.79,0:21:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.19,0:21:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  已经够了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.05,0:21:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有保守秘密的必要了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.23,0:21:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  也要和你  分开了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.77,0:21:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到极限了…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.12,0:22:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近…卫…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.01,0:23:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经不是管家了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.66,0:23:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是胆小鬼了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.90,0:23:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.91,0:23:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始变身野兽！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.45,0:23:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为大胆野性的男人！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.25,0:23:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了  近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.50,0:23:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.34,0:23:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.65,0:23:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  但是  要好好戴上哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.31,0:23:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.15,0:23:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.14,0:23:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.88,0:23:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话  我…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.65,0:24:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然章鱼烧要蘸蛋黄酱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.49,0:24:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」第12话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.42,0:24:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.66,0:24:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能变成崭新的两个人吗


