[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 05 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.26,0:00:44.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.11,0:00:47.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.07,0:00:52.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.57,0:01:10.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.69,0:01:16.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.05,0:01:22.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.13,0:01:27.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.08,0:01:32.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.72,0:01:35.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.38,0:01:40.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.26,0:01:44.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.13,0:01:47.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.12,0:01:51.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.74,0:01:52.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.72,0:01:55.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.50,0:01:58.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.21,0:02:00.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.76,0:02:06.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.26,0:00:44.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.11,0:00:47.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.07,0:00:52.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情  飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.57,0:01:10.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.69,0:01:16.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.05,0:01:22.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定  不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.13,0:01:27.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.08,0:01:32.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西  就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.72,0:01:35.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧  很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.38,0:01:40.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.26,0:01:44.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.13,0:01:47.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.12,0:01:51.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.74,0:01:52.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.72,0:01:55.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.50,0:01:58.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.21,0:02:00.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.76,0:02:06.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中  直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天  就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界  怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线  我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧  只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3  越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.29,0:00:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个炸肉丸看起来好好吃  给我一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.28,0:00:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好哦  那和你的煎鸡蛋换吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.64,0:00:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我说  放学后要不要顺便逛下站前大厦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.67,0:00:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说新品的杏仁饼干今天上市
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.91,0:00:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然很不错啊  那个颜色
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.01,0:00:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粉底也有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.82,0:00:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  只有唇膏
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.40,0:00:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊  哪里哪里  在哪买的
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.46,0:02:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请和我交往
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.53,0:02:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  闪开！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.81,0:02:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～还以为死定了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.07,0:02:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.55,0:02:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.75,0:02:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个样子大概快咽气了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.11,0:02:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们学校的校服？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.07,0:03:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  请问…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.19,0:03:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.40,0:03:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.72,0:03:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撞到人了  要打110才行
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.66,0:03:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  果然还是应该隐藏证据…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.10,0:03:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  我的话没事哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.27,0:03:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么还活着！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.63,0:03:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的是人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.59,0:03:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说这么没礼貌的话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.60,0:03:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是因为家里的原因身体稍微结实了点而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.44,0:03:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…是我们学校的学生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.56,0:03:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.73,0:03:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要问这个
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.49,0:03:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说也是场事故  至少名字我应该知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.24,0:03:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  我不想说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.34,0:03:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那学年呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.99,0:03:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2年级
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.27,0:03:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是2年级
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.70,0:03:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是几班…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.40,0:04:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么在那种地方…！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.17,0:04:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨  讨厌  你在看哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.80,0:04:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不是的  那里面有我想要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.15,0:04:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要的东西？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.22,0:04:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己不太好拿  你能帮我拿一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.29,0:04:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为  为什么我要做那种事！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.47,0:04:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实在不愿意的话  我只好自己来拿了…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.23,0:04:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.65,0:04:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.56,0:04:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.92,0:04:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然做什么啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.40,0:04:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴  变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.55,0:04:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会让你脱我衣服啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.43,0:04:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我脱衣服？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.71,0:04:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死好了  被我踢死好了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.15,0:04:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  等…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.22,0:04:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好险
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.06,0:04:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.24,0:04:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.76,0:04:53.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道…你要拿的就是这个？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.58,0:04:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你以为我要什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.95,0:05:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么刚才没发现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.01,0:05:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粉…色的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.89,0:05:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为那家伙的哥哥  你还真没用呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.25,0:05:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识红羽？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.55,0:05:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是  真是难以置信！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.60,0:05:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你这种人…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.62,0:05:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要出来了  什么东西要出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.55,0:05:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  告诉我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.27,0:05:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你这种人…能成为昴大人的朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.54,0:05:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.03,0:05:43.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这么难得我就告诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.40,0:05:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫宇佐美
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.07,0:05:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兔子？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.90,0:05:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是兔子！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.37,0:05:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浪岚学园2年D班  所属于手艺部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.73,0:05:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宇佐美政宗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.32,0:05:57.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手艺部…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.61,0:06:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.46,0:06:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.13,0:06:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.28,0:06:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.15,0:06:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.10,0:06:12.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  我吓了一跳哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.11,0:06:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不能把昏倒在路边的你放着不管
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.00,0:06:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就抬到学校来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.94,0:06:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是被车撞到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.88,0:06:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  差不多就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.34,0:06:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.32,0:06:27.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  没什么大问题
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.82,0:06:28.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.69,0:06:29.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.47,0:06:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.02,0:06:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚喊着意义不明的梦话…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.69,0:06:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦话？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.52,0:06:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「请原谅我吧  女王大人！」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.16,0:06:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.04,0:06:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「再这样被顶的话  就要看到另一个世界了」之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.46,0:06:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「两万  给你两万  饶了我吧  啊  不要  已经不行了…」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.88,0:06:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后还…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.95,0:06:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才体验过的事不都被直接反映出来了吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.32,0:06:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是有心病吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.59,0:06:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.99,0:07:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来  凉月她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.02,0:07:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没一起吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.72,0:07:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐在上课
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.15,0:07:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.92,0:07:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  是不是在躲着大小姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.63,0:07:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具体说的话  大概是在黄金周结束后开始的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.94,0:07:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么烦恼的话就告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.48,0:07:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  我和次郎不是朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.74,0:07:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友之间的话  至少可以商量一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.34,0:07:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.80,0:07:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  我有一个条件…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.76,0:07:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,条件？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.98,0:07:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭那天  希望你能陪我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.52,0:07:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.87,0:07:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像大小姐会因为班长的工作忙得不可开交
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.74,0:07:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然说「不用在意我  去好好享受学园祭」
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.63,0:07:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.32,0:07:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道学园祭该怎么逛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.73,0:08:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  希望你能和我一起逛学园祭…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.49,0:08:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真傻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.65,0:08:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.11,0:08:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去逛吧  学园祭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.00,0:08:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.53,0:08:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.36,0:08:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将会是个愉快的学园祭的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.50,0:08:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.12,0:08:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！尽管和我商量好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.98,0:08:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.27,0:08:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用客气哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.19,0:08:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听的时候别被吓到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.36,0:08:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个管家  一般的事吓不到我的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.59,0:08:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.97,0:08:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就说了  其实…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.25,0:08:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是关于我初吻的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.29,0:08:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为  为什么现在突然提这事！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.27,0:08:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难  难道是大小姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.04,0:08:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  因为很突然  吓了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.38,0:08:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也吓了一跳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.73,0:09:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  那是第一次…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.42,0:09:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然那家伙也这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.22,0:09:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.70,0:09:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  别说蠢话！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.88,0:09:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是第一次啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.56,0:09:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是吗  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.21,0:09:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.65,0:09:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果可以的话真想重来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.28,0:09:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.65,0:09:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说想重来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.52,0:09:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想重来！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.77,0:09:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算现在开始也好啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.66,0:09:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.89,0:09:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然说现在我们的确是在独处…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.62,0:09:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么都无法理解啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.00,0:09:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.02,0:09:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底是为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.38,0:09:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.41,0:09:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要做的话就快点…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.92,0:09:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.89,0:10:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你是个这么乖戾的人！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.58,0:10:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.66,0:10:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了  是KISS啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.33,0:10:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是你提出的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.04,0:10:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.41,0:10:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.95,0:10:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.36,0:10:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐  不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.43,0:10:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想做什么我是无所谓啦  不过要小心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.58,0:10:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在学校里你可是个男生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.09,0:10:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非  非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.16,0:10:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.91,0:10:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很久都没这样说话了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.41,0:10:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  先回教室了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.09,0:10:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没门  不会让你跑掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.06,0:10:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.20,0:10:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是知道我有女性恐惧症吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.09,0:10:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这是小小的治疗哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.88,0:10:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是为了这种事情专门过来的吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.29,0:10:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不～因为我们B班学园祭的节目决定了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.06,0:10:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来告诉你的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.35,0:11:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.66,0:11:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,cosplay女装咖啡厅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.70,0:11:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女装？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.07,0:11:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都说想看昴的女装呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.94,0:11:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能穿很可爱的衣服哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.07,0:11:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.24,0:11:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.92,0:11:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像掉东西了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.17,0:11:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个  在鞋柜发现的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.82,0:11:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还送情书？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.38,0:11:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学怎么想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.19,0:11:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.55,0:11:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我答应了告白  你会怎么想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.27,0:11:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？那就好好交往啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.46,0:11:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.56,0:11:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说昴  你会怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.94,0:11:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我被这封情书的主人强吻的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.34,0:11:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宰了他
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.70,0:11:50.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对大小姐做这种事的人  我不会原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.37,0:11:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.66,0:11:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可靠呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.51,0:11:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎同学  没事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.39,0:11:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸色不太好呢  要吃点头痛药吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.90,0:12:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以嘴对嘴喂你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.80,0:12:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那下回见  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.88,0:12:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拒绝告白之后也会回教室的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.61,0:12:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  贵安
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.27,0:12:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发展成这个样子  全都是那家伙的错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.60,0:12:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  那只黑心兔子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.56,0:12:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁黑心了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.99,0:12:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.36,0:12:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很重要的话要对你说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.46,0:12:31.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘟嘟嘟  嘟嘟嘟  蛋黄酱注入！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.00,0:12:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个黑丝美腿的特写是近卫吗…原来是我啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.60,0:12:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  请和我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.29,0:12:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.04,0:12:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯什么嗯  说了和我交往
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.76,0:12:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正确地说是和我扮成情侣  时间是到学园祭结束
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.80,0:12:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先告诉你  你没有拒绝的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.27,0:13:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊  你有什么不满吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.49,0:13:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  为了说那种玩笑话而特地把我叫到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.04,0:13:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是很重要的事  所以当然要选这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.77,0:13:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很中意这里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.37,0:13:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的话  能够一个人呆着
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.71,0:13:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.15,0:13:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里第一次见到了昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.97,0:13:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  是一见钟情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.18,0:13:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.11,0:13:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道「S4」吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.30,0:13:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是学园最大的近卫的粉丝俱乐部吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.88,0:13:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「S4」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.18,0:13:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「Shooting Star Subaru Sama」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.41,0:13:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是那里的会员
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.07,0:13:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才对我下那种毒手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.47,0:13:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这次的学园祭  我们「S4」有秘密活动
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.86,0:13:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么秘密活动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.96,0:13:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战争
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.44,0:13:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们「S4」和「用温暖的目光守护昴大人会」的全面战争
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.30,0:14:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事和你我交往有什么关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.28,0:14:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说在与昴大人交往的你一旦和女生交往
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.48,0:14:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让喜欢BL的「守望会」产生动摇？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.58,0:14:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是挺明白的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.30,0:14:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我没有理由听你的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.77,0:14:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不是免费的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.37,0:14:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活动结束我们胜利之后  就不再对你出手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.74,0:14:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会向「S4」上层这样请示
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.88,0:14:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛啊  讨厌吗  对我的长相不满？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.78,0:14:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不是  你非常可爱了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.97,0:14:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.97,0:14:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.19,0:14:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有我的困扰
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.54,0:14:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町近次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.16,0:14:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.97,0:14:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(242,323)\fs20}saka
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.97,0:14:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(298,323)\fs20}machikin
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.97,0:14:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(367,323)\fs20}jirou
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.97,0:14:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂    町近    次郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.26,0:14:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要叫我全名
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.87,0:14:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和名字一样的胆小鬼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.23,0:14:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那么怕惹怒昴大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.87,0:14:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？为什么会变成那样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.49,0:14:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少装蒜
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.63,0:15:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来「S4」和「守望会」对立的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.87,0:15:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你和昴大人在交往
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.33,0:15:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了那是误会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.75,0:15:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你们关系不是很好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.21,0:15:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经常在一起吃午饭什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.31,0:15:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？那种事朋友之间很正常吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.21,0:15:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人才不普通
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.17,0:15:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了主人凉月奏之外  不让任何人靠近的那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.47,0:15:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只对你敞开心扉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.77,0:15:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样已经够异常了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.74,0:15:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.52,0:15:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有证据的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.15,0:15:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪里看到的啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.78,0:15:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去买东西的时候  碰巧看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.75,0:15:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你送玩偶给昴大人  还像要拥抱一样相互靠近对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.65,0:15:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊不…那是因为我的女性恐惧…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.54,0:15:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  是你的兴趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.56,0:15:52.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你逼得昴大人不得不这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.68,0:15:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人最近好像变得有点女孩子气了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.64,0:15:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说举止有点像女孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.51,0:15:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都已经变成传闻了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.48,0:16:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是暴露了身份  近卫她就…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.30,0:16:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  是我让近卫这么做的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.99,0:16:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以把那照片删了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.85,0:16:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不行  你必须协助我的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.98,0:16:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝的话  我就把照片散布到整个学园
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.00,0:16:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.00,0:16:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  近卫  为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.48,0:16:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有去上课我才来找你的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.68,0:16:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.92,0:16:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴…昴…昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.95,0:16:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你说点什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.03,0:16:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我这样的普通学生  不可能和昴大人说话的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.66,0:16:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由你来说明
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.22,0:16:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要怎么说明啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.13,0:16:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直截了当地说我们是情侣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.73,0:16:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们偷偷摸摸地在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.43,0:16:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来介绍  这家伙名叫宇佐美政宗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.64,0:16:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点突然  我们…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.62,0:16:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…正在交往
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.06,0:16:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩笑的话  不怎么好笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.08,0:17:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近卫  那个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.41,0:17:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是次郎的什么人？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.03,0:17:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说点什么怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.88,0:17:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的在交往
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.67,0:17:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭也说好了要约会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.65,0:17:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.28,0:17:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭那天要和这孩子约会吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.39,0:17:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.83,0:17:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明都约好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.62,0:17:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎大骗子！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.62,0:17:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近近近近…近卫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.37,0:17:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  你不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.91,0:17:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭结束之前都会好好扮情侣的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.86,0:17:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  不要散布那张照片
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.34,0:17:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.40,0:17:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  今天的放学后赶快开始约会的预演吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.32,0:18:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  陪我去买东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.50,0:18:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要买点学园祭用的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.61,0:18:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,D班要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.83,0:18:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳装咖啡厅  灼热的恋爱冒险
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.79,0:18:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳装咖啡厅？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.32,0:18:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以要买泳装
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.74,0:18:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事和班上的女生一起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.36,0:18:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.02,0:18:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试穿试穿
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.52,0:18:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以进来了  但是仅限头部
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.85,0:18:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  我们是情侣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.91,0:18:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.27,0:18:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎  怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.96,0:18:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没有别的款式了吗  比如说比基尼什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.81,0:18:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在同学面前  不可能穿得那么难为情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.18,0:18:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.59,0:18:49.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不坏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.66,0:18:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那么就决定这件了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.15,0:18:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再不快点把头缩回去  我就砍了它
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.77,0:18:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买给我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.86,0:18:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.52,0:19:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为明明不是游泳部的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.51,0:19:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却要买这种正儿八经的竞技泳装  很难为情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.12,0:19:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被认为是有奇怪兴趣的人怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.59,0:19:12.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是游泳部的  而且还不是女生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.36,0:19:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己买
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.36,0:19:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少废话  买给我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.74,0:19:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.50,0:19:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.95,0:19:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.75,0:19:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件泳装还有余温
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.84,0:19:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才这家伙还穿着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.39,0:19:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛默不作声啊  难  难道说在闻味道？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.12,0:19:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋  变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.12,0:19:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会那么干啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.42,0:19:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.28,0:19:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走这边
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.77,0:19:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,车站是那边
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.26,0:19:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走回家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.23,0:19:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里走回去可是要花一小时的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.70,0:19:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有车票钱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.89,0:19:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都花在修理摩托车上了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.59,0:19:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个月很紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.33,0:19:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.08,0:20:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也走回去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.84,0:20:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为最近都没怎么锻炼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.44,0:20:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到家…会很晚的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.72,0:20:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正红羽也说了要准备学园祭会晚点回来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.68,0:20:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要紧吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.47,0:20:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.50,0:20:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早回去也没用
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.41,0:20:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町近次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.28,0:20:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(252,323)\fs20}saka
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.28,0:20:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(308,323)\fs20}machikin
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.28,0:20:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(377,323)\fs20}jirou
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.28,0:20:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂    町近    次郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.92,0:20:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说了别叫我全名
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.07,0:20:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要定好称呼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.92,0:20:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用亲切的称呼的话  不是很不自然吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.40,0:20:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲切…小佐美？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.71,0:20:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想被我从这里踢下去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.42,0:20:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请别这样  真的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.90,0:20:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  直到学园祭结束  你和我是情侣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.47,0:20:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说  是伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.96,0:20:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以和我约定一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.88,0:20:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约定？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.29,0:21:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管发生什么  都请相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.85,0:21:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.18,0:21:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会相信你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.24,0:21:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  请相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.01,0:21:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了  我会相信你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.57,0:21:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.32,0:21:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫宇佐美就好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.53,0:21:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.66,0:21:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,称呼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.90,0:21:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光叫名字就行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.75,0:21:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲切？也没什么不可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.98,0:21:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.46,0:21:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.07,0:21:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.18,0:21:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得和又笨又胆小的你很相配吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.16,0:21:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里配了！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.29,0:21:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请多关照  笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.01,0:21:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在骂人吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.90,0:23:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  次郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.51,0:23:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做「se」开头的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.05,0:23:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(309,323)\fs20}sentaku
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.05,0:23:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗衣服？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.98,0:23:48.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.27,0:23:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是更加激烈的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.81,0:23:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,323)\fs20}senbonnokku
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.81,0:23:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一千练
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.81,0:23:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}（注：指棒球中进行一千次击打练习）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.71,0:23:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是更加兴奋的事情哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.44,0:23:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(331,323)\fs20}sekuhara
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.44,0:23:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…性骚扰？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.96,0:23:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事我一直在做呀！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.86,0:23:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来一直在做啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.15,0:24:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想应该是你还没体验过的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.26,0:24:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是…se…se！
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.45,0:24:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集「迷茫管家与懦弱的我」
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.57,0:24:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第6话  「开始战争吧」


