[Script Info]
Title:Mayochiki BD 13 sc
Original Script:SumiSora
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: opjp,DFPMaruGothic-SB,17,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,10,1
Style: opcn,方正粗圆_GBK,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H006200C4,&HB4FF00FF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,10,1
Style: edjp,DFPMaruMoji-SL,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,8,10,10,8,1
Style: edcn,华康少女文字W5(P),20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00EA7500,&H96FF3C00,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,4,2,10,10,8,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.26,0:00:24.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.11,0:00:27.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.07,0:00:32.70,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}抱きしめて翔べ　遙か遠く
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.57,0:00:50.64,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}ゲームセットなんてない日々　イメージして
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.69,0:00:56.00,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}叶えたい未来　数えて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.05,0:01:02.08,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}打ち明け合ったら約束　あきらめない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.13,0:01:07.04,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}夢を形にするまで
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.08,0:01:12.59,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}好きなこと　全力で追いかけようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.72,0:01:15.35,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一緒に…ね!?　楽しくね!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.38,0:01:20.25,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}希望の羽広げて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.26,0:01:24.10,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}今、胸に生まれた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.13,0:01:27.03,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}揺るぎないこの気持ち
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.12,0:01:31.65,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}勇気と呼ぶため始めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.74,0:01:32.71,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.72,0:01:35.46,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}未知数のドアだって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.50,0:01:38.18,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怖がらず開けてね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.21,0:01:40.54,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.76,0:01:46.33,opjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}舞い上がれ　彼方へと
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.26,0:00:24.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.11,0:00:27.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.07,0:00:32.70,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}怀着这份心情  飞向远方
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.57,0:00:50.64,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}想像着没有尽头的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.69,0:00:56.00,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}细数着想要实现的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.05,0:01:02.08,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}说出心里话的我们约定  不要放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.13,0:01:07.04,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}直到将梦想变成现实
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.08,0:01:12.59,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}喜欢的东西  就要全力追寻
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.72,0:01:15.35,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}一起来吧  很开心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.38,0:01:20.25,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}张开希望的羽翼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.26,0:01:24.10,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}现在在胸口诞生的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.13,0:01:27.03,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}这不曾动摇的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.12,0:01:31.65,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}带着勇气启程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.74,0:01:32.71,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Be Starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.72,0:01:35.46,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}就算是未知数的门
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.50,0:01:38.18,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}也能毫不畏惧地打开
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.21,0:01:40.54,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}Flying far away
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.76,0:01:46.33,opcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,150)}飞扬空中  直至彼方
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}声に出して　楽しいって言っちゃったら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}雲一つ無い青空　この胸に広がってくよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハートシグナル　キュンと立てて　飛び込んだ世界
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}はみ出しちゃえ!　私と言うキャパシティ拡張　楽しいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}止まらないスピードになって恋してたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}急ごっ!　二人だけの時空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3　飛び越えて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君に逢いたいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}突き抜ける風になって届けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}もうちょっと　可愛くアプローチ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ハート型の未来になって
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}君にご奉仕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edjp,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}そばにいたいから
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.38,0:22:35.22,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}只要将快乐说出声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.61,0:22:43.28,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}万里无云的蓝天  就会在这心中展开
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.82,0:22:49.54,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在突然闯入的世界  怦然心跳地发射心灵的信号
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.85,0:22:58.52,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}冲破界线  我将快乐的容量扩张
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.26,0:23:04.70,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想以无法停止的速度恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.92,0:23:08.16,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧  只属于两人的时空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.53,0:23:11.55,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}1 to 3  越过阻碍
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.59,0:23:14.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想与你相见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.47,0:23:18.87,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}想化作穿透一切的风向你传递
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.13,0:23:22.39,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}略带可爱地接近
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.71,0:23:27.73,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}变成心形的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.79,0:23:30.47,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}为您效劳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.14,0:23:35.89,edcn,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}因为想在你身边
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------PREV-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.17,0:00:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.45,0:00:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久以前就一直喜欢你了！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.02,0:00:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人为什么会喜欢上别人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.82,0:00:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想解明
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.36,0:00:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋爱的…秘密
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.89,0:01:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请揉吧！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTA-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.12,0:01:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了吗  我的宝物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.59,0:02:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.61,0:02:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最佳推荐是戴眼镜的女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.43,0:02:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  不是有摘掉眼镜后的照片吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.07,0:02:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不戴眼镜时的表情  不觉得很工口吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.29,0:02:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.83,0:02:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摘下眼镜就是美少女
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.62,0:02:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真是萌啊  反差萌
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.69,0:02:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.02,0:02:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说为什么会变成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.91,0:02:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这本书是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.16,0:02:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.75,0:02:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有本BL的书在我房间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.02,0:02:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.41,0:02:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人来了  挂了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.86,0:02:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不需要推销
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.08,0:02:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要关门啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.74,0:02:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点把手放开  我要叫警察了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.38,0:02:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.25,0:02:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是个不折不扣的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.38,0:02:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到把我当成可疑人物？！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.22,0:02:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.11,0:03:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀～救命～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.63,0:03:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要被绑架监禁了～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.93,0:03:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你喊什么喊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.35,0:03:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底有什么事啊  找红羽吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.72,0:03:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  今天并不是来找红羽妹妹的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.23,0:03:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来您的房子真不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.26,0:03:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你突然这么夸我…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.85,0:03:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈的房间也很有生活气息  令人感动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.59,0:03:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的话不能听过就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.68,0:03:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀  说起前辈柔软的床…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.89,0:03:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你知道躺在我床上的感觉？！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.50,0:03:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  进入正题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.34,0:03:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.11,0:03:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我来这里  是有事想商量
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.35,0:03:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商量？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.31,0:03:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.02,0:04:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦  怎么…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.79,0:04:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要投了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.21,0:04:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么人！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.27,0:04:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法原谅  竟敢偷拍我的早浴姿态…！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.29,0:05:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  折射率1.60  超防水球面防反射镜片
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.97,0:05:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可视光线通过率35%～12%
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.30,0:05:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抗紫外线率达到99.9%的粗框墨镜啊啊啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.24,0:05:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…咦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.93,0:05:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是宝贵的画面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.71,0:05:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我会在这里…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.53,0:05:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴大人要点司康饼套餐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.24,0:05:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是来悠闲地喝茶的…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.59,0:05:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才拍的照片呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.60,0:05:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾  这样根本卖不出去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.21,0:05:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想卖的吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.17,0:05:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天守望会有场集会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.45,0:05:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在这次狠狠赚一笔的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.00,0:05:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流就  奈香流就…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.97,0:05:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不够钱制作下次活动要出的同人本了！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.36,0:05:59.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.24,0:06:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦  那可真是不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.34,0:06:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.21,0:06:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整件事昴刚才在电话里都告诉我了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.87,0:06:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.17,0:06:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请大小姐也严厉地批评她一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.00,0:06:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明只要和我好好商量一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.00,0:06:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会帮你的！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.58,0:06:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.09,0:06:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了…太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.04,0:06:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.93,0:06:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点照片算什么  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.47,0:06:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为交换  今后绝对别再私自偷拍我的管家了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.08,0:06:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要在可能的范围内  我都会尽力协助你的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.29,0:06:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.18,0:06:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了  别推别挤
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.40,0:06:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我这张
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.44,0:06:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要这张
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.60,0:06:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  这张照片是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.25,0:06:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样制作费就没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.74,0:07:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.25,0:07:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点不在状态
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.94,0:07:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只完成了一半
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.82,0:07:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只有前篇吗  小奈流
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.33,0:07:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太厚了  订书针订不下去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.02,0:07:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才想到找红羽妹妹来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.68,0:07:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有前篇的话别卖不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.16,0:07:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.99,0:07:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为有很多粉丝在等着奈香流的新作
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.71,0:07:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,粉丝？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.60,0:07:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连粉丝俱乐部都有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.53,0:07:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过说实在的很难为情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.95,0:07:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连打招呼说的都是奈香流的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.71,0:07:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打招呼？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.96,0:07:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3  2  1
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.80,0:07:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流～奈香流～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.82,0:07:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…请做出点反应
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.91,0:07:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.22,0:08:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  不在明早之前完工的话  活动的展区就浪费了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.37,0:08:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3  2  1
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.20,0:08:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流～奈香流～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.79,0:08:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.72,0:08:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  为什么连我都要做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.84,0:08:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一听我说会付工钱  扑过来的是宇佐美前辈吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.36,0:08:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  红羽妹妹也有工钱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.95,0:08:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.91,0:08:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工钱就是近卫前辈的…照片？！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.02,0:08:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是珍贵的日常照哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.98,0:08:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太厉害了  小奈流
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.48,0:08:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我这个的话  我什么都干
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.40,0:08:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么我能做的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.83,0:08:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你都那么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.67,0:08:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请进请进  哥哥今天住在黑濑前辈家所以不在
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.95,0:08:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  谁是攻谁是受呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.76,0:08:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次进男孩子的房间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.19,0:09:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实男生的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.24,0:09:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实男生的垃圾桶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.17,0:09:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.29,0:09:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实男生的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.00,0:09:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工口书！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.81,0:09:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  笨蛋胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.33,0:09:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町前辈对女孩子也有兴趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.89,0:09:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三角恋  说不定能行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.26,0:09:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为让我参观房间的回礼  把这本书也混在里面吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.89,0:09:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么进展
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.35,0:09:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.67,0:09:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  还要做多少啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.14,0:09:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借浴室用下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.70,0:09:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那我帮你准备毛巾
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.97,0:09:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样看来是赶不及在明早前完工了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.87,0:09:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,增加人手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.66,0:10:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.62,0:10:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴  昴大人？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.17,0:10:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且连凉月奏都在？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.61,0:10:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微试着拜托了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.14,0:10:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.85,0:10:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不愧是近卫前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.42,0:10:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.31,0:10:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能赶上真是太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.27,0:10:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  就算只有前篇…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.38,0:10:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是前篇吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.51,0:10:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,续篇还没什么灵感
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.24,0:10:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛  总之我们先回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.12,0:10:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  昴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.48,0:10:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.19,0:10:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  请等等
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.14,0:10:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.51,0:10:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话想问昴大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.03,0:10:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问我？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.98,0:10:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  稍微有点烦恼…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.10,0:11:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BL小说的话我不是很了解
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.44,0:11:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和BL没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.73,0:11:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼镜也…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.05,0:11:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和眼镜也没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.44,0:11:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  那你在烦恼什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.42,0:11:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真见外啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.38,0:11:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.42,0:11:15.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛快说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.28,0:11:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  稍微等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.12,0:11:23.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子的小奈流！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.12,0:11:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从没见过！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.03,0:11:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么事！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.37,0:11:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}「令人震惊的事实」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.29,0:11:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}「隐藏着的真相」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.12,0:11:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}「真凶的自白」
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.99,0:11:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么  我自己会解决的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.66,0:11:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.70,0:11:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别讲话讲一半啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.21,0:11:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算啦算啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.62,0:11:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  马上就到早上了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.68,0:11:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力把书运过去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.99,0:11:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等等！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.56,0:11:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乘法是我的强项
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.56,0:11:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs22}（注：黑濑×坂町…）
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TXTB-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.78,0:11:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次郎  我一直对你…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.56,0:12:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.52,0:12:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要打扮成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.29,0:12:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变装是跟踪的基础哦  小佐美前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.38,0:12:14.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要骗过自己人首先要融入他们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.34,0:12:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个说法好像有点不对劲…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.21,0:12:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小奈流的烦恼到底是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.09,0:12:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坂町…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.29,0:12:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连我们都不肯告诉…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.55,0:12:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能帮上忙就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.87,0:12:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部售完了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.62,0:12:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.37,0:12:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,3  2  1
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.38,0:12:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流～奈香流～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.02,0:12:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.70,0:12:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定比普通的打工更赚钱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.44,0:12:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有「我也来写吧」这种想法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.20,0:12:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.01,0:12:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漫咖
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.24,0:12:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动画店
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.44,0:12:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏店
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.03,0:13:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是和平时差不多嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.19,0:13:07.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.55,0:13:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有发觉到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.51,0:13:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才小奈流手里拿着的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.80,0:13:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都是男生和女生的恋爱故事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.43,0:13:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说不是BL
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.05,0:13:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.99,0:13:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.76,0:13:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.55,0:13:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.88,0:13:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋恋恋…恋爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.70,0:13:39.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是红羽妹妹和小佐美前辈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.35,0:13:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在做什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.24,0:13:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.58,0:13:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟踪…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.95,0:13:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便溜达溜达
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.48,0:13:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,bra…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.17,0:13:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮的火箭形状有弹性的胸部呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.45,0:13:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小也无可挑剔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.39,0:14:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸线也是满分
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.93,0:14:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎又变大了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.25,0:14:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说  烦恼是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.84,0:14:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那样的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.97,0:14:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.13,0:14:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么在意奈香流的烦恼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.33,0:14:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  我们想帮助有烦恼的小奈流
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.87,0:14:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.40,0:14:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候就实话实说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.74,0:14:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管什么我们都会听你说的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.04,0:14:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小佐美前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.32,0:14:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  请听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.06,0:14:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.34,0:14:39.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.37,0:14:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是  烦恼是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.43,0:14:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.54,0:14:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红羽妹妹  小佐美前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.71,0:14:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们对奈香流的胸部有什么感想？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.07,0:14:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然  不能和你们商量
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.76,0:14:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那和谁商量啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.34,0:15:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.62,0:15:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.98,0:15:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,综上所述  来找前辈商量了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.54,0:15:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太长了吧  话说回来  这和我房间有BL书有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.67,0:15:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一部分是奈香流脑补的  请谅解
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.24,0:15:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  你要商量什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.54,0:15:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在请和奈香流约会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.79,0:15:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.88,0:15:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  真亏前辈答应了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.66,0:15:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.49,0:15:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.63,0:15:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为会被干脆地拒绝呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.47,0:15:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.36,0:15:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴了比平时长了2公分的特别版猫耳也算物有所值了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.83,0:16:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.08,0:16:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天约会的安排是  简单地说就是野餐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.86,0:16:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然已经是晚上了…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.21,0:16:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那么…牵手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.83,0:16:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.01,0:16:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说  这是你的初次约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.42,0:16:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.71,0:16:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐那边吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.13,0:16:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了便当
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.82,0:16:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.10,0:16:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.45,0:16:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  让奈香流来喂你吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.20,0:16:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.10,0:16:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.14,0:16:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.73,0:17:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要被骗了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.20,0:17:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙其实有眼镜依存症
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.41,0:17:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管装得多可爱都是十足的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.23,0:17:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.82,0:17:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说  要商量什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.67,0:17:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实奈香流陷入了低谷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.64,0:17:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低谷？哪方面的？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.34,0:17:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,BL小说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.69,0:17:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次又想让我做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.13,0:17:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  变成这样是有原因的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.20,0:17:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点烦恼的事  无法集中写作
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.51,0:17:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…请不要笑我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.61,0:17:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.24,0:17:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…前辈对我的胸部有什么感想
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.78,0:17:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  那个呆滞的表情算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.11,0:17:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实  在此之前发生过一个事件
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.97,0:18:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事件？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.90,0:18:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被告白了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.52,0:18:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是告发吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.22,0:18:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是  对方是同班的男生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.42,0:18:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没怎么交谈过的一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.39,0:18:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却突然说了「我喜欢你  请和我交往」这样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.44,0:18:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  那之后你怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.52,0:18:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然拒绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.76,0:18:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为奈香流已经有所觉悟了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.36,0:18:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉悟？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.38,0:18:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流决定将高中生活全都投入BL的创作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.90,0:18:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成胸部的话题…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.56,0:18:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说我不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.66,0:18:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人为什么会对奈香流表白
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.26,0:18:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由自己来说有点奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.47,0:18:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但奈香流的性格并不受男孩子欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.50,0:18:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.72,0:18:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  我想了很多我单方面的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.47,0:18:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.44,0:19:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.91,0:19:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咋了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.92,0:19:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  请揉奈香流的胸部吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.94,0:19:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.04,0:19:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我听说过
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.46,0:19:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸部会越揉越小！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.50,0:19:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是从哪里听来那种错误的知识的！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.23,0:19:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  不是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.57,0:19:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  为什么我要揉你的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.36,0:19:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得自卑  有这样的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.68,0:19:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明再小一点就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.46,0:19:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要太在意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.36,0:19:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都会有自卑的事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.19,0:19:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都会有？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.72,0:19:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有怎么都治不好的烦恼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.65,0:19:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈也有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.54,0:19:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.03,0:19:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且男人大部分都喜欢巨乳
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.78,0:19:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然如此  光是胸部是无法让人陷入恋爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.99,0:19:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  就证明一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.54,0:19:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光凭胸部是无法让男人陷入恋爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.35,0:19:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用前辈的身体
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.14,0:20:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则…否则…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.00,0:20:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流就无法投入创作！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.79,0:20:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么歪理啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.58,0:20:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是相信着前辈才来找你商量的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.27,0:20:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈的话  一定能拯救奈香流的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.90,0:20:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我经受住的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.54,0:20:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就能克服自卑  解决烦恼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.75,0:20:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.40,0:20:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.85,0:20:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.26,0:20:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.31,0:20:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要输啊  我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.80,0:20:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要输啊  奈香流
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.40,0:20:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.18,0:20:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厉害什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.25,0:20:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被胸部这样压住还那么淡定
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.50,0:20:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈有天生的BL之才
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.51,0:20:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.40,0:21:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌  不要这样盯着看啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.09,0:21:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.39,0:21:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  眼镜眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.78,0:21:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是  这是…反差萌！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.02,0:21:24.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得舒畅多了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.16,0:21:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你了  前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.65,0:21:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说  太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.17,0:21:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  简单地说就像眼镜突然从脸上滑落的感觉一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.54,0:21:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是托前辈的福…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.71,0:21:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊嘞  啊嘞啊嘞
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.79,0:21:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  感觉前辈好像比平时…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.50,0:21:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来更帅了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.12,0:21:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.50,0:21:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.58,0:21:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  把这个收拾一下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.58,0:22:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.18,0:22:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.83,0:22:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  不要过来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.94,0:22:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.52,0:22:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈香流  这个  这个要怎么办啊


