[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-06-24 20:51:24
; // 版本: 0.74
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:STAR DRIVER 輝きのタクト
Original Script:shinjico@popgo
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.8,0.4,2,10,10,8,1
Style: note1,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,21,&H000FE3DE,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H001C1C1C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: note2,FZZhunYuan-M02,26,&H00213A3D,&H00FFFFFF,&H00C9E2E2,&H00F3F3F3,-1,0,0,0,90,100,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00242424,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,0,0,1,30,30,12,1
Style: staff,FZZhunYuan-M02,24,&H00EBEBEB,&H00000000,&H28000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,2,15,15,10,1
Style: OPCN1,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,25,&H00FAFAFA,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H28000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: EDCN1,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00A71ADD,&H1E941471,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,4,1
Style: OPCN2,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,24,&H00FAFAFA,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,4,1
Style: EDCN2,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00F02015,&H1E380118,-1,0,0,0,100,100,2,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,4,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.40,0:01:15.30,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an1\fad(1400,0)\fs36}（王）
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.17,0:24:02.28,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(600,600)\pos(424,12)\fsp-1\fs22}翻译：晶晶电脑   AKIRA
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.29,0:24:06.57,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(600,600)\pos(424,12)\fsp-1\fs22}后期：SHINJICO  X  SHINJICO
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.61,0:24:11.47,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(600,600)\pos(424,12)\fs22}漫游字幕组\N{\fsp-1\fnArial\fs18\b0}http://popgo.net/bbs
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------OPCN2-----------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.95,0:04:23.47,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}仰望天空 广阔梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.53,0:04:27.41,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}打开未来的门扉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.54,0:04:34.41,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}此刻依然无限光芒照耀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.21,0:04:44.72,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}明朗的天空
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.77,0:04:49.18,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}打开窗便有阳光洒下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.30,0:04:51.72,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}微风拂过
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.83,0:04:55.66,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\blur2}拭去昨日的泪水
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.72,0:04:59.15,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}寂寞之时
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.23,0:05:02.92,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}总是寻找着看不见的星星
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.00,0:05:06.30,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}不知它近在身旁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.35,0:05:11.55,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}依然不断追求
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.61,0:05:12.93,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}（you are the shining star）
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.95,0:05:16.44,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}仰望天空 广阔梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.50,0:05:20.38,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}打开未来的门扉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.48,0:05:27.01,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}此刻依然无限光芒照耀
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.09,0:05:30.52,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}星空闪烁的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.62,0:05:34.55,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}不计其数的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.63,0:05:40.88,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}如今依然等待着你去实现
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.92,0:05:45.59,OPCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\blur2}所以迈步前进吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------EDCN2-----------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.26,0:22:29.21,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}决心不会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.28,0:22:31.68,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}无论多少次
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.75,0:22:34.89,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,400)\be1}都能重新起跑
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.01,0:22:48.52,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}轻飘飘地随风飘扬
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.65,0:22:52.70,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}飒爽而来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.76,0:22:56.52,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}若只想消磨时间
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.53,0:23:00.42,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}就给我认真点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.50,0:23:03.32,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}黑白的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.38,0:23:08.12,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}你应该也早已厌倦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.25,0:23:11.98,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}被弄脏也不会放手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.07,0:23:18.48,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}紧拥着唯一的自尊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.57,0:23:20.42,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}梦想不会就此终结
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.44,0:23:22.12,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}你依然保持本色
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.22,0:23:26.31,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}随时都可以重生
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.40,0:23:30.93,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}摄人心魄的疯狂刺激
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.04,0:23:34.10,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}才能拯救爱 woo
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.14,0:23:36.24,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}决心不会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.33,0:23:37.86,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}谁也无法破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.91,0:23:42.23,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}给人添麻烦又如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.26,0:23:44.04,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}想要继续呐喊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.15,0:23:46.43,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}无论多少次
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.56,0:23:49.68,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)\be1}都能重新起跑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.92,0:23:54.55,EDCN2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be1}「想要的只是时代的一页」
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------PREV------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.60,0:00:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好困啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.69,0:00:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周日早上不如省了吧 这个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.49,0:00:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢上别人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.69,0:00:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟是什么感觉？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.49,0:00:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想抱在怀里 想占有对方
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.04,0:00:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终究脱不了这些吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.82,0:00:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是新式的精神攻击？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.93,0:00:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠语言攻势让对手露出破绽吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.76,0:00:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.54,0:00:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 上次打赌的事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.34,0:00:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无疾而终了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.64,0:00:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.08,0:00:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我与和子的婚约 就回归白纸
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.26,0:00:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调高一点奖金也无妨
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.21,0:00:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.48,0:01:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.19,0:01:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和子就归你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.58,0:01:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思啊 师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.20,0:01:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞬间睡意全无
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.67,0:01:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还未够班呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.08,0:01:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天实际上是我赢了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.54,0:01:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制胜一击时犹豫不决
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.11,0:01:29.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是切磋嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.27,0:01:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收起这份天真
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.37,0:01:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后会有什么情况没人知道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.71,0:01:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时刻能做出正确判断的应变能力
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.35,0:01:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.73,0:01:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 应该是自然天成的精神力
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.60,0:01:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有自信一直保护和子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.55,0:01:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.73,0:02:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.40,0:02:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 和子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.58,0:02:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.27,0:02:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果想一起入浴的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.58,0:02:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为您准备衣物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.03,0:02:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害来真的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.24,0:02:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓人 盐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.41,0:02:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打搅各位进餐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.10,0:02:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少爷 方才物件运到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.74,0:02:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,物件？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.08,0:02:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包装上标示为美术品
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.94,0:02:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是画
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.94,0:02:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.82,0:02:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.75,0:03:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我遇见的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.67,0:03:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.63,0:03:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓人的爸爸？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.19,0:03:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年龄看来与我们并无二致
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.91,0:03:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一阶？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.75,0:03:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 莫非是绮罗星？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.62,0:03:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有预料到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.44,0:03:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直找不到 原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.52,0:03:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这幅画
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.28,0:03:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形似 但神不似少爷
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.32,0:03:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到某种不好的欲望
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.46,0:03:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.98,0:03:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只感觉到支配欲
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.04,0:03:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.93,0:03:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么评论拓人父亲的画作
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.94,0:03:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.68,0:03:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正今后会是对手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.69,0:03:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管对方是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.27,0:03:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找和子的麻烦就打
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.32,0:03:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种程度不会动摇？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.90,0:03:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.16,0:04:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不被任何情况动摇的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.72,0:04:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的平常心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.37,0:04:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.87,0:04:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.50,0:04:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.71,0:04:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.65,0:04:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和须方两个人？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.19,0:04:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------TXTA------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.91,0:06:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.74,0:06:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.42,0:06:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.68,0:06:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试着跟和子的衣服搭配了下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.68,0:06:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.86,0:06:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎么了！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.95,0:06:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 拓人？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.26,0:06:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惦记学生宿舍了？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.87,0:06:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散步而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.20,0:06:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学长们总是亲密三人组呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.79,0:06:59.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.15,0:07:01.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不是三人组吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.54,0:07:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,须方和和子约会中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.32,0:07:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.60,0:07:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.82,0:07:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.72,0:07:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么性质？什么约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.07,0:07:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.48,0:07:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我还没放弃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.59,0:07:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宿舍长怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.02,0:07:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青春期的坐立不安吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.08,0:07:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.02,0:07:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宿舍修好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.02,0:07:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时可以回来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.69,0:07:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑考虑
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.44,0:07:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他叫回宿舍
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.68,0:07:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么作战计划？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.32,0:07:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.64,0:07:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.06,0:07:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的好像挺难熬的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.36,0:07:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说 执照被吊销
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.43,0:07:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要绮罗星到几时？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.52,0:08:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上周 拳击部的女孩向你表白了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.34,0:08:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也收了麻由美的情书吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.29,0:08:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家都开始读摩托杂志了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.39,0:08:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讴歌青春
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.28,0:08:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到头来启程的那天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.96,0:08:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成旁观者没关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.55,0:08:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要红绪不开口放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.38,0:08:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们就是「芯」
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.99,0:08:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在和过去 都是她的骑士
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.35,0:08:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看快看 那对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.02,0:08:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 就像一幅画
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.92,0:08:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近不知为何
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.44,0:08:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人独处反而不自在
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.52,0:08:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.89,0:08:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过有点吃惊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.34,0:09:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人出门散步是常有的事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.06,0:09:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一本正经说「我们约会吧」
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.16,0:09:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是第一次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.33,0:09:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到有一天 我们结婚的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.38,0:09:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓人会来玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.55,0:09:24.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者 和子和拓人结婚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.38,0:09:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会去玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.07,0:09:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前不久舞台上的吻
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.10,0:09:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.30,0:09:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是演戏啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.14,0:09:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 和子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.56,0:09:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.24,0:09:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.83,0:09:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.84,0:10:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 那边的帅哥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.19,0:10:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想问下路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.90,0:10:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.62,0:10:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.88,0:10:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有片海岸能看到火山
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.63,0:10:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.54,0:10:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别假惺惺的演戏
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.42,0:11:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以劝你别去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.81,0:11:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是只能除掉他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.28,0:11:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是因为被揍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.74,0:11:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他护着皆水巫女
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.67,0:11:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有强行除掉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.24,0:11:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要干
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.41,0:11:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复原Gimelock（驼）
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.51,0:11:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热血不像你的风格啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.13,0:11:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海德不值得信任
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.45,0:11:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该在他得到Shinpathy（牙）之前了结
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.73,0:11:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先掌握主导权
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.70,0:11:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.43,0:11:47.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剑之星？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.97,0:11:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算有真的印记
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.73,0:11:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有素体也无意义
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.36,0:11:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在要么干 要么放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.83,0:12:00.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.34,0:12:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被逼入绝境
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.88,0:12:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点男人的样子了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.38,0:12:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大闹一场吧
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------TXTB------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.24,0:12:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.30,0:12:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.50,0:12:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接吻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.20,0:12:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.96,0:12:30.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真羡慕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.97,0:12:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样两个人吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.56,0:12:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是约会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.35,0:12:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说也没错…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.48,0:12:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,须方说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.46,0:12:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白天和我约会过了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.16,0:12:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上去和拓人也约会次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.19,0:12:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.51,0:12:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在想什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.11,0:12:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓人今天怎么过的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.64,0:12:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见到了父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.49,0:13:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二话没说先揍了一拳
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.84,0:13:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,零时空间
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.32,0:13:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是它吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.38,0:13:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边也有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.07,0:13:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.81,0:13:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三台？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.46,0:13:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天真够热闹的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.66,0:13:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三对一吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.01,0:13:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.86,0:13:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驯化
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.92,0:14:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飒爽登场
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.22,0:14:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,银河美少年
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.03,0:14:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Tauburn
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.51,0:14:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改变战斗方式了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.43,0:14:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离终章不远的感觉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.53,0:14:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Gimelock的分离战法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.94,0:14:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,效果颇为不错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.81,0:14:49.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若非Qophlite（针孔）阻挠 原本似有胜算
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.79,0:14:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏时间结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.28,0:14:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你完了 Tauburn
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.10,0:15:00.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星剑 翡翠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.90,0:15:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星剑 蓝宝石
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.81,0:15:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背负素体复原的风险
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.88,0:15:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少那三人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.07,0:15:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比你更有勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.88,0:15:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好啊 年轻
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.43,0:15:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人羡慕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.47,0:15:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被围住就糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.97,0:15:43.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我方素体进入第三阶段
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.91,0:15:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也得到强化
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.94,0:15:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数量直接决定战斗力差距
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.29,0:15:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那台Tauburn
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.23,0:15:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是特殊素体
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.20,0:15:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有绝对性的能力差距
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.28,0:15:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑到这点的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.23,0:16:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它连胜至今才是奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.49,0:16:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豪快 银河
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.80,0:16:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十文字斩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.04,0:16:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 看你怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.95,0:16:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.56,0:17:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,津名志拓人从幼年时代起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.18,0:17:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就作为驭星者接受训练
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.73,0:17:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加上「保护弱小」的家训
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.84,0:17:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是今天应该
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.45,0:17:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,THE END了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.21,0:17:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛮厉害的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.84,0:17:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的「放逐时代」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.79,0:17:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.31,0:17:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配合越来越娴熟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.67,0:17:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,it's a pinch吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.01,0:17:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.25,0:17:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.06,0:18:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 拓人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.96,0:18:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我上Tauburn
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.95,0:18:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,须方？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.58,0:18:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,须方？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.57,0:18:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.22,0:18:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用我发射Tau飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.96,0:18:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.17,0:18:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.85,0:18:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上了 须方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.80,0:18:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不规则
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.68,0:18:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Tau飞弹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.07,0:19:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.79,0:19:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厉害啊 须方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.72,0:19:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 我就是逆日死之巫女
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.73,0:19:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.71,0:19:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绮罗星十字团第三队
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.44,0:19:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九重葛的「沉醉」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.28,0:20:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好险
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.41,0:20:17.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敌人也开始急了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.00,0:20:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.15,0:20:21.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包菜卷 蛋包饭 蛤杂烩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.98,0:20:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加恋人色拉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.21,0:20:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和子不怕吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.47,0:20:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.79,0:20:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拓人和须方到齐就无敌
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.54,0:20:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先不说我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.41,0:20:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,须方确实了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.04,0:20:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.50,0:20:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王之柱的能量容量
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.32,0:20:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今无法完全算出
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.85,0:21:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个怪物真复活了 该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.80,0:21:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.73,0:21:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚集会的目的是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.25,0:21:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.69,0:21:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说沉醉不在
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.57,0:21:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由出席的话 我可以回去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.37,0:21:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是闲着没事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.58,0:21:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在 绮罗星十字团
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.91,0:21:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总会开始
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.74,0:21:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今夜
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.32,0:21:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们迎接新的成员
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.43,0:21:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绮罗星十字团
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.00,0:21:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一队
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.66,0:21:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国王代表
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.28,0:21:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.70,0:22:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王之柱的驭星者
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.63,0:22:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进藤须方为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.69,0:22:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,须方…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.06,0:22:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,须方来了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.65,0:22:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绮罗星
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.25,0:22:26.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绮罗星！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------NEXT------------------------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.81,0:24:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上没在读书？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.69,0:24:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且少有的好心情
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.25,0:24:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么好事了？班长
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.72,0:24:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.40,0:24:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 驭星者
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.94,0:24:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆日死之巫女
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.46,0:24:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绮罗星
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//---------------------------------TVCM------------------------------------


