[Script Info]
Title:清雨
Original Script:清雨
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.8,0.4,2,10,10,8,134
Style: staff,黑体,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00860BF4,&H64860BF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,128
Style: OPCH,华康圆体W5(P),24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0000,&H64FF0000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正大黑简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: a,方正准圆_GBK,31,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF640064,0,0,0,0,100,105,1,0.00,1,0,1,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.40,0:00:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎 和我交往吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.38,0:00:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.56,0:00:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说当我的恋人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.87,0:00:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 这到底是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.20,0:00:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电视剧里经常出现的那种咯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.31,0:00:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人公通过爱的力量消除自卑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.55,0:00:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.65,0:00:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.58,0:00:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱将救赎猪太郎的作战
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.39,0:00:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这啥呀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.16,0:00:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不愿意到想吐 不过这也是神的工作嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.45,0:00:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是只限定为你的超M治好前这段时间哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.80,0:00:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我的意见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.18,0:00:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说 现在你跟我就是恋人了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.25,0:00:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这种方法能顺利治好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.14,0:00:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么开始第一次约会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.40,0:00:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具体的内容就交给我们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.86,0:02:32.91,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由极影字幕社(bbs.ktxp.com)制作 仅供交流试看 喜爱本作品请支持Z版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.86,0:02:32.91,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译: 神代辰弥  雲端の翼   特效: W-BOY   后期: 清雨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.49,0:02:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.28,0:02:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.12,0:02:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这回的使命了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.59,0:02:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.82,0:02:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大致的目的地已经跟美绪说过了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.66,0:02:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来的我会对准备好的节目下指示 放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.30,0:02:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.16,0:02:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就祝你好运了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.24,0:03:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 真的没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.22,0:03:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.75,0:03:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.86,0:03:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.57,0:03:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三十分钟左右…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.89,0:03:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢款待 太棒了 被踢的滋味
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.27,0:03:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里应该说 我也才刚到 你这蠢猪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.48,0:03:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.51,0:03:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 算了 那么开始咯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.58,0:03:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 更多的惩罚吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.19,0:03:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是约会咯 那么先去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.49,0:03:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满老师说已经跟你说了去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.55,0:03:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好像有那么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.76,0:03:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.12,0:03:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真啰嗦 我熬夜定了计划的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.25,0:03:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真累 来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.40,0:04:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.28,0:04:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 因为是约会 所以牵手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.83,0:04:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满姐说了约会时就像对恋人那样尽量牵起手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.11,0:04:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.94,0:04:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么呢 渣子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.39,0:04:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐的手这么软啊 这么的温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.42,0:04:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一阶段成功
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.31,0:04:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来很好吃呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.66,0:04:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 这是我亲手做的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.57,0:04:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐亲手做的？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.41,0:04:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 虽然是让满姐教我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.46,0:04:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢款待
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.68,0:04:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 你手指的伤是？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.00,0:04:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这个？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.27,0:05:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了我 竟然做到这种份上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.01,0:05:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么伤哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.73,0:05:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.91,0:05:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满姐叫我这么试试看 没想到真上钩了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.12,0:05:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说是单细胞呢 还是别的什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.36,0:05:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失望了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.79,0:05:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是切的还不错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.77,0:05:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.77,0:05:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是勉勉强强吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.38,0:05:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么被食物钓去了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.09,0:05:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…要去哪里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.07,0:05:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.95,0:05:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然不知道？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.49,0:05:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像这样闲逛公园就是约会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.78,0:05:46.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.13,0:05:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.93,0:05:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.96,0:05:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会应该做些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.32,0:05:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要来问我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.57,0:05:58.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你在和间宫同学交往啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.53,0:06:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 中学毕业后由美搬家后就自然而然分手了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.40,0:06:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.58,0:06:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是从前的事了 自己是不是现在还喜欢由美
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.79,0:06:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.93,0:06:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.74,0:06:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会的话做让对方高兴的事不就好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.83,0:06:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果知道这个的话就不用烦恼了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.83,0:06:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.26,0:06:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.46,0:06:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰激凌吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.61,0:06:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我冰激凌
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.75,0:06:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.80,0:06:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.58,0:06:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.41,0:06:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有要说的话就快说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.31,0:06:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.31,0:06:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么呢 不擦掉美绪脸上的冰激凌吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.78,0:06:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 这种事做不到的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.10,0:06:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.65,0:06:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.09,0:07:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 你的脸上沾着冰激凌
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.23,0:07:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的话 我自己也能擦掉嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.24,0:07:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐果然很可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.02,0:07:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.82,0:07:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 美绪的好感度上升了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.90,0:07:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.39,0:07:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像现在这样中途出现选项
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.49,0:07:30.42,a,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(204,220)}给美绪学姐擦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.49,0:07:29.95,a,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(204,345)}装作没看到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.74,0:07:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据你的选项 美绪的好感度就会发生变化
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.34,0:07:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好感度降的太低的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.67,0:07:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会就失败了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.70,0:07:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OMG
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.15,0:07:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就要在众人面前吃美绪一腿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.45,0:07:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的超M不就被围观了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.55,0:07:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便一提 会出现什么样的指示 美绪也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.97,0:07:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.54,0:08:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊嘞 脸有点红
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.95,0:08:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 学姐也在紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.46,0:08:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看到底谁才配约会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.78,0:08:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用爱的力量和我对决吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.77,0:08:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贫乳庶民
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.70,0:08:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是贫乳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.23,0:08:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 没事吧 辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.77,0:08:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.76,0:08:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.16,0:08:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.72,0:09:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在 在…在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.96,0:09:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.47,0:09:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是这种关系？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.66,0:09:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想 想要kiss？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.37,0:09:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不是那么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.75,0:09:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在惊讶些什么呢 相爱之人的话这是理所当然的了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.27,0:09:16.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么理所当然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.16,0:09:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连kiss的觉悟都没有 还想治好他的超M体质？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.54,0:09:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能kiss吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.97,0:09:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.03,0:09:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就是我赢了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.28,0:09:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.26,0:09:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一味生气的话贫乳就会变的更小哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.46,0:09:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这人妖变态
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.77,0:09:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会这才开始呢 拜托你了 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.79,0:10:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.93,0:10:05.22,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}发信人：满老师\N标题：在观览车里\N砂户太郎给美绪做膝枕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.35,0:10:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说给学姐做膝枕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.75,0:10:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愿意的话就不要做了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.99,0:10:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.60,0:10:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要动 这里很窄的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.16,0:10:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.27,0:10:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.19,0:10:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.28,0:10:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才真是得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.76,0:10:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是变态不是正合适吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.16,0:10:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.80,0:10:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然初吻不是喜欢的女孩的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.11,0:10:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是变态还真是少女情怀呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.78,0:10:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和变态没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.22,0:10:47.50,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}发信人：满老师\N标题：就按照这样的体势\N说说喜欢对方哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.37,0:10:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…叫我们说说喜欢对方哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.04,0:10:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有这种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.50,0:10:54.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.11,0:10:58.87,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}发信人：满老师\N标题：今天\N两人是恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.22,0:10:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.20,0:11:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说我们两人是恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.69,0:11:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从哪里看起来像啊 满姐也真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.91,0:11:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.90,0:11:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从你开始说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.58,0:11:15.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢你长得很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.28,0:11:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来轮到学姐了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.07,0:11:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.50,0:11:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M的变态的让人恶心的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.89,0:11:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒不如说这是讨厌的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.05,0:11:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右手灵巧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.65,0:11:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家不都是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.49,0:11:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 上厕所到指定的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.32,0:11:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当我是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.78,0:11:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.88,0:11:43.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说找不到？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.59,0:11:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能下次再说？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.29,0:11:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 叹什么气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.06,0:11:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.49,0:12:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和太郎约会的应该是我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.38,0:12:07.24,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}（满指令 选择真正的爱！）
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.42,0:12:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到连岚子都会出场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.21,0:12:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不会把这个家伙让给你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.85,0:12:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪难道对太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.06,0:12:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一决胜负吧 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.12,0:12:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正合我意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.51,0:12:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿咻 嘿咻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.52,0:12:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.09,0:12:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以输
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.35,0:12:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不放手
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.08,0:12:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快放开
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.00,0:12:29.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.31,0:12:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手麻痹没感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.12,0:12:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.42,0:12:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以输
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.79,0:12:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没事…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.19,0:12:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.78,0:12:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.07,0:13:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个约会要持续到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.39,0:13:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这附近吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.78,0:13:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.55,0:13:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我得了不治之症
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.14,0:13:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 因为我想和太郎约会
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.37,0:13:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偷偷地从医院里跑了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.56,0:13:25.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这是番茄汁吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.53,0:13:31.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}请和我结婚 1\N回到医院里吧 2
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.04,0:00:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.55,0:13:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 请和我结婚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.29,0:13:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.79,0:13:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我真的可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.40,0:13:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非学姐不可
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.43,0:13:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.06,0:14:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于到了最终事件了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.12,0:14:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.01,0:14:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是你们的结婚典礼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.49,0:14:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人宣誓永恒的爱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.80,0:14:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相互拥抱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.44,0:14:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做的太过了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.17,0:14:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来用爱来治愈我的超M体质什么的原本就…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.75,0:14:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛　可能是不行的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.65,0:14:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么为什么还要这么做？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.88,0:14:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的约会不是为了你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.65,0:14:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上是为了美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.72,0:14:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.20,0:14:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.43,0:14:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.75,0:14:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.85,0:14:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里很奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.75,0:14:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不　没有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.22,0:14:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.56,0:15:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是有效果的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.93,0:15:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.20,0:15:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不习惯穿这个　感觉很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.23,0:15:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐　你是不是已经喜欢上我了？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.38,0:15:11.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.08,0:15:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和那个是两码事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.13,0:15:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用不着隐藏
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.19,0:15:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是约会的意义
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.24,0:15:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了　最后的最后了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.48,0:15:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来你就会完全拜倒在我的石榴裙下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.81,0:15:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M体质什么的马上就能治好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.26,0:15:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐　不管怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.36,0:15:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥抱什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.09,0:15:37.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个还是算了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.12,0:15:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的是呢　那种行为…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.06,0:15:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相爱的人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.55,0:15:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,kiss更加自然吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.22,0:15:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？不会是认真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.26,0:15:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是啰嗦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.07,0:15:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点把眼睛闭上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.68,0:15:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是　是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.17,0:15:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再怎么说学姐也…是开玩笑的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.14,0:15:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概也不会以那么一副可怕的脸色去kiss吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.52,0:16:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.28,0:16:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.14,0:16:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.09,0:16:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要和我这样的人kiss？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.77,0:16:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是当然的吗？为了治愈你的M体质
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.21,0:16:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然就为了这件事？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.93,0:16:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女装变态不是也说了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.28,0:16:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相爱的人的话kiss这点程度没什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.71,0:16:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,kiss这点程度？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.99,0:16:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是神啊 一定要实现你的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.06,0:16:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐你已经习惯了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.15,0:16:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐认为kiss无论和谁都可以 像打招呼一般的东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.00,0:16:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.67,0:16:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是第一次啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.99,0:16:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.58,0:16:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你开什么玩笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.41,0:17:00.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你生气什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.79,0:17:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要和一点也不喜欢的人kiss啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.07,0:17:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是为了你…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.83,0:17:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.64,0:17:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等一下 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.23,0:17:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.82,0:17:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是事件吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.83,0:17:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.56,0:17:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正又是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.04,0:17:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会被你骗的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.50,0:17:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.39,0:17:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是发了高烧了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.39,0:17:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴露了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.48,0:17:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从什么时候开始的？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.00,0:17:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底做了些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.83,0:17:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要逞强乱来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.74,0:17:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 想要实现 你的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.15,0:17:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐是个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.51,0:17:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.51,0:18:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上…就要到医院了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.17,0:18:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐居然为了我…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.42,0:18:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哭吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.17,0:18:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 原来是雨
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.67,0:18:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擅自就和你kiss了 真对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.39,0:18:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也难怪你如此生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.94,0:18:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我这样的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.89,0:18:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.97,0:18:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的学姐让人好不舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.94,0:18:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么吗 难得我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.91,0:19:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的巴掌打我也不会舒服的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.05,0:19:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请还像以前一样打我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.95,0:19:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个变态
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.30,0:19:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然你还是对我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.00,0:19:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.58,0:19:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.06,0:19:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…欢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.21,0:19:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.45,0:19:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了别人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.52,0:19:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了别人去拼命
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.45,0:19:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.27,0:19:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的一点都不像你的作风啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.00,0:19:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为保健医生真是失格
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.38,0:20:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有这种时候擅长装作若无其事的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.69,0:20:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.90,0:20:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您说过今天的约会是为了学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.13,0:20:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.37,0:20:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还是孩子的时候基本上没有和同龄人一起玩过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.07,0:20:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不擅长和他人交往
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.49,0:20:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就算只是一点点也好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.04,0:20:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将这个问题克服
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.35,0:20:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.84,0:20:24.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天已经很累了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.26,0:20:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.78,0:20:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我要呆在学姐的身边
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.45,0:20:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.51,0:20:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 担心死我了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.90,0:20:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐我会照顾你的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.44,0:20:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.00,0:20:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出汗了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.51,0:20:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐来帮你擦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.37,0:20:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静香 别来捣乱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.01,0:20:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈你才是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.29,0:20:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 照顾病人是母亲的职责
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.55,0:20:58.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以决定不能让给你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.81,0:21:01.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 姐姐来照顾你~
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.67,0:21:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了 给我滚出去！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.20,0:21:05.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎~
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.75,0:21:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.00,0:21:11.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.32,0:21:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没问题了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.65,0:21:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息三天了当然没有问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.62,0:21:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.40,0:21:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.99,0:21:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.75,0:21:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把眼睛闭上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.54,0:21:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.11,0:21:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是命令 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.03,0:21:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.85,0:21:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是完全没有治好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.41,0:21:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然爱的力量还是有达不到的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.86,0:21:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 爱的力量又是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.01,0:21:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在才说话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.70,0:21:57.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为那是真的kiss吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.07,0:22:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 真是没救了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.78,0:22:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个猪头
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.04,0:00:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.12,0:23:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.50,0:23:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.88,0:23:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭吗 还是先洗澡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.81,0:23:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.83,0:23:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.92,0:23:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人相互凝视
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.08,0:23:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双手相抚
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.19,0:23:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕啊
Dialogue: 2,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 1,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,452,848,453)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,453,848,454)}{\1c&HFAF7FD&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,454,848,455)}{\1c&HF6F0FC&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,455,848,456)}{\1c&HF2E9FB&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,456,848,457)}{\1c&HEEE1FA&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,457,848,458)}{\1c&HEADAF9&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,458,848,459)}{\1c&HE6D3F8&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,459,848,460)}{\1c&HE2CBF7&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,460,848,461)}{\1c&HDEC4F6&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,461,848,462)}{\1c&HD9BDF5&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,462,848,463)}{\1c&HD5B6F4&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,463,848,464)}{\1c&HD1AEF3&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,464,848,465)}{\1c&HCDA7F2&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,465,848,466)}{\1c&HC9A0F1&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,466,848,467)}{\1c&HC598F0&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,467,848,468)}{\1c&HC191EF&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,468,848,469)}{\1c&HBD8AEE&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:02:35.56,0:02:37.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,469,848,470)}{\1c&HB983ED&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 2,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,26,848,27)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,27,848,28)}{\1c&HFBF8FE&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,28,848,29)}{\1c&HF7F1FD&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,29,848,30)}{\1c&HF3EBFC&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,30,848,31)}{\1c&HF0E4FB&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,31,848,32)}{\1c&HECDEFA&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,32,848,33)}{\1c&HE8D7F9&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,33,848,34)}{\1c&HE5D1F8&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,34,848,35)}{\1c&HE1CAF7&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,35,848,36)}{\1c&HDDC4F6&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,36,848,37)}{\1c&HDABDF5&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,37,848,38)}{\1c&HD6B7F4&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,38,848,39)}{\1c&HD2B0F3&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,39,848,40)}{\1c&HCFAAF2&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,40,848,41)}{\1c&HCBA3F1&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,41,848,42)}{\1c&HC79DF0&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,42,848,43)}{\1c&HC496EF&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,43,848,44)}{\1c&HC090EE&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,44,848,45)}{\1c&HBC89ED&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,45,848,46)}{\1c&HB983ED&}天才少女的暴走危机！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.97,0:00:54.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.53,0:00:58.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.15,0:01:03.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.55,0:01:09.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこの迷えるオマエ 惰性感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.13,0:01:15.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すがるワラを探して　他力本願バンザイ？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.50,0:01:19.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここに来ただけ（相当）お利口ねボウヤ（上等）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.99,0:01:25.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞いてあげるわ　早くゲロっていっそGo to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.21,0:01:28.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.85,0:01:30.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神の仕事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.83,0:01:33.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.18,0:01:37.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試行錯誤のevery day　いくら足騒いたトコで無駄
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.87,0:01:42.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神に従ってれば　万事OKでしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.62,0:01:44.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身の程わきまえて、さあ（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.91,0:01:47.18,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆らうヤツらはお仕置きよ（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.19,0:01:51.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果主義更生させなくちゃGo to Hell→Deaaaath!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.98,0:02:00.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絶対的で革新的な　チカラ見せつけてあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.49,0:02:04.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと存在感異常のイカレタ趣味くらいノープロブレム
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.11,0:02:09.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこにひざまずいて教えを請いなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.07,0:02:14.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生観変えるような出会いになるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.25,0:02:19.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなビビってないで　全部あずけりゃいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.34,0:02:21.85,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.97,0:00:54.43,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.53,0:00:58.99,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.15,0:01:03.67,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.55,0:01:09.94,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里迷惘着的你　惰性感满载的face
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.13,0:01:15.31,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找着救命稻草 坐享其成万岁？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.50,0:01:19.96,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够到达这里（相当）真聪明啊男孩（很好）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.99,0:01:25.98,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就听你说说 快点全说出来干脆Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.21,0:01:28.66,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.85,0:01:30.82,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.83,0:01:33.15,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.18,0:01:37.68,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不断摸索的every day 不管怎么挣扎都是没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.87,0:01:42.46,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺从神明的话 就万事OK了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.62,0:01:44.90,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看清自己的斤两（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.91,0:01:47.18,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反抗的家伙都要调教哦（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.19,0:01:51.89,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须让结果注意复兴Go to Hell→Deaaaath!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.98,0:02:00.31,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你见识见识绝对的革新的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.49,0:02:04.95,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着稍微存在感异常的奇怪兴趣而已No problem
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.11,0:02:09.91,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪在那里请求我的教导吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.07,0:02:14.06,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为会成为改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.25,0:02:19.17,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那么害怕 全部交给我就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.34,0:02:21.85,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要H!E!L!P!你！

Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.54,0:22:07.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.79,0:22:10.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.95,0:22:13.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.57,0:22:15.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.71,0:22:20.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.07,0:22:21.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.39,0:22:22.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.84,0:22:23.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.14,0:22:26.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.79,0:22:29.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.41,0:22:31.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.60,0:22:31.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.00,0:22:33.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.42,0:22:34.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.68,0:22:35.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.07,0:22:37.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.32,0:22:38.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋には緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.68,0:22:39.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.06,0:22:42.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.22,0:22:44.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.73,0:22:48.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.69,0:22:54.44,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.24,0:22:59.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.34,0:23:01.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.91,0:23:04.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.81,0:23:06.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.17,0:23:09.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ 胸、痛い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.88,0:23:15.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちがとまらない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.54,0:23:17.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.73,0:23:20.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.80,0:23:23.35,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.51,0:23:25.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.61,0:23:29.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.97,0:23:32.70,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.54,0:22:07.62,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.79,0:22:10.76,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成就算是硬来？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.95,0:22:13.41,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气吐气之后是告白的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.57,0:22:15.53,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法安下心来的我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.71,0:22:20.07,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是特别的这是特别的…万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.07,0:22:21.33,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.39,0:22:22.67,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想靠的太近…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.84,0:22:23.95,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者是…可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.14,0:22:26.60,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近又远离 背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.79,0:22:29.21,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和欢笑可能是很相似的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.41,0:22:31.46,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想接近你喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.60,0:22:31.94,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.00,0:22:33.23,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我哪边都不擅长
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.42,0:22:34.52,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单行道是单方面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.68,0:22:35.88,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商谈枪弹 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.07,0:22:37.13,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.32,0:22:38.51,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是爱还是恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.68,0:22:39.87,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情文物让她们对立吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.06,0:22:42.01,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.22,0:22:44.51,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想看到梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.73,0:22:48.47,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.69,0:22:54.44,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我眼中你闪耀着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.24,0:22:59.33,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？对了…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.34,0:23:01.73,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要好好决定好哦 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.91,0:23:04.59,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席位只有一个所以就算硬来！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.81,0:23:06.97,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.17,0:23:09.68,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成 胸口 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.88,0:23:15.32,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之感情停不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.54,0:23:17.55,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好决定啊 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.73,0:23:20.65,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也想要挑战一下 想要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.80,0:23:23.35,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这次是承诺的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.51,0:23:25.42,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让你让我安心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.61,0:23:29.96,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为特别你是特别的…按下去！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.97,0:23:32.70,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!


