[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-04-03 10:53:30
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:MM!07
Original Script:澄空×华盟
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,5,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,5,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H50000000,&H50FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,1,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.05,0:03:10.97,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻译: 艾哀  天地有正气　校对: TurtleIzzy　打杂: HySauce、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.05,0:03:10.97,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.72,0:03:10.97,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}盛夏的三角恋爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.72,0:03:10.97,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}盛夏的三角恋爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.72,0:03:10.97,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}盛夏的三角恋爱？
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.29,0:01:37.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.91,0:01:42.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.38,0:01:47.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.71,0:01:53.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこの迷えるオマエ　悲壮感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.38,0:01:58.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーがないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.72,0:02:03.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.20,0:02:08.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.45,0:02:11.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.03,0:02:14.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.18,0:02:16.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.38,0:02:21.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.14,0:02:25.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.84,0:02:28.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.18,0:02:30.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.42,0:02:35.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to へブン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.20,0:02:39.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.89,0:02:43.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.83,0:02:48.21,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.27,0:02:53.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.18,0:02:57.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.44,0:03:02.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.61,0:03:05.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.29,0:01:37.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.91,0:01:42.25,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.38,0:01:47.14,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.71,0:01:53.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那边的迷途小羔羊　满是悲壮感的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.38,0:01:58.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}连救命稻草都不要了　这也是无可奈何的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.72,0:02:03.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为今天的命运也在（横冲直撞）刁难人（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.20,0:02:08.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少我想　成为你的伙伴帮你一把
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.45,0:02:11.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.03,0:02:14.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}交给我试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.18,0:02:16.34,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.38,0:02:21.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}极限的界线太温和　全部毁灭归零会怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.14,0:02:25.78,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}顽固的DNA　勉强是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.84,0:02:28.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}在强制结束5秒之前（迫在眉睫）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.18,0:02:30.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}是不是有脱胎换骨的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.42,0:02:35.17,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}改改你的现场主义就能Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.20,0:02:39.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不论有无　就让我用尽手段
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.89,0:02:43.77,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}现在就让你走上正途
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.83,0:02:48.21,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}有点超出存在感让人在意的恋人未满
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.27,0:02:53.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}一脸可怜的样子让人无法置之不理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.18,0:02:57.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为这已是改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.44,0:03:02.58,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}之后只要任凭摆布　随波逐流就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.61,0:03:05.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}HE! L! P!开始吧!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.79,0:21:58.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.86,0:22:01.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.04,0:22:04.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.77,0:22:07.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.44,0:22:12.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.58,0:22:13.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.97,0:22:17.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？ よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.98,0:22:22.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.82,0:22:23.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.27,0:22:24.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.56,0:22:25.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.87,0:22:28.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.50,0:22:29.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋は緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.87,0:22:33.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.41,0:22:35.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.89,0:22:39.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われてもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.77,0:22:46.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.62,0:22:50.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？ そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.58,0:22:53.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.04,0:22:56.19,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.22,0:22:58.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.34,0:23:00.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ　胸、痛い。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:06.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちが止まらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.69,0:23:08.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.88,0:23:11.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ　したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.93,0:23:14.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.62,0:23:17.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.34,0:23:24.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.79,0:21:58.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.86,0:22:01.97,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少为达成目的也要不择手段？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.04,0:22:04.71,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气呼气这是告白的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.77,0:22:07.42,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一直无法安心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.44,0:22:12.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个一定是特别的…万岁！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.58,0:22:13.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近一点…会讨厌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.97,0:22:17.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说…可以？ 一进一退背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.98,0:22:22.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和笑容说不定很像 靠近围观我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.82,0:22:23.22,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.27,0:22:24.56,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我都不擅长应付
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.56,0:22:25.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单方片面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.87,0:22:28.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商量和子弹 da-dan-da down load 对啦！对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.50,0:22:29.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.87,0:22:33.23,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情的文武双全 insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.41,0:22:35.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.89,0:22:39.68,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.77,0:22:46.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的眼中你是如此耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.62,0:22:50.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？ 对啦…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.58,0:22:53.02,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.04,0:22:56.19,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个位子所以要不择手段！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.22,0:22:58.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.34,0:23:00.95,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达到目的 胸口好疼。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:06.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之我的心意已经无法阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.69,0:23:08.82,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.88,0:23:11.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少想挑战一下 挑战一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.93,0:23:14.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这是同意的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.62,0:23:17.30,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应想要安心的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.34,0:23:24.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为是特别的你 就让我特别地…推倒你！  yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.60,0:00:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.68,0:00:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.29,0:00:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.14,0:00:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.90,0:00:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美少女最闪耀的季节
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.69,0:00:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（禁止游泳  有鲨鱼出没）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.18,0:00:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美  美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.46,0:00:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我快断气了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.17,0:00:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢  你的治疗不才刚开始吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.23,0:00:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了治愈你的超M体质
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.56,0:01:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须让你的身体记住痛苦直接关系到危机
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.75,0:01:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  人的力量是有限的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.13,0:01:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说  我一直对你太宽容了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.79,0:01:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什  什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.46,0:01:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.00,0:01:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那群嗜血的鲨鱼是一定会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  来什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.91,0:01:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二义工社  夏季特别强化合宿！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.72,0:01:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目标  治愈猪太郎的超M体质
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.13,0:01:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要成功！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.02,0:03:21.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎  没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.04,0:03:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里…不行…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.66,0:03:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你说不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.27,0:03:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.57,0:03:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快住手…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.10,0:03:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是可爱啊  岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.63,0:03:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.64,0:03:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  间宫由美
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.06,0:03:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来也拜托你给美绪按摩一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.78,0:03:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲨鱼居然没出现！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.38,0:03:51.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚烫的沙子和美绪大人的脚底
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.88,0:03:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个告示板不是骗人的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.46,0:03:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得为了你连小船都借来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.31,0:03:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没用的鲨鱼！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.89,0:04:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.05,0:04:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个变态在搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.88,0:04:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,M得让人脊背发凉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.35,0:04:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来  再来踩我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.90,0:04:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治疗才刚刚开始哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.34,0:04:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.18,0:04:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就由他们来治疗猪太郎的超M体质
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.95,0:04:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.32,0:04:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…这是这么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.72,0:04:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的超M体质在被女性虐待时才有反应
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.88,0:04:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是把施虐者换成螃蟹呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.94,0:04:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.55,0:04:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  螃蟹没法让你的超M体质反应吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.58,0:04:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就靠它们让你习惯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.90,0:04:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是觉得这个计划很完美呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.04,0:04:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.26,0:04:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说这个也不是很痛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.87,0:04:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的小螃蟹没效果吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.78,0:04:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要增加数量
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.52,0:04:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼痛的形式也因身体部位而异
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.30,0:04:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你们也来帮忙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.30,0:04:55.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.37,0:04:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要直接碰猪太郎  没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.10,0:04:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.10,0:05:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人恶心的社团活动啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.54,0:05:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是算了  帮你们一次
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.27,0:05:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说会痛的地方  这里和那里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.74,0:05:15.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.63,0:05:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.99,0:05:20.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像很糟糕…而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.95,0:05:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  这可是螃蟹夹的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.82,0:05:26.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我没关系  是螃蟹哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.24,0:05:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是螃蟹  你这个变态
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.71,0:05:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这明明是美少女在夹我嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.58,0:05:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燃起来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.02,0:05:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再给我些螃蟹  给我螃蟹  螃蟹…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.96,0:05:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啊  失败了么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.58,0:05:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那进行下一个计划
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.21,0:05:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我也来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.43,0:06:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二义工社流  砸西瓜大赛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.71,0:06:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧  西瓜就在那边
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.53,0:06:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我砸烂他
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.80,0:06:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.18,0:06:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M是人类特有的癖好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.22,0:06:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要不再是人类就能解放了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.28,0:06:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  变成西瓜结束你那短暂的一生吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.71,0:06:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是砂户  是西瓜  不是男生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.36,0:06:36.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊！男生好可怕好可怕…好可怕哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.62,0:06:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是悲哀的西瓜  请继续砸我  砸烂我…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.35,0:06:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个计划也失败了么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.85,0:06:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然被小满老师叫来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.58,0:06:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但居然是第二义工社的合宿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.30,0:06:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.92,0:06:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.04,0:06:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…还有由美在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.73,0:06:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炒面很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.75,0:06:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.95,0:07:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次想让你教教我怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.02,0:07:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是普通的炒面而已啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.26,0:07:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  但是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.20,0:07:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是第一次吃到那么美味的炒面
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.73,0:07:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干  干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.42,0:07:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  果然还是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.35,0:07:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.70,0:07:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…快看那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.61,0:07:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.16,0:07:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.80,0:07:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野你说想坐小船
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.01,0:07:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉两个人就坐上来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.37,0:07:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.35,0:07:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.30,0:07:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  因为我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.43,0:07:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系…因为我…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.97,0:08:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.58,0:08:05.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离岚子远点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.53,0:08:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M的大变态
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.70,0:08:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁早给我沉入海底  不要再出现在我面前了垃圾虫
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.61,0:08:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.95,0:08:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说今晚在神社有夏祭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.60,0:08:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好像是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.99,0:08:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.70,0:08:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想吃棉花糖
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.76,0:08:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棉花糖吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.55,0:08:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小时候以来就没吃过了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.53,0:08:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.37,0:08:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  今天就和我一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.76,0:08:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.00,0:08:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊！男生好可怕好可怕…好可怕哦！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.25,0:08:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是做这事的时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.72,0:08:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.16,0:08:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在才来吗  笨蛋鲨鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.30,0:08:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子要是有什么万一  我就把你切成三片
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.02,0:09:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是  鲨鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.78,0:09:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.67,0:09:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.07,0:09:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.98,0:09:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐！？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.84,0:09:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要把我们带到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.51,0:09:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学…  还记得我们…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.60,0:09:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.88,0:09:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的约定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.88,0:10:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说要和诺亚好好玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.89,0:10:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐  可以的话就让我来陪你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.63,0:10:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐想要做的事  全都一起来做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.05,0:10:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来和我一起「普通」地玩耍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.87,0:10:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以今天要和砂户同学玩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.44,0:10:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  所以才特地这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.26,0:10:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  太郎还在社团的夏季合宿中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.13,0:10:34.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该是  叫做「结野岚子」的家伙吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.55,0:10:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  是和太郎来自同一个初中的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.72,0:10:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同一个班级  同一个社团的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.28,0:10:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有过在太郎家和他家人一起吃过饭的经历
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.83,0:10:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有过进太郎房间的经历
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.32,0:10:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有过和太郎两人一起去动物园的经历的结野岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.69,0:10:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  有点让人恼火
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.35,0:10:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然半路杀出这么个家伙  诺亚  太失策了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.17,0:11:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要管她了  一起回去吧  太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.69,0:11:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学要和诺亚一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.79,0:11:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  太郎要和我一起回去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.58,0:11:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要和诺亚一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.26,0:11:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起玩吧  比起两个人  三个人一起更有趣啦  肯定的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.84,0:11:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  要玩什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.53,0:11:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提议  玩扮家家酒
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.24,0:11:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扮家家酒？  在这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.49,0:11:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.61,0:11:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我按
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.54,0:11:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.37,0:11:42.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是诺亚特制的家家酒之屋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.61,0:11:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.29,0:11:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学是爸爸  诺亚是妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.49,0:11:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来扮女儿的角色
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.31,0:11:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有异议
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.78,0:11:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐没有妈妈的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.43,0:11:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以由我来扮演妻子的角色比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.94,0:12:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学的妻子由诺亚来扮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.96,0:12:03.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话就有失真实感
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.21,0:12:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐还是小孩子角色最适合了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.47,0:12:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小孩子…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.95,0:12:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  刚才说「小孩子」了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.65,0:12:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦好啦  这里就公平起见来猜拳决定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.09,0:12:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  赢了的就扮妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.12,0:12:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头剪刀  布
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.12,0:12:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.88,0:12:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  已经是早上了哦  快起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.99,0:12:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  说「亲爱的」了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.99,0:12:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  结野
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.77,0:12:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  哪有叫自己妻子「结野」的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.10,0:12:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.58,0:12:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以啊  呐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.23,0:12:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫…叫我岚子吧  亲  爱  的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.58,0:13:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  早上好  岚子…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.22,0:13:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎  我亲爱的darling  我想死你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.43,0:13:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.66,0:13:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人  初次见面  我是太郎的外遇对象诺亚
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.20,0:13:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  柊学姐是女儿角色的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.08,0:13:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚确实是在猜拳中把妻子角色输给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.24,0:13:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没说过要扮女儿角色
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.73,0:13:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  就让我们继续吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.92,0:13:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎和诺亚外遇相爱了  对  从三年前就开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.47,0:13:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  三年前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.69,0:13:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事  亲爱的  给我解释一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.66,0:13:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  就算你这么对我说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.10,0:13:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎他  一直苦恼于夫人你的暴力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.96,0:13:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  我的暴力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.42,0:13:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  这就是其证据
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.76,0:14:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法忍受压力的太郎追寻着治愈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.16,0:14:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终到达了名为「诺亚」的绿洲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.98,0:14:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你胡说八道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.69,0:14:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  那么请温柔地触摸太郎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.60,0:14:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.08,0:14:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然做不到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.39,0:14:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夫人你除了暴力以外  和丈夫之间没有任何交流
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.87,0:14:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也能称为夫妇吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.98,0:14:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.19,0:14:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是说的有点过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.62,0:14:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐  我们是夫妇  所以碰触什么的很容易做到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.48,0:14:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结  结野
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.08,0:14:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.93,0:14:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太过分了  反对家庭暴力  的说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.77,0:14:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  但是我家丈夫看起来很舒服的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.00,0:15:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎他啊  是个会因痛楚而爽的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.34,0:15:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最喜欢被妻子痛扁的  超M变态
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.74,0:15:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是暴力  而是夫妇的另一种表现
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.73,0:15:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是在自曝你们是变态SM夫妇哦  一点也不觉得羞耻吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.85,0:15:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有关系  因为就算是这种恶心的丈夫  我也…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.69,0:15:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深爱着他
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.08,0:15:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有种被说的很过分的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.89,0:15:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.38,0:15:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.37,0:15:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.55,0:15:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家  为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.49,0:15:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追着被迷之鲨鱼型机械绑架的你们来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.40,0:15:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们玩的很快活嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.67,0:15:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中生了还玩家家酒真有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.72,0:16:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为挺有趣的  让我也参一脚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.73,0:16:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.98,0:16:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路过的  公主
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.28,0:16:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等一下  我没听说会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.80,0:16:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是太郎的青梅竹马
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.85,0:16:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对猪太郎的暴力可是有历史的了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.33,0:16:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是夺走太郎「第一次」的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.34,0:16:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是欧洲大国的公主  砂户太郎的情妇
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.53,0:16:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.00,0:16:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子  快把这个废物丢掉  得到幸福吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.07,0:16:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那群人  让人一点也搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.69,0:16:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎  你应该会觉得我的脚踢很爽对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.80,0:16:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽得不得了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.60,0:16:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这丫的太恶心了  快把岚子还回来  变态恶心猪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.94,0:16:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被骂得好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.68,0:16:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说你忘了我的调教的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.82,0:16:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  老师  那里不行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.99,0:16:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我国传承的爱之仪式  给我好好接受下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.93,0:16:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的我才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.69,0:17:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎居然会有如此淫乱的过去  太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.06,0:17:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不纯洁  不健康  外遇一个人只能有一次
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.04,0:17:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太美妙了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.69,0:17:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小学生就给我退下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.63,0:17:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是小学生  能干的职业妇女  是这样设定的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.48,0:17:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这体型这样说啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.85,0:17:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  诺亚还有秘策
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.04,0:17:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用女人的魅力来让把砂户同学迷得神魂颠倒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.57,0:17:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.70,0:17:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.96,0:17:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐  你这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.23,0:17:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用了什么手段
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.05,0:18:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.20,0:18:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.29,0:18:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让诺亚  有感觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.67,0:18:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊  柊学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.74,0:18:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由诺亚的发明而来的美妙身材
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.85,0:18:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这样砂户同学就应该满意了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.22,0:18:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以砂户同学  和诺亚一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.78,0:18:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.42,0:18:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.44,0:18:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.76,0:18:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.62,0:18:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为使用了这个药  怪物会…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.40,0:18:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那个是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.57,0:18:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙  我说过不许再吃那个恶魔之药的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.37,0:19:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是  日村吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.23,0:19:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  他一直都很温和的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.92,0:19:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是诺亚一吃这个药就会因愤怒而暴走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.04,0:19:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用那个变态腰带
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.48,0:19:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此  他是萝莉控啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.14,0:19:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了那个药的人  必须坠落到地狱去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.98,0:19:23.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话诺亚我们都要完了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.23,0:19:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够和现在的日村对抗的  只有砂户同学了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.19,0:19:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  做不到的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.72,0:19:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题的  是砂户同学的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.83,0:19:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.96,0:19:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.93,0:19:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了拯救我们啊  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.74,0:19:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么说的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.68,0:19:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.56,0:19:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好  爽
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.98,0:19:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一鼓作气  MM
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.47,0:19:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,LOLI  LOLI  LOLI  LOLI  LOLI
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.64,0:20:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M和萝莉控
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.42,0:20:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这变态之战无比壮绝  持续了三天三夜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.06,0:20:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实并没有那么久  只一眨眼  一小会儿  简简单单就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.97,0:20:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我记着  砂户太郎  我一定会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.57,0:20:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  然后啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.90,0:20:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.67,0:20:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有捞金鱼是我的特长
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.50,0:21:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  说起来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.72,0:21:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  给我一个棉花糖  这个可爱袋子装着的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.00,0:21:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢惠顾  哎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.91,0:21:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.59,0:21:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户啊  真巧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.96,0:21:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊  店长
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.75,0:21:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于也对二次元觉醒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.01,0:21:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么先给你介绍我的老婆们吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.53,0:21:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去其它地方买吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.85,0:21:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.42,0:21:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  是对今天努力的奖励哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.08,0:21:34.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有做过什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.17,0:21:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  就算没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.48,0:21:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你很讨人厌没人会找你  所以才叫你来的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.65,0:21:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.71,0:21:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.46,0:21:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.04,0:23:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  流星
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.59,0:23:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让世界上只有小小的可爱的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.27,0:23:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让世界变得只有梦幻迷你小裤裤
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.72,0:23:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让世界…  啊啊  消失啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.43,0:23:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  诺亚大人许了什么愿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.97,0:23:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说吧  汝
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.98,0:23:40.99,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.98,0:23:40.99,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.98,0:23:40.99,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.98,0:23:40.99,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}男男恋爱样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.98,0:23:40.99,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}男男恋爱样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.98,0:23:40.99,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(335,280)}男男恋爱样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.20,0:00:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
