[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.8
; http://www.aegisub.org/
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-05-29 21:42:00
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:MM!11
Original Script:澄空×华盟
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,5,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,5,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00000000,&H50FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,65,1
Style: SPEC2,方正黑体_GBK,14,&H2D000000,&HFF0000FF,&H64FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC3,@方正黑体_GBK,16,&H1E000000,&HFF0000FF,&H64FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,270.00,1,2,2,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC4,方正黑体_GBK,14,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC5,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&HFFFFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC6,方正黑体_GBK,12,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,3,10,10,10,1
Style: EDJP,DFGKaiSho-Md,15,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E1212D2,&H960D0AAC,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,7,15,20,5,1
Style: EDCN,方正楷体_GBK,14,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H1E1212D2,&H960D0AAC,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,7,15,25,5,1
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,21,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H00A11419,&HFF000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,5,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.43,0:02:43.45,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}翻译: 艾哀  天地有正气　校对: TurtleIzzy　打杂: バカばっかのHY、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.43,0:02:43.45,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.15,0:02:43.45,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}圣诞心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.15,0:02:43.45,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}圣诞心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.15,0:02:43.45,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}圣诞心愿
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.62,0:01:10.19,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.24,0:01:14.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.71,0:01:19.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.04,0:01:25.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}そこの迷えるオマエ　悲壮感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.71,0:01:30.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーがないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.05,0:01:35.45,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.53,0:01:41.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.78,0:01:44.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.36,0:01:46.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.51,0:01:48.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.71,0:01:53.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.47,0:01:58.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.17,0:02:00.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.51,0:02:02.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.75,0:02:07.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to へブン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.53,0:02:12.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.22,0:02:16.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.16,0:02:20.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.60,0:02:25.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.51,0:02:29.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.77,0:02:34.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.94,0:02:37.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.62,0:01:10.19,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.24,0:01:14.58,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.71,0:01:19.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.04,0:01:25.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那边的迷途小羔羊　满是悲壮感的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.71,0:01:30.96,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}连救命稻草都不要了　这也是无可奈何的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.05,0:01:35.45,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为今天的命运也在（横冲直撞）刁难人（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.53,0:01:41.26,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少我想　成为你的伙伴帮你一把
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.78,0:01:44.24,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.36,0:01:46.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}交给我试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.51,0:01:48.67,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.71,0:01:53.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}极限的界线太温和　全部毁灭归零会怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.47,0:01:58.11,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}顽固的DNA　勉强是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.17,0:02:00.48,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}在强制结束5秒之前（迫在眉睫）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.51,0:02:02.73,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}是不是有脱胎换骨的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.75,0:02:07.50,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}改改你的现场主义就能Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.53,0:02:12.15,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}不论有无　就让我用尽手段
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.22,0:02:16.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}现在就让你走上正途
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.16,0:02:20.54,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}有点超出存在感让人在意的恋人未满
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.60,0:02:25.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}一脸可怜的样子让人无法置之不理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.51,0:02:29.63,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为这已是改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.77,0:02:34.91,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}之后只要任凭摆布　随波逐流就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.94,0:02:37.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}HE! L! P!开始吧!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.93,0:21:11.00,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}まっしろな息をはずませ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.06,0:21:16.79,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}みんな会いにきてくれたの
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.88,0:21:20.15,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}「Happy birthday to you」「おめでとう」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.22,0:21:29.29,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}いちねん最初の笑顔 見せてあげたい(Thank you my dears)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.36,0:21:32.99,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}ありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.04,0:21:34.86,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}キャンドルに(キャンドルに)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.92,0:21:41.69,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}思い思いの祈りが揺れてる(祈りをこめ)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.78,0:21:52.27,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}たくさんのやさしさがここにあつまってきた
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.31,0:21:57.78,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}トクベツな日(It's my holy day)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.73,0:22:10.95,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}聖なる鐘の音がまた
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.03,0:22:16.80,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}ひとつ未来うながしてる
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.86,0:22:20.13,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}Happy birthday to me… おめでとう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.18,0:22:29.30,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}そっとココロに刻む この瞬間を(You bring me joy)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.35,0:22:34.77,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}よろこびに包まれて(包まれて)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.85,0:22:41.61,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}みんなの声もはずんでうれしい(うれしくなる)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.70,0:22:52.37,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}たいせつな温もりがまるで奇跡みたいに
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.45,0:22:55.44,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}届いたんだ(It's a dream come true)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.58,0:23:00.88,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}よろこびに包まれて(包まれて)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.11,0:23:07.93,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}みんなの声もはずんでうれしい(うれしくなる)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.05,0:23:18.56,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}いつか大人になっても ずっと覚えているよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.65,0:23:23.18,EDJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}トクベツな日(It's my holy day)
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.93,0:21:11.00,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}吐着白色的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.06,0:21:16.79,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}大家一起来找我了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.88,0:21:20.15,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}「祝你生日快乐」「生日快乐」
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.22,0:21:29.29,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}一年里最初的笑脸 想给你看到(谢谢你 我亲爱的)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.36,0:21:32.99,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.04,0:21:34.86,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}对着蜡烛 (对着蜡烛)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.92,0:21:41.69,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}包含众多思念的祈祷在摇曳着(注入祈祷)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.78,0:21:52.27,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}许许多多的温暖在这里聚集起来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.31,0:21:57.78,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}特别的那一天(它是我神圣的日子)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.73,0:22:10.95,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}神圣的钟声
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.03,0:22:16.80,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}又催促起一个未来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.86,0:22:20.13,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}祝我生日快乐… 生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.18,0:22:29.30,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}静静地刻在心里 将这个瞬间(你带给我快乐)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.35,0:22:34.77,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}被快乐包围着(包围着)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.85,0:22:41.61,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}回荡着大家的声音让我很开心(变得开心)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.70,0:22:52.37,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}最爱的温暖就像是奇迹一样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.45,0:22:55.44,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}传递过来了(这是实现了的梦想)
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.58,0:23:00.88,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}被快乐包围着(包围着)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.11,0:23:07.93,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}回荡着大家的声音让我很开心(变得开心)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.05,0:23:18.56,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}就算哪天长大了 也不会忘记哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.65,0:23:23.18,EDCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)\be10}特别的那一天(它是我神圣的日子)
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.85,0:00:07.86,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,0)}圣诞节前一天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.93,0:00:06.83,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐的愿望是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.08,0:00:07.92,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的愿望？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.35,0:00:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是神明所以不需要那种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.55,0:00:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了 赶快给我前进
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.80,0:00:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请让我把这放下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.32,0:00:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.54,0:00:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞老人是坐雪橇的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.45,0:00:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪麋鹿是拉雪橇的！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.76,0:00:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带刺的话和针叶树扎得我好～爽～啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.94,0:00:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽你妹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.60,0:00:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊好难受
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.90,0:00:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我放下来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.11,0:00:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.28,0:00:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.99,0:00:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把它放满整个城市
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.22,0:00:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎！？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.21,0:00:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.92,0:00:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,便签都放好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.36,0:00:47.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是七夕 拿便签有什么用啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.30,0:00:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以挂在许愿树上啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.74,0:00:55.74,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(545,55)\fs15\be2\fad(200,0)}许愿树
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.74,0:00:55.74,SPEC2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(545,115)\be2\fad(200,0)}将写上愿望的便签\N挂在这棵树上\N圣诞老人就会为你\N实现愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.74,0:00:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想为那些寻找救赎的人实现一个愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.34,0:00:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为圣诞礼物送给他们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.02,0:00:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.69,0:00:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.89,0:01:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 什么都没说
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.03,0:01:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实现圣诞节的愿望 也是神明的工作啊
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.44,0:02:48.11,SPEC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,0)}圣诞节当天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.63,0:02:48.22,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总而言之 虽然回收了便签…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.65,0:02:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比想象中的要少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.87,0:02:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是免费实现愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.98,0:02:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是写上「想变成美女」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.48,0:02:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「想变成有钱人」这类的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.06,0:03:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也无能为力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.10,0:03:04.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且名字都没写 怎么帮他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.96,0:03:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以回去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.36,0:03:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 还以为会人手不足特地多叫人来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.26,0:03:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐 知道委托人的便签 只有这两张
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.73,0:03:19.10,SPEC3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(140,85)\fad(200,0)}请救救爸爸的咖啡店
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.73,0:03:19.10,SPEC3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(540,85)\fad(200,0)}急募女服务生！因为感冒店内人手不足
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.58,0:03:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮助咖啡店和蛋糕店
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.32,0:03:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 就它们了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.82,0:03:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮哪个？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.16,0:03:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个都帮
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.82,0:03:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这么多人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.70,0:03:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就兵分两路地去实现他们的愿望吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.11,0:03:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.57,0:03:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.52,0:03:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎!?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.90,0:03:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说这俩店…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.09,0:03:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是正对着的两家店
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.29,0:03:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说我们是竞争对手了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.67,0:03:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竞争对手？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.02,0:03:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一决胜负吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.73,0:03:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说等等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.30,0:04:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有趣 我接受
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.55,0:04:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然有人向我们提出比赛我们就不能退缩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.78,0:04:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 有奖品的话应该会更有干劲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.61,0:04:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,200)}（奖品）
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.96,0:04:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.20,0:04:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢了就可以随便使唤他
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.08,0:04:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会加油的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.67,0:04:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们…不是来实现愿望的么…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.16,0:04:22.50,SPEC4,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(285,175)\fad(0,200)\frz5\fry-20\fs13\be2}爱丽丝咖啡店\N今日4时起包场
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.30,0:04:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 让这家店热闹起来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.70,0:04:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.90,0:04:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美 美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.34,0:04:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 樱守祭那时候的…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.96,0:04:36.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要拯救这家咖啡店的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.73,0:04:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就由我来实现
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.03,0:04:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张便签…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.94,0:04:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但劳烦美绪大人大驾…诚惶诚恐…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.43,0:04:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个也在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.35,0:04:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 请多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.74,0:04:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 真是家寒酸的店啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.53,0:04:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思真是太破旧了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.78,0:04:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样才有复兴的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.37,0:05:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能输给对面的蛋糕店
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.58,0:05:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉挺不好意思的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.67,0:05:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿成这样要干嘛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.54,0:05:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侦查啊侦查
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.41,0:05:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不能暴露身份
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.19,0:05:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们两个是恋人关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.39,0:05:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞节这样才正常吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.77,0:05:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.37,0:05:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸红什么啊猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.91,0:05:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是装装样子罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.53,0:05:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.28,0:05:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 客人还不少嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.92,0:05:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,价格适宜 种类丰富
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.02,0:05:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外表也没什么缺点
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.14,0:06:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.85,0:06:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键是味道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.29,0:06:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.82,0:06:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.39,0:06:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.79,0:06:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.15,0:06:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 不愿意啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.81,0:06:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没 没这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.01,0:06:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了 快点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.01,0:06:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.78,0:06:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.80,0:06:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家店不可小视啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.85,0:06:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问你们是情侣吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.19,0:06:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正在举行情侣限定的活动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.23,0:06:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活动？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.45,0:06:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人一起吃这根巧克力棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.10,0:06:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在觉得是极限的地方停下来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.41,0:06:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据所剩的长度 我们将送上礼品
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.08,0:06:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事谁会做啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.27,0:06:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位是初次约会吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.28,0:06:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话可能有点勉强吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.45,0:06:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才没…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.13,0:06:59.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说不参加的话就不算情侣？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.57,0:07:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向我挑战吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.62,0:07:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}喂喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.71,0:07:02.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放马过来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.48,0:07:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 开始！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.72,0:07:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先开始吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.99,0:07:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.18,0:07:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来一个圣诞蛋糕怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.34,0:07:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.02,0:07:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要哪个？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.17,0:08:01.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个好像都很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.43,0:08:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.95,0:08:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.80,0:08:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请给我蛋糕 还有烤猪排
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.35,0:08:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.70,0:08:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢 谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.45,0:08:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到变态能量了…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.28,0:08:26.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要放弃吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.89,0:08:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干嘛啊 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.02,0:08:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学 美绪学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.09,0:08:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.82,0:08:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}嘁 没想到会暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.40,0:08:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去了 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.90,0:08:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.80,0:08:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.91,0:08:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐老是和太郎在一起 太狡猾了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.20,0:08:52.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对面那家店着实是个强敌啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.51,0:08:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.99,0:08:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我想个好主意 现在马上
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.89,0:08:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太不讲理啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.24,0:08:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了各位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.88,0:09:03.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来一杯本店推荐的王室奶茶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.02,0:09:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.41,0:09:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 真是悠哉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.02,0:09:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.82,0:09:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 现在只能实行新菜单作战了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.26,0:09:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这么说…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.62,0:09:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了都交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.99,0:09:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人亲手做的料理？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.15,0:09:23.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算现在这家店立马倒闭也无所谓了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.44,0:09:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乌贼墨意面？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.21,0:09:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是奶油蛋黄意面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.84,0:09:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃吧猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.31,0:09:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.38,0:09:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想吃吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.52,0:09:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.66,0:09:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,张嘴 啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.45,0:09:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.28,0:09:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火山爆发！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.73,0:09:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在口中扩散开来的甘醇苦味
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.00,0:09:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直刺舌头的香辛料的痛楚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.23,0:09:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是意面界的黑船开国啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.79,0:09:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人的…特制奶油蛋黄意面…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.89,0:10:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然能把人感动到这份上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.58,0:10:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 这可是美绪大人亲手做的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.71,0:10:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 爸爸也一起吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.19,0:10:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.34,0:10:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吃得都晕过去了？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.18,0:10:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.96,0:10:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来一个本店推荐的蛋糕怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.45,0:10:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 从现在开始咖啡半价
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.62,0:10:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝赞限时优惠中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.19,0:10:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,限时优惠 还真想得出来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.88,0:10:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.37,0:10:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要超过他们！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.27,0:10:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.67,0:10:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚找到的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.83,0:10:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些东西菜单里有吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.95,0:10:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠这些就能赢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.60,0:10:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的东西全都2元出售
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.71,0:10:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,限时优惠大抢购哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.21,0:10:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2元也太低了点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.41,0:10:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.46,0:10:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店里的东西就是客人的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.15,0:10:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大卖一场吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.98,0:10:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2元也太犯规了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.20,0:11:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.60,0:11:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位注意
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.50,0:11:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在买附赠美少女的魔法哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.69,0:11:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔法是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.14,0:11:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 大家都在等着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.54,0:11:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么做才好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.98,0:11:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变好吃 变好吃～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.99,0:11:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你也跟着做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.59,0:11:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…变 变好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.90,0:11:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.87,0:11:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,lovelove
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.08,0:11:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,spice！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.43,0:11:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朝着你的心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.93,0:11:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发射！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.22,0:11:32.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发射
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.04,0:11:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话我们也祭出王牌！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.93,0:11:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,华丽地光临又小又脏的庶民小店
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.13,0:11:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么连我也要…穿成这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.99,0:11:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个 就这样给我去拉男人去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.77,0:11:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪倒在我的魅力之下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.47,0:11:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么说 马上会被人家发现我是男生的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.36,0:11:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像还不太清楚自己的女装素质啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.50,0:12:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有男人会看穿的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.35,0:12:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.03,0:12:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎子…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.95,0:12:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看一看啊看一看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.62,0:12:09.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多可爱的女生哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.69,0:12:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愚民们 尽情地崇拜我吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.45,0:12:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.93,0:12:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是太丢人啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.76,0:12:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了过来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.45,0:12:27.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.21,0:12:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.53,0:12:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.54,0:12:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去就要输了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.10,0:12:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么只有这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.25,0:12:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我掀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.17,0:12:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成熟的魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.33,0:12:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成熟的 魅力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.25,0:12:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个好主意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.56,0:12:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别限时优惠哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.77,0:12:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成熟的诺亚也掀…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.91,0:12:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.41,0:12:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此刺激强烈的风景…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.64,0:12:59.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没叫你！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.66,0:13:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.89,0:13:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我们也来！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.48,0:13:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点穿上
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.00,0:13:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这实在是太勉强了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.40,0:13:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无权拒绝！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.38,0:13:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成熟的美腿让人忍不住
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.33,0:13:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萝莉的腿也不能放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.35,0:13:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看 这个女生更…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.77,0:13:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕好可怕好可怕好可怕 好可怕啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.85,0:13:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Merry Christmas！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.50,0:13:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 终于结束了 结果到底是哪边赢了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.73,0:13:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 就不要提这个了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.92,0:13:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚和大家在一起很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.15,0:13:46.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来辰吉人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.98,0:13:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 去哪了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.48,0:13:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天已经关门了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.55,0:13:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 有预约过4点开始的包场的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.14,0:13:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 包场？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.58,0:14:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 是生日派对
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.21,0:14:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是圣诞派对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.99,0:14:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班上的一个女生的生日和圣诞是同一天
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.73,0:14:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要作为生日来好好庆祝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.60,0:14:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.55,0:14:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的蛋糕…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.32,0:14:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.69,0:14:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算现在开始做也赶不上了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.29,0:14:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法 只能先道歉再拒绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.49,0:14:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.31,0:14:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.46,0:14:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日派对照常进行
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.50,0:14:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.43,0:14:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要进行 绝对的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.70,0:14:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.35,0:14:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.88,0:14:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 来做吧 派对
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.33,0:14:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 庶民
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.20,0:14:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰…美小姐 料理拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.03,0:14:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店里的准备就由我和结野来做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.42,0:15:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,间宫同学和柊学姐去买蛋糕来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.35,0:15:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是受不了你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.61,0:15:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿你没办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.59,0:15:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday to you
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.36,0:15:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday to you
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.93,0:15:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday dear ——
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.13,0:15:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,——mio
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.93,0:15:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs16\pos(341,328)}美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.21,0:15:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday to you
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.47,0:15:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生日快乐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.71,0:15:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好累啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.10,0:15:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 能让他们高兴真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.90,0:15:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子看起来非常开心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.29,0:16:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神的字典里没有不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.87,0:16:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday dear mio
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.08,0:16:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.46,0:16:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 一脸复杂的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.58,0:16:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天难道说 是石动学姐的生日吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.76,0:16:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 但是美绪并不喜欢自己的生日
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.84,0:16:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从小时候开始就一个人过生日的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.05,0:16:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是今年不同了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.80,0:16:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心愿吗 说不定其实就只是想和大家在一起而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.25,0:16:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MM小子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.60,0:16:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别给我忘了 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.96,0:17:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地点就在社团教室没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.99,0:17:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 之后就是如何不让学姐发现来准备
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.88,0:17:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石动学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.49,0:17:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事 叶山
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.35,0:17:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎他啊 说「今天因为那个贫乳累死了 真不爽」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.26,0:17:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.24,0:17:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,争取时间 拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.27,0:17:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚 刚才的是事实吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.43,0:17:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了 你这洗衣板少女
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.89,0:17:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你没事乱来我已经受够了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.94,0:17:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 是什么啊 那个胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.65,0:17:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 呀 没胸部的小美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.37,0:17:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灭杀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.62,0:18:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住 你这混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.05,0:18:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.81,0:18:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点也没有生气 所以站住 你这大变态
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.53,0:18:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}绝对是骗人的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.63,0:18:26.59,SPEC5,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(356,109,345,83)\frz25}加油！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.63,0:18:26.59,SPEC5,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(455,245,444,219)\frz25}还差一点了\N祝你好运！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.05,0:18:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你逃到哪里 都要把你抹杀掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.19,0:18:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我站住
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.00,0:18:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.67,0:18:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}辰吉 快点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.46,0:18:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住 你这混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.59,0:18:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.80,0:18:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经逃不掉了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.14,0:18:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认命吧 混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.89,0:18:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老老实实说出来不就好了 「是我生日」这几个字
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.52,0:19:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很简单的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.95,0:19:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连自己的愿望都不能实现
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.68,0:19:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又为什么要去实现别人的愿望啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.00,0:19:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次每次 都是只关心别人的事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.99,0:19:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却又不说关键的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.06,0:19:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.38,0:19:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看在同在一个社团的份上 就听听你的遗言吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.24,0:19:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 学姐你觉得我怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.41,0:19:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话一直没有对学姐说
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.42,0:19:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷 冷不防的说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.08,0:19:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个时候 说这种事 有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.40,0:19:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.89,0:19:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.80,0:19:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什么 什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.35,0:19:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是 没有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.72,0:19:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 你 你 你这混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.18,0:20:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能抓到我的话就来抓抓看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.29,0:20:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是到地狱的尽头 也不会放过你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.04,0:20:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消失吧 你这垃圾
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.53,0:20:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这臭猪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.58,0:20:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我费这么大工夫 你这臭垃圾变态猪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.28,0:20:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天 是学姐的生日对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.39,0:20:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎…？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.03,0:20:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以大家就想搞个惊喜派对
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.81,0:20:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你可能不喜欢这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.77,0:20:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可是学姐出生的 特别的日子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.49,0:20:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜 美绪姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.33,0:21:04.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了呢 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.39,0:21:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.67,0:21:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是 这个该说是不一样呢 那个… 这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.58,0:21:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的啦 不是啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.72,0:21:34.40,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.01,0:21:39.55,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦 快来一口气吹灭掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.88,0:21:41.46,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是主角的工作哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.92,0:21:49.09,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这之前还有事要做
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.29,0:21:56.11,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在灭掉蜡烛的火之前 要先把这东西的生命之火灭掉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.53,0:21:59.61,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话很有趣呢 哈哈 哈哈 哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.81,0:22:01.41,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我是在开玩笑吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.42,0:22:04.74,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是喜日啊 喜日…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.94,0:22:13.89,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday to you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.32,0:22:17.29,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday to you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.10,0:22:22.69,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday dear mio
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.00,0:22:27.92,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Happy birthday to you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.84,0:22:37.53,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.85,0:22:39.12,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜的说
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.51,0:22:40.97,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜 美绪学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.69,0:22:43.74,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 大家
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.47,0:23:03.70,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.63,0:23:11.24,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有东西 想要送给你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.20,0:23:14.38,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是 我送给你的…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.77,0:23:22.06,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣诞礼物哟
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.05,0:23:28.42,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈 痛并快乐着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.66,0:23:39.62,SPEC6,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1400)}——太郎·岚子·诺亚·辰吉·由美·小满
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.66,0:23:39.62,SPEC6,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1400)\fs18}愿美绪学姐的愿望能够实现
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
