[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 2.1.7
; http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-03-06 15:30:46
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,25,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.6,0.3,2,10,10,6,1
Style: STAFF,微软雅黑,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H32000000,&HB4000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,8,10,10,5,1
Style: TITLE,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,5,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE2,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,7,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: TITLE3,方正大黑_GBK,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H007B0A25,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,3,0.00,1,8,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPJP,DFGCraftYu-W5,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H00A11419,&H967A0D11,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,7,20,20,5,1
Style: OPCN,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&H005B12E3,&H965C13B7,0,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,3,10,25,5,1
Style: NEXT,华康少女文字W5(P),28,&H3C001698,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC,方正准圆_GBK,24,&H00000000,&HFF0000FF,&H32FFFFFF,&H50FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,1,10,10,10,1
Style: SPEC2,方正准圆_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0000FF,&HFF000000,&HFFFFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,2,1,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------STAFF------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.67,0:02:50.68,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译: 艾哀  天地有正气　校对: TurtleIzzy　打杂: HySauce、魔动小贤、9416-kun
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.67,0:02:50.68,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20\fad(300,300)}澄空学园×华盟字幕社
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TITLE------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.63,0:02:38.88,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}天才少女暴走剧！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.63,0:02:38.88,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}天才少女暴走剧！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.63,0:02:38.88,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(330,330)\fad(50,0)}天才少女暴走剧！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.98,0:01:05.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.60,0:01:09.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.07,0:01:14.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.40,0:01:20.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこの迷えるオマエ　悲壮感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.07,0:01:26.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーがないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.41,0:01:30.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.89,0:01:36.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:39.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.72,0:01:41.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.87,0:01:44.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.07,0:01:48.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.83,0:01:53.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.53,0:01:55.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.87,0:01:58.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.11,0:02:02.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to へブン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.89,0:02:07.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.58,0:02:11.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.52,0:02:15.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.96,0:02:20.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.87,0:02:24.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.13,0:02:30.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.30,0:02:32.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.98,0:01:05.55,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.60,0:01:09.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.07,0:01:14.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.40,0:01:20.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的迷途小羔羊　满是悲壮感的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.07,0:01:26.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连救命稻草都不要了　这也是无可奈何的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.41,0:01:30.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为今天的命运也在（横冲直撞）刁难人（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.89,0:01:36.62,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我想　成为你的伙伴帮你一把
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.14,0:01:39.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NO!! Jesus crisis! Oh my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.72,0:01:41.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给我试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.87,0:01:44.03,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.07,0:01:48.69,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极限的界线太温和　全部毁灭归零会怎样？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.83,0:01:53.47,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顽固的DNA　勉强是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.53,0:01:55.84,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在强制结束5秒之前（迫在眉睫）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.87,0:01:58.09,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有脱胎换骨的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.11,0:02:02.86,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改改你的现场主义就能Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.89,0:02:07.51,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论有无　就让我用尽手段
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.58,0:02:11.46,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就让你走上正途
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.52,0:02:15.90,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点超出存在感让人在意的恋人未满
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.96,0:02:20.76,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一脸可怜的样子让人无法置之不理
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.87,0:02:24.99,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这已是改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.13,0:02:30.27,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后只要任凭摆布　随波逐流就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.30,0:02:32.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,HE! L! P!开始吧!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.89,0:21:58.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.96,0:22:02.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.14,0:22:04.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.87,0:22:07.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.54,0:22:12.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.68,0:22:14.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.07,0:22:18.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}それとも…いいの？ よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.08,0:22:22.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.92,0:22:23.32,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.37,0:22:24.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.66,0:22:25.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.97,0:22:28.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.60,0:22:29.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}愛には恋は緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.97,0:22:33.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}純情文武両立させて insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.51,0:22:35.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.99,0:22:39.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}嫌われてもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.87,0:22:46.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.72,0:22:50.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}どうして？ そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.68,0:22:53.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.14,0:22:56.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.32,0:22:58.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.44,0:23:01.05,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて達成しなくちゃ　胸、痛い。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.08,0:23:06.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}とにかく気持ちが止まらないの
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.79,0:23:08.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.98,0:23:12.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}せめて挑戦したいよ　したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.03,0:23:14.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.72,0:23:17.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.44,0:23:24.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}だって特別キミは特別…押して！ yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.89,0:21:58.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.96,0:22:02.07,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少为达成目的也要不择手段？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.14,0:22:04.81,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸气呼气这是告白的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.87,0:22:07.52,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但我一直无法安心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.54,0:22:12.60,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}那个一定是特别的…万岁！ yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.68,0:22:14.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}靠近一点…会讨厌吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.07,0:22:18.06,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}还是说…可以？ 一进一退背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.08,0:22:22.83,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}恐怖和笑容说不定很像 靠近围观我很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.92,0:22:23.32,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.37,0:22:24.66,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}爱和恋我都不擅长应付
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.66,0:22:25.93,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}纯情单方片面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.97,0:22:28.57,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}商量和子弹 da-dan-da down load 对啦！对啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.60,0:22:29.94,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}爱和恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.97,0:22:33.33,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}纯情的文武双全 insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.51,0:22:35.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}我想做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.99,0:22:39.78,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}就算被讨厌也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.87,0:22:46.10,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}在我的眼中你是如此耀眼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.72,0:22:50.61,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}为什么？ 对啦…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.68,0:22:53.12,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}但是请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.14,0:22:56.29,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}只有一个位子所以要不择手段！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.32,0:22:58.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.44,0:23:01.05,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少也要达到目的 胸口好疼。
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.08,0:23:06.72,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}总而言之我的心意已经无法阻挡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.79,0:23:08.92,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}请用心决定 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.98,0:23:12.00,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}至少想挑战一下 挑战一下！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.03,0:23:14.65,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}吸气这是同意的天气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.72,0:23:17.40,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}答应想要安心的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.44,0:23:24.36,OPCN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(50,50)}因为是特别的你 就让我特别地…推倒你！  yeah-yeah-yaeh-yaeh!!
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------TEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.31,0:00:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶灵退散！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.40,0:00:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫好烫好烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.17,0:00:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蕴含于大气中的魔力哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.94,0:00:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驱散附身于你的超M恶灵吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.18,0:00:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜡蜡蜡蜡蜡…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.96,0:00:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来  再来  再来…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.75,0:00:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪真是很适合魔女装啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.95,0:00:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万四千  一万五千…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.81,0:00:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万六千  一万七千  一万八千…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.76,0:00:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两万！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.61,0:00:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强大
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.74,0:00:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我适可而止！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.01,0:00:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.44,0:01:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于让我找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.30,0:01:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚的福音
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.23,0:02:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美那家伙  为什么现在还…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.32,0:02:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.27,0:02:48.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.36,0:02:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏什么呢  情书吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.12,0:02:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.72,0:02:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉那家伙  还真受人欢迎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.92,0:03:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  这是…！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.56,0:03:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前略
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.60,0:03:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话想和砂户君说（心）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.77,0:03:13.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放学后请来发明部的部室
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.63,0:03:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等你哦（心）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.73,0:03:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真  真的是情书
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.97,0:03:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  我们学校有发明部吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.80,0:03:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发明部部长柊学姐可是名人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.95,0:03:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,智商超过200的天才
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.25,0:03:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发表的论文和专利不计其数
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.18,0:03:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.20,0:03:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  长得超可爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.59,0:03:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.04,0:03:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野！？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.35,0:03:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么纸啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.45,0:03:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没没没…没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.05,0:03:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说你有什么事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.80,0:03:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  刚刚美绪学姐打来电话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.21,0:03:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说自己今天请假
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.80,0:04:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  还真少见啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.23,0:04:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那今天的社团活动取消吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.57,0:04:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  美绪姐说了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.98,0:04:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「就算我请假了  也不许翘社团活动」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.89,0:04:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.04,0:04:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.31,0:04:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然这是情书啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.90,0:04:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底对方是个怎样的女生呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.64,0:04:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.33,0:04:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算两人的气氛不错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.40,0:04:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦被对方知道了我的超M体质
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.94,0:04:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对会被甩的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.74,0:04:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我这种人本来就不可能收到情书
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.21,0:04:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说  是知道我超M变态的人的恐吓信吗！？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.37,0:04:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.98,0:04:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得好可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.48,0:05:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是去吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.93,0:05:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.67,0:05:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什  什么时候来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.08,0:05:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在要去社团活动吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.81,0:05:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.89,0:05:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.60,0:05:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会不去吧  社团活动室
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.15,0:05:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我有点事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.89,0:05:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.07,0:05:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头我会过去的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.30,0:05:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.55,0:05:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还  还是来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.69,0:05:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.52,0:05:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在等你哦  砂户太郎同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.84,0:05:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚名叫柊诺亚  发明部的部长
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.89,0:05:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊诺亚学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.02,0:05:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识诺亚吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.97,0:05:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  好像是很厉害的天才
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.35,0:05:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  诺亚是天才
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.12,0:05:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么可爱的女生喜欢我…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.09,0:05:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.89,0:05:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.82,0:06:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚有一个很重要的请求
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.22,0:06:03.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请求？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.37,0:06:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.69,0:06:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.53,0:06:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这种眼神请求我的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.11,0:06:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能帮诺亚做一个重要的实验
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.35,0:06:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  实验？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.24,0:06:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学是我特别的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.61,0:06:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.57,0:06:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学要是肯帮我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.92,0:06:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚什么都会做的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.33,0:06:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中男生都很色的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.82,0:06:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为诺亚是天才所以知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.81,0:06:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要用色相打动他们
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.70,0:06:45.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会一切顺利了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.26,0:06:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.76,0:06:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.87,0:06:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让砂户同学帮我  诺亚要全裸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.74,0:07:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以拜托了  请你帮助诺亚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.81,0:07:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你不帮诺亚的话  诺亚就不把扣子解开
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.92,0:07:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.58,0:07:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？  那么赶紧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.54,0:07:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.37,0:07:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实验开始！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.23,0:07:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要让你更加痛苦！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.77,0:07:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快挂掉了…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.88,0:07:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实验非常成功！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.73,0:07:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托你的福计划开展得很顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.30,0:07:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.78,0:07:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来晚了么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.21,0:07:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.93,0:08:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是诺亚大人的助手  日村雪之丞
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.80,0:08:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类变态化计划？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.08,0:08:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.13,0:08:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一会儿再和你说明
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.86,0:08:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不快点制止诺亚大人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.71,0:08:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全人类就都要变成变态了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.97,0:08:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.24,0:08:15.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一阶段已经结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.77,0:08:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱守高中的学生已经全都变态化了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.63,0:08:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,锁骨  果然女生还是要看锁骨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.92,0:08:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱身材可绝不输给列奥纳多！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.33,0:08:28.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Oh  Yes  布鲁马
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.65,0:08:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我下半生就全裸下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.02,0:08:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从很早以前就对学姐你…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.41,0:08:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以叫我姐姐大人哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.87,0:08:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.36,0:08:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚大人发现了一种由变态人释放的变态能量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.95,0:08:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它能放大普通人体内蕴藏的些许变态性力量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.81,0:08:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚大人想通过这个力量
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.48,0:09:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将全地球的人类变态化
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.20,0:09:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.30,0:09:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是真的女王
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.48,0:09:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我顶礼膜拜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.42,0:09:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉  给我让开
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.82,0:09:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我按摩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.77,0:09:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要按摩…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.84,0:09:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子大人  多踩我几下吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.63,0:09:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生好可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.79,0:09:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.22,0:09:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学校变成这样都是砂户同学的错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.22,0:09:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.86,0:09:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为你拥有超出常识庞大变态能量
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.60,0:09:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个计划才会成功的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.04,0:09:43.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我早点阻止诺亚大人的话就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.06,0:09:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个好象是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.52,0:09:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.06,0:09:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是柊学姐的袜子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.83,0:09:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.54,0:09:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.90,0:09:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是有那种兴趣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.81,0:10:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢可爱的东西应该是人类的本性吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.65,0:10:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.83,0:10:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入发明部也是因为柊学姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.74,0:10:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.75,0:10:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有萝莉可爱身材的学姐和我约好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.79,0:10:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会为我做出人类幼儿化装置
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.88,0:10:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不也是个变态吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.23,0:10:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个  现在还是快点去诺亚大人那里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.75,0:10:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐在哪里？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.57,0:10:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.95,0:10:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.95,0:10:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是将变态能量共振后向全世界发送的装置
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.30,0:10:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要阻止诺亚大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.67,0:10:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.64,0:10:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是诺亚大人的敌人！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.97,0:10:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要妨碍诺亚大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.98,0:10:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.58,0:10:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.92,0:10:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够将变态能量转换为超能力的诺亚大人的发明
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.74,0:10:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豪华变态零号
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.47,0:10:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害  真不愧是砂户君
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.70,0:10:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好强大的变态力
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.88,0:10:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}什么能量要出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.54,0:11:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.61,0:11:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭  臭老太婆  我对你们没兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.59,0:11:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.24,0:11:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死小白脸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.37,0:11:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是向不受欢迎的男生挑衅么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.19,0:11:28.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这  这里就交给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.93,0:11:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学赶快去屋顶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.88,0:11:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  在一切还能挽回的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.80,0:11:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉了  日村
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.44,0:11:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学  世界就交给你了…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.99,0:11:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙不可原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.21,0:11:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日村  你是真爷们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.84,0:11:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是个萝莉控！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.70,0:11:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊  诺亚大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.11,0:12:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐  不要做傻事了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.92,0:12:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经没有用了  砂户
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.83,0:12:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里所收集到的变态能量将会把全人类都化为变态
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.79,0:12:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎能让你得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.59,0:12:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要妨碍诺亚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.23,0:12:34.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上吧  把这家伙轰成渣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.83,0:12:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.65,0:12:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊  救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.71,0:13:03.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,距离诺亚所追求的世界  还差一点了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.29,0:13:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我还有更多力量的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.78,0:13:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是能够把变态能量转换为超能力的腰带
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.64,0:13:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态能量…  对了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.87,0:13:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是只能赌一把
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.24,0:13:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎  有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.48,0:13:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐  身体还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.28,0:13:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是  因为担心我才…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.20,0:13:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话要对学姐说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.65,0:13:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  什么啊  你这是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.33,0:13:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丑女！平胸！母猪！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.79,0:13:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.34,0:13:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好快
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.60,0:13:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说谁是丑女啊  还有你说了「平胸」？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.77,0:14:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了「母猪」？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.99,0:14:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  对不起…  啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.45,0:14:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真烦啊  搓衣板  没胸还拽什么拽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.69,0:14:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  这么不想活了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.91,0:14:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是个变态猪太郎而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.72,0:14:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混  混蛋  猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.08,0:14:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是变态  居然对美绪大人我…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.96,0:14:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  火大
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.38,0:14:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs20}好…  好…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.75,0:14:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好你妹啊  你这超M变态人渣混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.12,0:14:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.15,0:15:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.90,0:15:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多亏了你  我进化成为「超级大变态」了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.24,0:15:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很危险  请退下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.30,0:15:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.78,0:15:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  快点  趁我还有理性的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.78,0:15:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs18}（悟空变超赛后对悟饭说的...）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.74,0:15:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.33,0:15:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雕虫小技
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.92,0:15:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐  快住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.78,0:15:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开  开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.49,0:15:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解除限制  把那个碍事的家伙消灭掉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.28,0:15:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你见识下超越「超M」的「超级大变态」的厉害吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.56,0:15:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是  什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.90,0:16:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变  态  波！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.71,0:16:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.35,0:16:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户  很可惜  是诺亚赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.37,0:16:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有的工程都结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.90,0:16:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上变态能量就会发送  遍布整个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.26,0:16:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界将会成为变态们的乐园
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.97,0:16:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要做这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.30,0:16:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了制造诺亚的伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.41,0:16:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚是天才  和普通人不一样  是被选中的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.85,0:17:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以一次都没有和同年纪的人玩耍过
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.19,0:17:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚想要和朋友一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.16,0:17:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学习结束之后一起玩会也没关系的吧  呐  呐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.40,0:17:18.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚只是想要朋友而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.48,0:17:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚一直都是孤零零的  因为「不普通」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.78,0:17:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就让所有人都变得「不普通」就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.17,0:17:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  所以
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.22,0:17:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把大家都变成变态
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.51,0:17:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.80,0:17:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样  诺亚就不再是孤零零的了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.69,0:17:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.80,0:17:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为超M这一个「才能」
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.01,0:17:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我也苦恼于孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.60,0:17:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐她就更…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.28,0:17:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐  可以的话就让我来陪你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.34,0:17:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐想要做的事  全都一起来做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.73,0:18:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来和我一起「普通」地玩耍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.14,0:18:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.32,0:18:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说吧  想要玩什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.01,0:18:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.53,0:18:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那  那么就扮家家酒  荡秋千和爬铁架  还有丢接球
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.23,0:18:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.04,0:18:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.32,0:18:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.50,0:18:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入最终阶段了  已经来不及了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.74,0:18:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一分钟  全人类就要都变成变态了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.11,0:18:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.70,0:18:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  诺亚也无法阻止它了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.80,0:18:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会  难道只能这样等全人类都变成变态了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.91,0:18:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经  无论如何都于事无补了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.79,0:18:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止  了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.58,0:18:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态啊  拥抱大气吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.40,0:19:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态与常人的等级不同
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.15,0:19:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人心潮澎湃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.37,0:19:06.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧张也没关系  来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.10,0:19:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态并不值得羞耻
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.31,0:19:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个声音是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.79,0:19:12.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态  大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.50,0:19:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的变态们  正呼唤着我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.33,0:19:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  完全搞不懂什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.91,0:19:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家  把「变态」分给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.17,0:19:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咕…  恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.18,0:19:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家  变态力量  我收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.23,0:19:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.29,0:20:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用机械来把强行人类变成变态这种行为是扭曲的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.30,0:20:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我这点的是  纯粹的变态们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.79,0:20:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是变态们所创造的…  奇迹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.74,0:20:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.49,0:20:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这感觉是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.59,0:20:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个感觉  无法理解
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.09,0:20:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.57,0:20:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.55,0:20:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为学姐来了  所以世界摆脱危机了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.33,0:20:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然从刚才开始一点没搞懂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.60,0:20:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有一点很清楚的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.31,0:20:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得对我说了什么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.39,0:20:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了我  「丑女」  「平胸」  「母猪」
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.99,0:20:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来需要最极致的惩罚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.56,0:20:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.04,0:21:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂  从现在开始的一周  觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.52,0:21:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  好的  很乐意
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.35,0:21:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  是礼物  送给砂户
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.79,0:21:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.21,0:21:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户  请不要忘记约定
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.59,0:21:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个花
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.00,0:21:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是紫丁香啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.31,0:21:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.22,0:21:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫丁香的花语是  「初恋」哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.97,0:21:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  是这样的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.44,0:21:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.88,0:21:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个变态好色猪混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.10,0:21:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  为什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.90,0:21:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈  好爽
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,//------------------NEXT-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.06,0:23:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  诺亚好想「普通」地玩个痛快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.09,0:23:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捉迷藏  抓鬼游戏…  怎么了  日村
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.10,0:23:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的野心？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.18,0:23:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西我怎么知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.09,0:23:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等着你来哦  砂户
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.94,0:23:40.90,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.94,0:23:40.90,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.94,0:23:40.90,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(240,240)\fs20}次回
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.94,0:23:40.90,TITLE3,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(325,280)}我家大骚动
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.94,0:23:40.90,TITLE2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(325,280)}我家大骚动
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.94,0:23:40.90,TITLE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(325,280)}我家大骚动
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
