[Script Info]
Title:清雨
Original Script:清雨
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.8,0.4,2,10,10,8,134
Style: staff,黑体,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00860BF4,&H64860BF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,128
Style: OPCH,华康圆体W5(P),24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0000,&H64FF0000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正大黑简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.11,0:00:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.21,0:00:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的声音是？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.09,0:00:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.36,0:00:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫 好烫好 烫 好烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.33,0:00:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明应该持续感受到痛苦的话就会厌倦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.53,0:00:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是超M体质的砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.20,0:00:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙真是个千锤百炼的变态 真没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.65,0:00:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑下一个作战吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.70,0:00:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.08,0:00:37.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.95,0:00:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗完澡就来一发真是太爽啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.98,0:02:23.86,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由极影字幕社(bbs.ktxp.com)制作 仅供交流试看 喜爱本作品请支持Z版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.98,0:02:23.86,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译: 神代辰弥  kaouji   特效: W-BOY   后期: 清雨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.84,0:02:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也被整的好惨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.96,0:02:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.67,0:02:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这样的…像你这样的…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.92,0:02:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎 怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.76,0:02:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.18,0:03:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请再揍我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.17,0:03:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用言语辱骂我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.39,0:03:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.71,0:03:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟超M体质的元凶会在同一个社团
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.76,0:03:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要跟她一起吧 下一班吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.11,0:03:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.35,0:03:49.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.45,0:03:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算等下一班也不见得会有位置坐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.39,0:03:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.25,0:03:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么为什么没上车
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.09,0:04:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑上车很危险 请不要这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.50,0:04:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要关车门了 请注意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.30,0:04:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.55,0:04:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.60,0:04:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是把你丢下不管就回家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.39,0:04:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计会被学姐和满老师往死里整
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.42,0:04:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哪里不舒服吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.10,0:04:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是 我对男人…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.89,0:04:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.83,0:04:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别靠近我！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.27,0:04:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.05,0:04:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是做错了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.85,0:04:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很害怕男人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.73,0:04:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男性恐惧症？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.41,0:04:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和男的在一起 就会觉得很不舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.63,0:04:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次都是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.93,0:04:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候也能忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.29,0:05:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道常常迟到或是请假也是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.56,0:05:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是很难启齿的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.97,0:05:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么迄今为止 一直都扁我也是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.36,0:05:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都害怕被男的碰到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.61,0:05:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不禁…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.21,0:05:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 在被打之前先打过去…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.51,0:05:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太扯啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.38,0:05:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别用这样的表情 我也知道这是不对的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.02,0:05:39.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 我会好好保持距离的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.29,0:05:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.13,0:05:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.05,0:05:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的名字是太郎对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.68,0:05:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.83,0:05:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你太郎行吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.67,0:05:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小时候养过一只狗 名字也叫太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.73,0:05:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙是小狗的太郎 小狗的太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.84,0:05:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是人 不是男人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.38,0:06:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可怕 不可怕 一点都不可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.73,0:06:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙居然对自己心理暗示
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.33,0:06:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 这里得说教一下她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.31,0:06:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是岚子大人您的一只低贱的畜生小狗汪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.42,0:06:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请你下命令吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.98,0:06:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又犯了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.33,0:06:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别笑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.42,0:06:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.89,0:06:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中学以来一直都很不擅长应对她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.84,0:06:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑着的结野很可爱…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.53,0:06:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那明天见
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.02,0:06:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.37,0:06:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事情想拜托你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.98,0:06:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实 我也完全不想拜托你这种事情的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.86,0:06:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.52,0:06:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快要期中考了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.86,0:06:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 拜托你帮我复习
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.98,0:07:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为班里没有其他能拜托的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.30,0:07:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.07,0:07:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么拜托石动学姐如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.08,0:07:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 美绪学姐她 好像成绩不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.09,0:07:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以拜托了 一生就此一次的拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.02,0:07:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.48,0:07:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.38,0:07:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想就我一个人的话结野还是会感到难受的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.48,0:07:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.87,0:07:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野 这家伙其实是辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.20,0:07:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我擦 叶山君
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.00,0:07:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拜托的人只是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.47,0:07:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙成绩很好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.66,0:07:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话 你就不会把他当成男人了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.70,0:07:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说来 能有这么漂亮的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.12,0:07:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了美绪以外还没见到过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.59,0:08:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么看都是女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.59,0:08:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别 别这么看我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.20,0:08:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺带一提 服装是我亲手做的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.46,0:08:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是满姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.64,0:08:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 现在的我是不是很怪？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.15,0:08:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.23,0:08:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 可爱极了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.60,0:08:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.36,0:08:20.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自信点 对你的美貌
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.44,0:08:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微把脸斜过来点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.13,0:08:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.61,0:08:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 能给你个及格分
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.61,0:08:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然比不上我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.33,0:08:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全算得上是美少女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.91,0:08:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没被你以外的别人看过这模样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.19,0:08:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.27,0:08:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.34,0:08:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…很美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.14,0:08:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.61,0:08:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.19,0:08:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.52,0:08:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的美貌可是世界第一
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.17,0:09:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愚民们多些赞美我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.92,0:09:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 辰吉？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.02,0:09:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过就是个平民别叫的那么随便
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.58,0:09:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是来世能做贵族的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.64,0:09:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陪陪你跳支舞也不是不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.58,0:09:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪的人格出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.12,0:09:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这变态说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.60,0:09:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的美 可是跨越性别的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.47,0:09:24.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.16,0:09:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然还有个毫无起伏的胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.90,0:09:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的算是女人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.70,0:09:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你丫的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.50,0:09:38.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,区区一个变态 居然对人家的胸部…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.97,0:09:41.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐冷静点 这家伙和我不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.58,0:09:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是再这样下去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.53,0:09:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我变成海藻屑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.18,0:09:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样考前复习开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.63,0:09:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关系超差的辰吉和石动学姐也还是会小打小闹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.07,0:09:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是得过且过下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.63,0:10:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放学后的复习会还是继续着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.55,0:10:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于明天就是期中考的当日
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.87,0:10:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就走这边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.53,0:10:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.26,0:10:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.13,0:10:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.28,0:10:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.92,0:10:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要我送你回家是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.45,0:10:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都没有说过…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.32,0:10:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何都要的话就让你送吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.72,0:10:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样我的超M不会有反应的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.47,0:10:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是是 请让我送你你吧 岚子公主
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.42,0:10:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真没办法呢 既然说到这份上就让你随行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.88,0:10:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 别在我身边走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.16,0:10:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离我身后三米
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.31,0:10:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离那么远
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.75,0:10:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被袭击的话 我来不及救你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.88,0:10:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两米的话还能接受
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.16,0:11:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里的人还没回来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.96,0:11:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天的考试没问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.18,0:11:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题 都用功到这份上了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.45,0:11:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 说的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.03,0:11:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.60,0:11:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.91,0:11:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.57,0:11:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今为止 帮我复习的事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.94,0:11:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢…谢…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.64,0:11:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无上光荣 岚子公主
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.87,0:11:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要在复习一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.84,0:11:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也快回家吧 再见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.48,0:11:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道谢的话要好好的说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.63,0:11:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.85,0:11:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.43,0:11:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九十分应该没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.27,0:11:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉老师真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.19,0:12:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子有努力复习啊  了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.05,0:12:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都晚回家的复习
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.80,0:12:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜它所赐 应该能考及格
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.41,0:12:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.88,0:12:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.90,0:12:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚好够人数
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.73,0:12:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.25,0:12:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动物园？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.48,0:12:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔去去也不坏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.09,0:12:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我们一起的话 结野会…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.98,0:12:36.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动物园？！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.11,0:12:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满老师太谢谢了 我超期待
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.73,0:12:43.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 动物园哦 动物园
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.88,0:12:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子最喜欢动物园是吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.89,0:12:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.12,0:12:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她忘记了和我们一起去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.26,0:12:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你咋了？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.23,0:12:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.98,0:12:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 不准爽约哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.50,0:12:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算感冒了 遇到事故也好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.12,0:12:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也绝对要来 懂了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.97,0:13:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.89,0:13:16.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.02,0:13:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又擅自跑到我被窝里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.22,0:13:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上的起床时间要跟太郎一起度过
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.37,0:13:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯粹的欲望啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.01,0:13:28.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪门子的纯粹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.91,0:13:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闹钟！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.03,0:13:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥？我明明调了8点的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.55,0:13:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我停下来的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.82,0:13:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.81,0:13:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为两个人的恋爱不能容下其他东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.53,0:13:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么恋爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.61,0:13:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个闲人大学生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.02,0:13:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.52,0:13:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉好幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.74,0:13:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太不公平了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.11,0:13:56.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也有受到甜蜜而又严厉的辱骂的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.63,0:13:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.29,0:14:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎  你这个坏心眼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.35,0:14:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也让我陪睡吧please~
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.11,0:14:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 我迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.74,0:14:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都不在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.69,0:14:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是些不守时的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.42,0:14:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我迟到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.57,0:14:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有太郎一个？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.01,0:14:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 我白道歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.58,0:14:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.49,0:14:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.59,0:14:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 时间已经过很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.29,0:14:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子到了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.70,0:14:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.52,0:14:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么今天你们两个就加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.78,0:14:47.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？你说什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.61,0:14:50.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个一起享受动物园的意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.72,0:14:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就不来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.38,0:14:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞不懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.01,0:14:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 变态帝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.47,0:15:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是改善超M和克服男性恐惧症的行动的一环
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.84,0:15:03.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你们两个是很像
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.33,0:15:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和结野？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.96,0:15:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被女性虐待感到快感的你就像
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.93,0:15:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女性接近你就会感到某种的恐惧是一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.63,0:15:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而岚子是对男性存在的恐惧而无可奈何
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.25,0:15:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.81,0:15:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是人类是会适应环境的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.51,0:15:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的你们最需要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.10,0:15:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 岚子就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.39,0:15:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…学姐 喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.65,0:15:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好大 鼻子好长好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.71,0:15:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这难道是？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.62,0:15:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说中的约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.92,0:15:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来过来 太郎看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.90,0:15:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近你们两个的关系挺不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.61,0:15:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以把岚子托付给你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.06,0:15:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 结野是怎么得上男性恐惧症的？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.37,0:16:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事去问本人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.60,0:16:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本人吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.55,0:16:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.08,0:16:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.35,0:16:10.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然和我一起的话高兴不起来？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.86,0:16:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.05,0:16:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才听到电话的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.80,0:16:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满老师跟我说了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.98,0:16:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须要习惯和男人相处
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.55,0:16:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎现在是为了这个才跟我在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.91,0:16:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.76,0:16:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪她们在努力着
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.32,0:16:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我也要努力一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.91,0:16:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你也就像狗一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.16,0:16:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.96,0:16:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.05,0:16:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正都是狗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.04,0:16:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.85,0:16:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候真是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.56,0:16:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.29,0:16:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中学时候的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.19,0:16:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我误会了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.70,0:16:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.42,0:16:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.51,0:16:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我的超M醒觉的那事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.78,0:16:53.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个耳光
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.98,0:16:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 误会是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.67,0:17:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候我以为我的挚友被抢走…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.03,0:17:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.98,0:17:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.25,0:17:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个可怜的超级大畜生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.59,0:17:21.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论是钻火圈走钢丝杂耍还是被打
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.81,0:17:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 和她一起在马戏团演出…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.25,0:17:28.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个死猪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.22,0:17:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 他犯病了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.11,0:17:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？ 要好好保重啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.86,0:17:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.65,0:17:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥也别说了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.66,0:17:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是我的不对
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.90,0:17:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 总算是过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.32,0:17:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱 毛茸茸 好想住这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.60,0:17:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子的伤口大概
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.46,0:17:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比你所想象的还要深
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.21,0:18:02.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是笑容最适合她
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.89,0:18:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以拜托你了太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.41,0:18:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.34,0:18:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的是很喜欢动物园啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.76,0:18:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 而且这里是充满回忆的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.10,0:18:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回忆？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.21,0:18:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是幼儿园的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.20,0:18:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全家一起来过一次 三个人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.09,0:18:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说好了绝对还会再来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.11,0:18:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果至今再也没有来过了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.11,0:18:31.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.42,0:18:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸和妈妈离婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.04,0:18:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.85,0:18:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.55,0:18:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.78,0:18:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么得上男性恐惧症的？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.33,0:18:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有点在意而已
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.25,0:18:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想说的话就算了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.18,0:18:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有从美绪那里听说过吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.48,0:18:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫我去问本人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.57,0:18:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.23,0:19:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 我们走了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.26,0:19:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.52,0:19:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中学的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.99,0:19:10.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟现在不一样 很活泼又很开朗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.63,0:19:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也很有男人缘
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.36,0:19:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是对这没有兴趣 所以都拒绝了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.43,0:19:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 初二的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.58,0:19:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高我一届的吉冈学长
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.17,0:19:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何 结野？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.82,0:19:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.73,0:19:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.90,0:19:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会有会拒绝学长的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.63,0:19:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为什么 总觉得拒绝不了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.37,0:19:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉冈不就是长得像模特 很有人气的人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.39,0:19:46.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果还是交往了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.21,0:19:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有一天 学长突然到了我家
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.90,0:19:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强迫的想要吻我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.00,0:19:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不停地挣扎 结果划破了学长的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.42,0:20:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流了血
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.52,0:20:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 她确实和我很相似
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.88,0:20:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中学的时候 M体质暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.72,0:20:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被全班同学孤立的我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.09,0:20:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石动学姐说我们很像的那句话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.79,0:20:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.36,0:20:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪打来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.65,0:20:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.01,0:20:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.16,0:20:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和变态一起没问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.14,0:20:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有对你做什么奇怪的事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.00,0:21:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把岚子弄哭的话我轻饶不了你 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.52,0:21:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.72,0:21:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.34,0:21:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪学姐和满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.03,0:21:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天都会打电话或发短信给我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.80,0:21:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.73,0:21:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用短信来聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.20,0:21:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉蛮有趣的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.22,0:21:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我几乎没有能这样的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.81,0:21:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一等 你要干什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.72,0:21:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的邮箱给你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.71,0:21:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你 我也在我的手机里输入了你的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.71,0:21:37.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.06,0:21:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有空的话 就能发短信什么的给你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.85,0:21:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.89,0:21:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里好笑了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.19,0:21:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.65,0:21:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子 果然是岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.40,0:21:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找你很久了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.93,0:22:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美为什么会在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.61,0:22:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.83,0:23:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被石动学姐踢 被结野殴打
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.52,0:23:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天M体质又觉醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.98,0:23:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样可不行 我要变坚强
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.39,0:23:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 尽情得来蹂躏我吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.75,0:23:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…爽…
Dialogue: 2,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 1,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,452,848,453)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,453,848,454)}{\1c&HFAF7FD&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,454,848,455)}{\1c&HF6F0FC&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,455,848,456)}{\1c&HF2E9FB&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,456,848,457)}{\1c&HEEE1FA&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,457,848,458)}{\1c&HEADAF9&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,458,848,459)}{\1c&HE6D3F8&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,459,848,460)}{\1c&HE2CBF7&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,460,848,461)}{\1c&HDEC4F6&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,461,848,462)}{\1c&HD9BDF5&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,462,848,463)}{\1c&HD5B6F4&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,463,848,464)}{\1c&HD1AEF3&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,464,848,465)}{\1c&HCDA7F2&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,465,848,466)}{\1c&HC9A0F1&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,466,848,467)}{\1c&HC598F0&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,467,848,468)}{\1c&HC191EF&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,468,848,469)}{\1c&HBD8AEE&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 3,0:02:26.56,0:02:28.89,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,469,848,470)}{\1c&HB983ED&}相似人的距离
Dialogue: 2,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,26,848,27)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,27,848,28)}{\1c&HFBF8FE&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,28,848,29)}{\1c&HF7F1FD&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,29,848,30)}{\1c&HF3EBFC&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,30,848,31)}{\1c&HF0E4FB&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,31,848,32)}{\1c&HECDEFA&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,32,848,33)}{\1c&HE8D7F9&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,33,848,34)}{\1c&HE5D1F8&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,34,848,35)}{\1c&HE1CAF7&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,35,848,36)}{\1c&HDDC4F6&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,36,848,37)}{\1c&HDABDF5&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,37,848,38)}{\1c&HD6B7F4&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,38,848,39)}{\1c&HD2B0F3&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,39,848,40)}{\1c&HCFAAF2&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,40,848,41)}{\1c&HCBA3F1&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,41,848,42)}{\1c&HC79DF0&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,42,848,43)}{\1c&HC496EF&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,43,848,44)}{\1c&HC090EE&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,44,848,45)}{\1c&HBC89ED&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.94,0:23:49.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,45,848,46)}{\1c&HB983ED&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.90,0:00:45.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.46,0:00:49.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.08,0:00:54.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.48,0:01:00.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこの迷えるオマエ 惰性感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.06,0:01:06.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すがるワラを探して　他力本願バンザイ？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.43,0:01:10.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここに来ただけ（相当）お利口ねボウヤ（上等）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.92,0:01:16.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞いてあげるわ　早くゲロっていっそGo to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.14,0:01:19.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.78,0:01:21.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神の仕事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.76,0:01:24.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.11,0:01:28.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試行錯誤のevery day　いくら足騒いたトコで無駄
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.80,0:01:33.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神に従ってれば　万事OKでしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.55,0:01:35.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身の程わきまえて、さあ（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.84,0:01:38.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆らうヤツらはお仕置きよ（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.12,0:01:42.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果主義更生させなくちゃGo to Hell→Deaaaath!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.91,0:01:51.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絶対的で革新的な　チカラ見せつけてあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.42,0:01:55.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと存在感異常のイカレタ趣味くらいノープロブレム
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.04,0:02:00.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこにひざまずいて教えを請いなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.00,0:02:04.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生観変えるような出会いになるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.18,0:02:10.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなビビってないで　全部あずけりゃいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.27,0:02:12.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.90,0:00:45.36,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.46,0:00:49.92,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.08,0:00:54.60,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.48,0:01:00.87,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里迷惘着的你　惰性感满载的face
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.06,0:01:06.24,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找着救命稻草 坐享其成万岁？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.43,0:01:10.89,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够到达这里（相当）真聪明啊男孩（很好）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.92,0:01:16.91,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就听你说说 快点全说出来干脆Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.14,0:01:19.59,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.78,0:01:21.75,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.76,0:01:24.08,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.11,0:01:28.61,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不断摸索的every day 不管怎么挣扎都是没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.80,0:01:33.39,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺从神明的话 就万事OK了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.55,0:01:35.83,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看清自己的斤两（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.84,0:01:38.11,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反抗的家伙都要调教哦（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.12,0:01:42.82,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须让结果注意复兴Go to Hell→Deaaaath!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.91,0:01:51.24,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你见识见识绝对的革新的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.42,0:01:55.88,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着稍微存在感异常的奇怪兴趣而已No problem
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.04,0:02:00.84,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪在那里请求我的教导吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.00,0:02:04.99,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为会成为改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.18,0:02:10.10,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那么害怕 全部交给我就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.27,0:02:12.78,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要H!E!L!P!你！

Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.50,0:22:07.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.75,0:22:10.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.91,0:22:13.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.53,0:22:15.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.67,0:22:20.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.03,0:22:21.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.35,0:22:22.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.80,0:22:23.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.10,0:22:26.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.75,0:22:29.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.37,0:22:31.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.56,0:22:31.90,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.96,0:22:33.19,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.38,0:22:34.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.64,0:22:35.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.03,0:22:37.09,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.28,0:22:38.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋には緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.64,0:22:39.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.02,0:22:41.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.18,0:22:44.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.69,0:22:48.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.65,0:22:54.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.20,0:22:59.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.30,0:23:01.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.87,0:23:04.55,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.77,0:23:06.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.13,0:23:09.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ 胸、痛い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.84,0:23:15.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちがとまらない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.50,0:23:17.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.69,0:23:20.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.76,0:23:23.31,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.47,0:23:25.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.57,0:23:29.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.93,0:23:32.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.50,0:22:07.58,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.75,0:22:10.72,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成就算是硬来？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.91,0:22:13.37,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气吐气之后是告白的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.53,0:22:15.49,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法安下心来的我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.67,0:22:20.03,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是特别的这是特别的…万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.03,0:22:21.29,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.35,0:22:22.63,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想靠的太近…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.80,0:22:23.91,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者是…可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.10,0:22:26.56,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近又远离 背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.75,0:22:29.17,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和欢笑可能是很相似的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.37,0:22:31.42,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想接近你喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.56,0:22:31.90,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.96,0:22:33.19,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我哪边都不擅长
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.38,0:22:34.48,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单行道是单方面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.64,0:22:35.84,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商谈枪弹 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.03,0:22:37.09,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.28,0:22:38.47,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是爱还是恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.64,0:22:39.83,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情文物让她们对立吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.02,0:22:41.97,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.18,0:22:44.47,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想看到梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.69,0:22:48.43,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.65,0:22:54.40,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我眼中你闪耀着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.20,0:22:59.29,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？对了…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.30,0:23:01.69,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要好好决定好哦 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.87,0:23:04.55,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席位只有一个所以就算硬来！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.77,0:23:06.93,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.13,0:23:09.64,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成 胸口 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.84,0:23:15.28,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之感情停不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.50,0:23:17.51,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好决定啊 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.69,0:23:20.61,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也想要挑战一下 想要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.76,0:23:23.31,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这次是承诺的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.47,0:23:25.38,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让你让我安心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.57,0:23:29.92,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为特别你是特别的…按下去！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.93,0:23:32.66,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!


