[Script Info]
Title:清雨
Original Script:清雨
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.8,0.4,2,10,10,8,134
Style: staff,黑体,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正大黑简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: a,方正准圆_GBK,31,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF640064,0,0,0,0,100,105,1,0.00,1,0,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00860BF4,&H64860BF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,128
Style: OPCH,华康圆体W5(P),24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0000,&H64FF0000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00F7EEFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0080,&H00640064,-1,0,0,0,100,105,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.93,0:00:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天终于樱守祭要开幕了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.47,0:00:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵守规定
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.95,0:00:10.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一个自豪的樱守高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.61,0:00:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受节日吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.27,0:00:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.55,0:00:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.89,0:00:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学好像确实是第二义工社的社员吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.65,0:00:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们社要推出些什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.99,0:00:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了提高社团人气 我们打算搞麻烦解决办事处
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.07,0:00:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.53,0:00:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,班长也有什么想要解决的事的话尽管吩咐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.31,0:00:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？我并没有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.09,0:00:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且作为执行委员已经很忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.37,0:00:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失陪了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.64,0:00:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 既然没有问题也没必要扯进去嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.90,0:02:34.85,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由极影字幕社(bbs.ktxp.com)制作 仅供交流试看 喜爱本作品请支持Z版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.90,0:02:34.85,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译: 神代辰弥  雲端の翼   特效: W-BOY   后期: 清雨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.87,0:03:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.91,0:03:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.86,0:03:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 结野呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.74,0:03:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发短信来说是会晚来
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.16,0:03:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没法和你取得联系她很担心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.41,0:03:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 忘记带手机了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.79,0:03:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是能帮忙解决麻烦的是这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.94,0:03:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.71,0:03:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊嘞 这不是砂户君吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.60,0:03:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识这人？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.41,0:03:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我在打工的那个便利店的店长
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.61,0:03:37.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的恋人琉璃琉璃失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.03,0:03:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋人失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.83,0:03:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是重大事件呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.53,0:03:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微没盯着那么一小会儿 就失踪了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.77,0:03:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋人？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.09,0:03:49.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是前阵子看到的等身大的抱枕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.08,0:03:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说啥呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.83,0:03:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉璃琉璃才不是什么抱枕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.99,0:03:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我最重要的恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.17,0:03:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉璃琉璃
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.87,0:04:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店长只对二次元感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.17,0:04:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个非常有个性的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.11,0:04:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说这家伙是把抱枕当做恋人的变态吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.89,0:04:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就自己去找吧 呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.67,0:04:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请 猫咪咖啡营业中
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.99,0:04:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请务必光顾
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.89,0:04:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里好想和太郎一起去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.00,0:04:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 在这里不见的啊抱枕…啊不对 琉璃琉璃
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.85,0:04:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是被诱拐了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.47,0:04:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧 大概只是被当做遗失物品了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.77,0:04:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.51,0:04:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了 好想你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.30,0:04:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琉璃琉璃~
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.33,0:04:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 很寂寞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.37,0:04:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会再让你一个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.58,0:04:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.45,0:04:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想作为可疑物品处理掉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.71,0:04:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.50,0:04:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.78,0:05:00.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话跟你说
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.60,0:05:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有事相托第二义工社
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.86,0:05:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎去帮人找丢失物品了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.91,0:05:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.71,0:05:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找他
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.54,0:05:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 你看下这个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.35,0:05:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送到樱守祭执行委员会的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.58,0:05:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是恐吓信
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.89,0:05:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐吓信？！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.32,0:05:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被诅咒的世界 因为重大的罪孽而招来灾难
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.05,0:05:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为理所当然的报应 接受惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.96,0:05:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了悄悄的解决这事件
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.80,0:05:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是要我们协助他们找出犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.41,0:05:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 虽然我认为只是个恶作剧而已
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.63,0:05:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才对嘛 这才是我等着的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.81,0:05:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点 快去吧 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.67,0:05:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 等下 到底要去那里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.69,0:05:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么要怎么找出犯人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.21,0:05:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.16,0:05:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微等下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.74,0:06:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发现可疑的人了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.01,0:06:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,57日元…切
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.07,0:06:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.28,0:06:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.85,0:06:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.12,0:06:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你请我吃薄饼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.99,0:06:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.49,0:06:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我去 你这没用的猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.85,0:06:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好~
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.62,0:06:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢光顾
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.62,0:06:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.00,0:06:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.18,0:06:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有破绽
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.20,0:06:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？你干什么呢 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.24,0:06:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 你的是巧克力味啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.00,0:06:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个也不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.94,0:06:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.33,0:06:59.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么想吃的话 请吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.36,0:06:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.74,0:07:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.74,0:07:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.56,0:07:10.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}【校内 巡视中】
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.39,0:07:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.01,0:07:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底去哪里了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.87,0:07:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,章鱼 章鱼 章鱼…章鱼烧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.19,0:07:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好吃 不妙啊 章鱼烧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.73,0:07:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.47,0:07:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我口渴了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.07,0:07:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是我来请客吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.18,0:07:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就由我来请你了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.08,0:07:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.95,0:07:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.18,0:07:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这里的话结野会很高兴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.76,0:08:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.86,0:08:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.38,0:08:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.83,0:08:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.40,0:08:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这里饮料是免费的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.84,0:08:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啦 不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.57,0:08:20.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.92,0:08:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.58,0:08:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这啊 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.74,0:08:29.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去逛逛吧 好不好？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.01,0:08:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美真是的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.90,0:08:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.64,0:08:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.28,0:08:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这种事 你没忘了我们的使命吧 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.68,0:08:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使命？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.91,0:08:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二义工社接受的委托啊 呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.35,0:08:53.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 现在正在校内巡视中
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.43,0:08:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.86,0:08:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是选美开始了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.60,0:09:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 为了创造犯罪的时机
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.55,0:09:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可能是故意把大型活动作为惨剧的舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.66,0:09:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？啊 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.04,0:09:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下去 编号05 辰吉·安东尼特十六世
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.90,0:09:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该和预选对决的你们说拜拜了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.17,0:09:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这樱守祭最美丽的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.50,0:09:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愚民们 全心全意的崇拜我的美貌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.14,0:09:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在干什么呢 那个恶心的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.52,0:09:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下去是编号06 静香 请登台
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.95,0:09:45.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 有燃起来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.89,0:09:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是静香
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.97,0:09:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.87,0:09:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.83,0:09:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静香会努力优胜的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.81,0:09:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选美的优胜奖品是什么来着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.59,0:10:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是双人温泉旅行券
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.72,0:10:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 姐姐是认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.56,0:10:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家不要被她给骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.12,0:10:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音是…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.32,0:10:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.60,0:10:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静香看起来是这么年轻 但却是确确实实的大学生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.34,0:10:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是樱守高中的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.23,0:10:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 那个老太婆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.42,0:10:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然在这里爆我料
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.57,0:10:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是完全的舞弊行为
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.76,0:10:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请马上勒令其退场
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.20,0:10:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 由我优胜的有力竞争者 我是智子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.13,0:10:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.70,0:10:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啊 我是正正的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.74,0:10:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水灵灵的女高中生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.79,0:10:47.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么啊 那个大妈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.55,0:10:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说自己是女高中生 她正常吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.85,0:11:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 恐吓信
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.37,0:11:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这还真不太平呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.57,0:11:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过不知道怎么才能找到犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.13,0:11:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 被诅咒的学生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.84,0:11:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉有吓唬人的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.03,0:11:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为只是喜欢这种事的人的恶作剧而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.86,0:11:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到吓人 发明部的鬼屋听说弄的蛮不错哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.26,0:11:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼屋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.93,0:11:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 好棒 最高啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.14,0:11:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 再稍微脱掉点外套
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.09,0:11:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发明部吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.26,0:11:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.08,0:11:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.86,0:11:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被治愈了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.11,0:11:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.23,0:11:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电话也打不通
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.60,0:11:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.72,0:11:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这里吧 传说中的口碑很好的鬼屋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.73,0:11:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面又黑 就算发出悲鸣也没什么奇怪的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.01,0:11:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为惨剧的舞台真是最适合了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.25,0:12:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.17,0:12:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.11,0:12:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到发明部的鬼屋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.47,0:12:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集诺亚全部精髓的而制造的杰作
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.99,0:12:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请往这边走
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.70,0:12:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在进门前就吓成这样了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.26,0:12:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.36,0:12:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 别这么推啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.40,0:12:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当真实啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.26,0:12:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是发明部
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.95,0:12:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.86,0:12:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅蠛蝶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.68,0:12:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个不折不扣的废柴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.51,0:12:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么学姐就这么淡定？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.73,0:12:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是相当害怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.56,0:12:53.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边好像有什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.49,0:12:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你没办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.63,0:12:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等一下 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.19,0:13:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别走的那么快啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.03,0:13:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 这个家伙是猫妖吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.78,0:13:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过倒还很可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.15,0:13:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫…猫…猫…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.41,0:13:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.84,0:13:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌猫啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.41,0:13:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来害怕猫啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.83,0:13:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了 到一边去啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.39,0:13:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以那个时候…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.26,0:13:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 一边凉快去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.28,0:13:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 已经没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.22,0:13:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫已经消失不见了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.66,0:13:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.71,0:13:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猫…猫…好害怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.55,0:13:48.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了 请不要再哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.31,0:13:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.36,0:13:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子很害怕那种地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.66,0:13:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.95,0:13:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么去其他地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.68,0:13:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.59,0:14:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.86,0:14:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.41,0:14:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手…给你牵
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.89,0:14:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.73,0:14:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是害怕妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.77,0:14:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我来牵着你的手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.62,0:14:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.58,0:14:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真拿你没办法呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.77,0:14:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快点伸手
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.49,0:14:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.14,0:14:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.13,0:14:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎你 被诅咒的学生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.43,0:15:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是什么人？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.37,0:15:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,委员长？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.05,0:15:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里我可不是什么班长
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.45,0:15:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.76,0:15:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是MFC的会长
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.38,0:15:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綾瀬川霧乃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.21,0:15:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里的各位都是同志
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.86,0:15:20.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MFC？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.66,0:15:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MFC是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.05,0:15:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人的FAN CLUB的略称
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.84,0:15:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…这是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.51,0:15:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年被选为樱守小姐的美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.75,0:15:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于她美貌的尊敬 崇拜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.43,0:15:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于蔑视她的人给予惩罚的组织
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.40,0:15:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惩罚…？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.52,0:15:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说那封恐吓信是班长你…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.61,0:15:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把猪太郎绑到哪里去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.65,0:15:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么我完全不懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.99,0:15:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不快点回答我的话就把你吊在屋顶上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.07,0:15:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耸那…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.50,0:16:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.63,0:16:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.29,0:16:06.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.22,0:16:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开门见山地问你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.78,0:16:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学你和美绪大人是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.26,0:16:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恋人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.39,0:16:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.12,0:16:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾经收到过情报说美绪大人和你去约会过
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.70,0:16:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约会？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.88,0:16:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.45,0:16:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且在今天的樱守祭也…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.07,0:16:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为班长你转交过来的恐吓信…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.02,0:16:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才会有那样的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.61,0:16:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你和美绪大人不是恋人是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.35,0:16:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.06,0:16:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听你这么一说我就放心了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.63,0:16:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被诅咒的学生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.62,0:16:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受报应吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.79,0:17:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是恋人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.90,0:17:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然会很悲伤但是还是会原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.20,0:17:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人的笑脸 还是哭泣的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.75,0:17:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是生气的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.65,0:17:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算全部占有 那也是理所当然的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.75,0:17:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你不过就是个社团中的后辈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.46,0:17:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是却一个人霸占着美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.75,0:17:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太不像话了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.88,0:17:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碍眼的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.04,0:17:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连美绪大人鞋底粘着的口香糖都不如的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.58,0:17:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却和美绪大人一起在樱守祭上游玩
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.19,0:17:34.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.31,0:17:37.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.06,0:17:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了 如果吃这招的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.28,0:17:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定 绝对 确实 无误地会
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.91,0:17:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M全开的…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.39,0:17:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 这是惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.10,0:17:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 学姐可不希望这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.57,0:17:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又知道美绪大人些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.08,0:17:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就凭你这个不是恋人的你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.48,0:17:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐只是想帮助别人实现愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.79,0:18:00.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是什么崇拜 尊敬
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.20,0:18:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.06,0:18:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.83,0:18:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.85,0:18:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.02,0:18:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.60,0:18:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.95,0:18:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绑了猪太郎打算做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.10,0:18:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目的又是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.82,0:18:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 我是美绪大人FAN CLUB的会长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.27,0:18:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綾瀬川霧乃
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.05,0:18:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？ 美绪大人FAN CLUB？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.14,0:18:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们称颂美绪大人的美丽
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.44,0:18:37.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尊敬石动美绪大人 并且崇拜着
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.39,0:18:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.25,0:18:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要什么尊敬 崇拜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.32,0:18:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美…美绪大人！？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.77,0:18:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人和我们说话了…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.87,0:18:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多么的飒爽英姿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.91,0:18:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然能够距离这么近…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.85,0:18:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算是啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.35,0:18:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 你是来救我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.94,0:19:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得把手给你牵的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.17,0:19:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要随随便便就松手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.22,0:19:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 懂了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.33,0:19:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.49,0:19:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人 给您添麻烦了真是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.58,0:19:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MFC就此解散
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.22,0:19:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.75,0:19:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的使命已经达成
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.78,0:19:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 MFC能够到今天真是感谢各位了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.88,0:19:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.74,0:19:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会长…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.01,0:19:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才应该感谢你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.33,0:19:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是非常的开心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.08,0:19:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,MFC万岁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.17,0:19:42.82,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}万岁…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.01,0:19:39.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的原因吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.81,0:19:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像打下圆场更好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.22,0:19:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.22,0:19:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们要是再做奇怪的事情可别怪我不客气了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.32,0:19:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得令
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.57,0:19:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有想达成的事情的话就来第二义工社吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.00,0:19:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荣幸之至
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.89,0:19:56.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 解散
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.23,0:19:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.51,0:20:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年的樱守小姐是学姐摘得桂冠吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.09,0:20:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.89,0:20:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,获胜奖品是双人温泉旅行券是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.97,0:20:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…学姐和谁一起去的？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.48,0:20:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 很在意吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.05,0:20:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…也不是那个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.22,0:20:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是和满姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.07,0:20:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要和谁一起去是我的自由吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.21,0:20:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.38,0:20:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.76,0:20:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 算了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.07,0:20:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今 今天谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.30,0:20:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.13,0:20:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.41,0:21:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.91,0:21:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子！？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.71,0:21:09.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人好开心的样子…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.61,0:21:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎和美绪今天两个人一直都在一起的是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.49,0:21:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 两个人牵着手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.96,0:21:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.29,0:21:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是的 那是猪太郎他…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.14,0:21:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.95,0:21:25.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也想和太郎牵着手一起游玩的说
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.36,0:21:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.19,0:21:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 不要碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.17,0:21:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要说也是你摸我的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.85,0:21:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.60,0:21:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要在这里发动超M啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.90,0:21:46.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.64,0:21:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话不就把超M暴露了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.30,0:21:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把这家伙弄气绝了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.07,0:21:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子也来帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.63,0:21:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是很明白 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.72,0:21:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人真可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.63,0:22:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在真是无上的幸福啊~
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.96,0:23:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不可思议呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.57,0:23:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么对于砂户君来说就不如动的其中的好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.45,0:23:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是人生的损失啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.55,0:23:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二次元的妹子们明明是那么有魅力的说
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.81,0:23:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 妹子绝对是二次元的好是吧
Dialogue: 2,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 1,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,452,848,453)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,453,848,454)}{\1c&HFAF7FD&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,454,848,455)}{\1c&HF6F0FC&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,455,848,456)}{\1c&HF2E9FB&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,456,848,457)}{\1c&HEEE1FA&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,457,848,458)}{\1c&HEADAF9&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,458,848,459)}{\1c&HE6D3F8&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,459,848,460)}{\1c&HE2CBF7&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,460,848,461)}{\1c&HDEC4F6&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,461,848,462)}{\1c&HD9BDF5&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,462,848,463)}{\1c&HD5B6F4&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,463,848,464)}{\1c&HD1AEF3&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,464,848,465)}{\1c&HCDA7F2&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,465,848,466)}{\1c&HC9A0F1&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,466,848,467)}{\1c&HC598F0&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,467,848,468)}{\1c&HC191EF&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,468,848,469)}{\1c&HBD8AEE&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 3,0:02:37.54,0:02:39.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,469,848,470)}{\1c&HB983ED&}MFC的华丽的阴谋
Dialogue: 2,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,26,848,27)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,27,848,28)}{\1c&HFBF8FE&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,28,848,29)}{\1c&HF7F1FD&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,29,848,30)}{\1c&HF3EBFC&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,30,848,31)}{\1c&HF0E4FB&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,31,848,32)}{\1c&HECDEFA&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,32,848,33)}{\1c&HE8D7F9&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,33,848,34)}{\1c&HE5D1F8&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,34,848,35)}{\1c&HE1CAF7&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,35,848,36)}{\1c&HDDC4F6&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,36,848,37)}{\1c&HDABDF5&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,37,848,38)}{\1c&HD6B7F4&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,38,848,39)}{\1c&HD2B0F3&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,39,848,40)}{\1c&HCFAAF2&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,40,848,41)}{\1c&HCBA3F1&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,41,848,42)}{\1c&HC79DF0&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,42,848,43)}{\1c&HC496EF&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,43,848,44)}{\1c&HC090EE&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,44,848,45)}{\1c&HBC89ED&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.87,0:23:49.84,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,45,848,46)}{\1c&HB983ED&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.99,0:00:56.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.58,0:01:01.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.19,0:01:05.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.66,0:01:12.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこの迷えるオマエ　悲状感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.28,0:01:17.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーガないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.47,0:01:21.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.11,0:01:27.45,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.25,0:01:30.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.84,0:01:32.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.90,0:01:35.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.31,0:01:39.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.93,0:01:44.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.63,0:01:46.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.96,0:01:49.19,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.20,0:01:53.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to ヘ·ブン
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.09,0:01:58.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.65,0:02:02.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.56,0:02:06.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.19,0:02:11.80,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.99,0:02:16.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.33,0:02:21.26,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.43,0:02:23.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.99,0:00:56.52,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.58,0:01:01.03,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.19,0:01:05.64,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.66,0:01:12.10,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里迷惘着的你 满是悲壮感的face
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.28,0:01:17.29,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢弃救命稻草吧 这也是没办法的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.47,0:01:21.95,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命运现在也（迷走）在坏心眼（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.11,0:01:27.45,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少让我 成为你的同伴为你做些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.25,0:01:30.64,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.84,0:01:32.88,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.90,0:01:35.15,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.31,0:01:39.71,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧绷的神经没有用 破坏掉的话就什么都没了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.93,0:01:44.61,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顽固的DNA 勉强是禁止的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.63,0:01:46.95,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强制停止5秒前（近在咫尺）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.96,0:01:49.19,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像要重生一样的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.19,0:01:53.87,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实主义复活的话Go to天堂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.09,0:01:58.42,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说可否 在那双手这双手中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.65,0:02:02.37,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在马上给你修正
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.56,0:02:06.98,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点存在感但还未陷入爱河
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.19,0:02:11.80,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摆出一副可怜的表情没法让人放着不管
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.99,0:02:16.12,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为想要改变人生观一样的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.33,0:02:21.26,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就这样吧 放任逐流就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.43,0:02:23.78,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要H!E!L!P!你！

Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.70,0:22:07.78,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.95,0:22:10.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.11,0:22:13.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.73,0:22:15.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.87,0:22:20.23,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.23,0:22:21.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.55,0:22:22.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.00,0:22:24.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.30,0:22:26.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.95,0:22:29.37,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.57,0:22:31.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.76,0:22:32.10,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.16,0:22:33.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.58,0:22:34.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.84,0:22:36.04,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.23,0:22:37.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.48,0:22:38.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋には緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.84,0:22:40.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.22,0:22:42.17,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.38,0:22:44.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.89,0:22:48.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.85,0:22:54.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.40,0:22:59.49,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.50,0:23:01.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.07,0:23:04.75,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.97,0:23:07.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.33,0:23:09.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ 胸、痛い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.04,0:23:15.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちがとまらない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.70,0:23:17.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.89,0:23:20.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.96,0:23:23.51,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.67,0:23:25.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.77,0:23:30.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.13,0:23:32.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.70,0:22:07.78,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.95,0:22:10.92,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成就算是硬来？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.11,0:22:13.57,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气吐气之后是告白的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.73,0:22:15.69,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法安下心来的我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.87,0:22:20.23,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是特别的这是特别的…万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.23,0:22:21.49,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.55,0:22:22.83,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想靠的太近…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.00,0:22:24.11,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者是…可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.30,0:22:26.76,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近又远离 背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.95,0:22:29.37,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和欢笑可能是很相似的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.57,0:22:31.62,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想接近你喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.76,0:22:32.10,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.16,0:22:33.39,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我哪边都不擅长
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.58,0:22:34.68,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单行道是单方面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.84,0:22:36.04,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商谈枪弹 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.23,0:22:37.29,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.48,0:22:38.67,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是爱还是恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.84,0:22:40.03,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情文物让她们对立吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.22,0:22:42.17,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.38,0:22:44.67,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想看到梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.89,0:22:48.63,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.85,0:22:54.60,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我眼中你闪耀着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.40,0:22:59.49,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？对了…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.50,0:23:01.89,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要好好决定好哦 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.07,0:23:04.75,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席位只有一个所以就算硬来！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.97,0:23:07.13,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.33,0:23:09.84,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成 胸口 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.04,0:23:15.48,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之感情停不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.70,0:23:17.71,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好决定啊 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.89,0:23:20.81,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也想要挑战一下 想要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.96,0:23:23.51,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这次是承诺的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.67,0:23:25.58,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让你让我安心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.77,0:23:30.12,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为特别你是特别的…按下去！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.13,0:23:32.86,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!


