[Script Info]
Title:清雨
Original Script:清雨
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.8,0.4,2,10,10,8,134
Style: staff,黑体,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正大黑简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: a,方正准圆_GBK,31,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF640064,0,0,0,0,100,105,1,0.00,1,0,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00860BF4,&H64860BF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,128
Style: OPCH,华康圆体W5(P),24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0000,&H64FF0000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00F7EEFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0080,&H00640064,-1,0,0,0,100,105,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.63,0:00:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这蠢狗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.87,0:00:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 一大清早的别这么没口德啊 石动学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.62,0:00:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.89,0:00:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 刚才的是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.99,0:00:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像…像你这样的劣等狗竟敢俯视我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.26,0:00:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狗就该像狗那样 快点给我趴地上去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.82,0:00:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结…结野？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.22,0:00:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你快给我趴下啊 你这变态猪狗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.93,0:00:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.55,0:00:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.89,0:00:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫…叫我岚子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.85,0:00:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子…岚子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被叫了 第一次被叫岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.58,0:00:59.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的吧 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.49,0:01:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结…岚子大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.08,0:01:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛随随便便叫我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.19,0:01:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宠物就应该像个宠物样 乖乖听主人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.52,0:01:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宠…宠物 啊 再多说一点吧 多贬低我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.11,0:01:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调教
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.62,0:01:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今…今天开始好好调教调教你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.47,0:01:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做好觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.91,0:03:01.91,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由极影字幕社(bbs.ktxp.com)制作 仅供交流试看 喜爱本作品请支持Z版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.91,0:03:01.91,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译: 神代辰弥  雲端の翼   特效: W-BOY   后期: 清雨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.25,0:03:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子会做这种事？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.09,0:03:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是石动学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.82,0:03:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是那样的话就不会烦恼了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.24,0:03:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是做了什么让结野生气的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.26,0:03:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没什么头绪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.25,0:03:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.96,0:03:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.24,0:03:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有…有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.68,0:03:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 做了便当
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.69,0:03:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.42,0:03:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你吃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.48,0:03:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.25,0:03:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么难得特地做了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.17,0:03:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你的便当哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.49,0:03:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,板砖？！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.81,0:03:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是纺锤形面包
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.54,0:03:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对啊 怎么看都是板砖嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.12,0:03:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子大人为了我做了面包
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.43,0:03:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能不吃啊 不能不吃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.87,0:03:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做这种事的话 肯定会磕掉牙的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.94,0:03:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 只是有点硬而已
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.34,0:04:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点给我嗑下去 来有牛奶哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.35,0:04:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奶瓶？！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.49,0:04:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个不行的啊 不行的 不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.65,0:04:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的啦 我帮你啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.51,0:04:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好痛苦…感觉…渐渐变爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.41,0:04:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.33,0:04:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然我…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.34,0:04:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.07,0:04:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天晓得
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.05,0:04:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 借一步说话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.54,0:04:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要来这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.15,0:04:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子会做这种事 看来是非常生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.12,0:04:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就…就算你这么说 我…也不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.29,0:04:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别给我装傻
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.92,0:04:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,间宫流按摩审问术
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.50,0:04:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的 我什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.46,0:04:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能只是在你不经意间伤害了岚子也说不定
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.82,0:05:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点自觉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.00,0:05:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子真是的啦 为什么为了这种家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.86,0:05:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别就这样丢下我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.04,0:05:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别丢我一个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.43,0:05:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户同学 为什么你会在女厕所里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.72,0:05:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这是因为 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.93,0:05:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然你不配作为美绪大人的拍档呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.68,0:05:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说了这是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.00,0:05:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,端庄豪雅 庄严美丽 宇宙级的贵族美少女
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.44,0:05:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辰吉·安东尼特十六世大驾光临
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.43,0:05:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么看都是东洋人嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.55,0:05:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你久等了 我的侍从
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.31,0:05:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,侍从？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.20,0:05:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么去假面舞道会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.67,0:05:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵安 一般臣民
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.15,0:05:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得救了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.61,0:05:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不回来就料到了 还真是让人操劳的劣等人种呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.55,0:05:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了 不过为什么是女装
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.18,0:06:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以男生的样子进不去那里嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.15,0:06:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的圆周率的定义的复习
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.08,0:06:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一个弧的圆周率很相近
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.98,0:06:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底做了什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.22,0:06:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好慢啊 我一个人好闲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.60,0:06:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我闲的发慌 你以为你是谁啊 你这蠢猪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.64,0:06:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像让你久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.89,0:06:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…等什么的 怎么可能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.13,0:06:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.48,0:06:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.09,0:06:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会等你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.74,0:06:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是在找你茬而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.19,0:06:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近看到你就一阵不爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.99,0:06:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.41,0:06:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.33,0:06:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对结野说了什么吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.88,0:06:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.95,0:06:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的样子好奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.79,0:06:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我没什么头绪 难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.85,0:06:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这可恶的蠢猪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.35,0:06:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在那一个人自言自语个什么劲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.94,0:06:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这大变态
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.40,0:06:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更加 更加 稳一点
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.20,0:07:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让人火大
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.53,0:07:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你是需要更加认真的调教呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.17,0:07:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经很认真了 已经是非常认真了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.49,0:07:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.84,0:07:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 稍微调教一下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.95,0:07:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 这只是开胃菜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.89,0:07:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主菜才刚刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.74,0:07:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好期待啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.72,0:07:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然也有点心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.67,0:07:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主菜 点心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.98,0:07:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 赢不过的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.44,0:07:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以现在的我根本就…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.64,0:07:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.35,0:07:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.57,0:07:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.53,0:07:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我稍微去修行一下 学校暂时请一段时间假
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.97,0:07:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以社团活动也无法来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.89,0:07:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修行？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.19,0:07:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么喵？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.99,0:07:47.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提到秋天当然就是黄昏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.73,0:07:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夕阳照下 山的山涧…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.08,0:07:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野 今天也是请假吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.47,0:08:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.18,0:08:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在泄什么气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.88,0:08:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你认真起来的程度
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.51,0:08:18.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点站起来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.05,0:08:25.88,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9}来自 太郎\N没事吧？结野\N今天你也缺席了啊\N想知道你现在怎么样了 身体…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.14,0:08:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.32,0:08:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我决定了 要努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.84,0:08:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我是结野
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.09,0:08:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.39,0:08:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我不能接电话 如果您有事请在听到哔——…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.63,0:08:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在烦恼着啊 砂户君
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.63,0:08:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子的态度突然间变了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.24,0:08:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是搞不懂啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.07,0:08:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竖旗了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.80,0:09:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.44,0:09:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你选错了选项可不行哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.64,0:09:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好感度会变的 线路也会变的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.76,0:09:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.58,0:09:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家不用担心 都会打出best ending的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.74,0:09:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经第三天了 岚子到底在哪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.15,0:09:16.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.97,0:09:18.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都是猪太郎的错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.37,0:09:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太强词夺理了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.76,0:09:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我负起责任来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.21,0:09:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之先抽个五万次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.63,0:09:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是治疗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.02,0:09:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那就算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.89,0:09:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.29,0:09:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.74,0:09:38.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.83,0:09:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连间宫同学也…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.04,0:09:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 都没事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.89,0:09:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天来你都去干什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.03,0:09:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.98,0:09:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.26,0:09:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一决胜负吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.35,0:09:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决胜负？决什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.75,0:09:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.65,0:09:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁才是真正的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.12,0:10:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的超S
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.65,0:10:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决定超S少女的胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.06,0:10:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的…啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.79,0:10:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超S少女
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.79,0:10:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全不理解意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.16,0:10:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是在绕着弯子说我根本不是你的对手吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.57,0:10:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.30,0:10:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须要成为超越美绪的S少女
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.18,0:10:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以请跟我对决吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.46,0:10:40.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么要超越我…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.43,0:10:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不是什么超S少女
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.45,0:10:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 这气氛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.19,0:10:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没自觉吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.70,0:10:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在好好调教你 你这蠢猪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.11,0:10:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有错 超S少女 超S
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.80,0:11:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不跟我对决的话我就退出第二义工社
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.09,0:11:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 岚子 你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.17,0:11:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.86,0:11:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道了些什么的话就告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.56,0:11:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经搞不清什么跟什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.08,0:11:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这没法从我这里说出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.98,0:11:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特别是砂户太郎 对你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.19,0:11:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪 岚子都说到这份上了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.66,0:11:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就跟她对决吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.21,0:11:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.16,0:11:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子是认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.97,0:11:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去就要退出社团了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.45,0:11:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 绝对不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.71,0:11:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果美绪赢了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.71,0:11:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就给太郎一天自由的权利
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.49,0:11:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.22,0:11:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.05,0:11:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管做什么都是自由的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.45,0:11:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如说约会什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.47,0:11:43.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎么找茬都可以咯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.52,0:11:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由 比如说约会什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.93,0:11:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 两位
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.45,0:11:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 既然是这样的话我就接受这场对决了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.53,0:11:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.86,0:11:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无视我的意志吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.55,0:11:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相对的 不管是什么对决我都不会手软哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.47,0:12:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正合我意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.49,0:12:08.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.58,0:12:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奖品给我闭嘴！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.27,0:12:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对决的方式 已经写在里面的卡片上了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.96,0:12:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先赢得两局的人获胜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.24,0:12:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何评定胜负呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.72,0:12:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以砂户太郎的兴奋状态来判断吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.28,0:12:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来抽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.54,0:12:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦…好的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.83,0:12:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超S COSPLAY
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.72,0:12:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通过COS能够使你超M激发出来的就算赢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.98,0:12:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑到岚子的男性恐怖症
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.56,0:12:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,触碰身体的行为是禁止的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.87,0:12:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个超级变态
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.85,0:12:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被捕了！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.07,0:12:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错哦 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.43,0:12:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想被逮捕哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.38,0:12:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子 我已经没有什么能够教你了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.70,0:12:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信你自己
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.14,0:12:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甩什么尾巴啊 你这个猪头狗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.78,0:13:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心我把你做成猪肉饭团
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.44,0:13:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是何等的女王啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.18,0:13:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大分叉烧肉 投入决定
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.06,0:13:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,荣幸之至
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.42,0:13:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定岚子要胜了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.63,0:13:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请忏悔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.57,0:13:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忏悔？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.37,0:13:33.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.98,0:13:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.10,0:13:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是如果忏悔的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.25,0:13:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人作呕的你也会被宽恕的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.81,0:13:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿门
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.52,0:13:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人 请原谅我…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.45,0:13:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.78,0:13:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个大头鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.19,0:13:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算全世界原谅你我也不会原谅你的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.88,0:13:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此恶心的生物在面前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.81,0:13:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能笑得出来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.31,0:13:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我下地狱去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.83,0:14:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论转世一百回你还是头猪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.56,0:14:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神圣的修女对我用污蔑的言语…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.36,0:14:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来净化你那肮脏的脸吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.69,0:14:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把脸凑过来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.39,0:14:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情地来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.14,0:14:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是右边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.51,0:14:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是左边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.61,0:14:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是左边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.52,0:14:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,期待着会打过来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.64,0:14:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太自负了你这个可怜的死猪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.41,0:14:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.35,0:14:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.10,0:14:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜者 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.66,0:14:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.49,0:14:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.93,0:14:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子的超S打扮应该是超完美的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.92,0:14:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然确实不错
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.11,0:14:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那终归是模仿我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.07,0:14:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永远追赶我的身后吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.32,0:14:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超S无声电影？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.72,0:14:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.02,0:14:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部禁止说话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.17,0:14:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在无声的状态下让砂户太郎触发超M
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.37,0:15:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这要怎么做…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.22,0:15:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是敌人但是做的相当不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.11,0:15:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是吃这一拳的话我会…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.94,0:15:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.10,0:15:29.59,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9}恶心的猪头狗！\N你这个无可救药的变态！\N太变态了？\N让人肃然起敬呢！\N骗你的！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.78,0:15:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.12,0:15:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 用短信的话不会发出声音
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.19,0:15:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是天才
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.38,0:15:45.26,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个猪头狗DOG!\N让你拉着雪橇\N横穿南极！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.72,0:15:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只是文字 但在我的脑袋里充分YY起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.02,0:15:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是多么过分的短信啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.68,0:15:56.46,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9}在南极点作诗一首
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.69,0:15:59.01,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9}猪头狗啊\N风雪交加\N在外狂吠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.97,0:16:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心中开始温暖起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.90,0:16:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜者 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.00,0:16:08.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.62,0:16:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.19,0:16:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从美绪那里夺回一局了 好开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.05,0:16:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知何时已经超越师傅了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.79,0:16:20.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到会用短信这一招呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.90,0:16:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我也没有想到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.02,0:16:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前言撤回 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.24,0:16:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.50,0:16:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然在不知不觉中追上了我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.78,0:16:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是最后的决胜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.81,0:16:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会手下留情的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.48,0:16:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.38,0:16:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道具超S？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.30,0:16:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用在这里的道具让他触发超S
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.15,0:16:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就开始
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.69,0:16:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个死M
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.94,0:16:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人我来踩踏你 感到高兴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.67,0:16:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舒服吗 舒服的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.31,0:17:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个纯种超M变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.88,0:17:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 很舒服吧 是吧 是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.73,0:17:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…那就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.86,0:17:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是熊猫熊猫是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.27,0:17:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好爽 爽到翻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.02,0:17:13.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(猪头狗作文)
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.03,0:17:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪头狗的BU
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.06,0:17:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直截了当的说太恶心了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.09,0:17:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪头狗的TA
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.13,0:17:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的你这张搓脸傻笑个毛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.88,0:17:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪头狗的I
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.83,0:17:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别老是那么得意 你这个超变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.34,0:17:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留恋 太留恋了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.81,0:17:36.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那样也能够兴奋起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.81,0:17:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天的他什么都会出现呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.64,0:17:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 没发呼吸了 很痛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.07,0:17:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太赞了 被压在美绪大人的PP下面
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.19,0:17:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽的不行啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.98,0:17:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不会认输呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.41,0:17:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪头狗的NU
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.41,0:17:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NU？嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.74,0:17:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别黏黏糊糊地过来啊 你这个章鱼！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.14,0:18:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子 这有点不知所云…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.40,0:18:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好舒服哦…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.83,0:18:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你扔到可燃垃圾里去了哦 你这个垃圾猪头
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.42,0:18:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜生狗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.62,0:18:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人狗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.79,0:18:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垃圾狗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.61,0:18:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是很明白 但是对我的心灵是一记直线球啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.82,0:18:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球的渣滓
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.76,0:18:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微生物
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.46,0:18:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态变态
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.71,0:18:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态变态
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.78,0:18:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个超级变态！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.04,0:18:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.68,0:18:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.97,0:18:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 没事吧 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.98,0:18:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.88,0:18:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要全力上了哦 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.37,0:18:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 等一下爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.32,0:18:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.95,0:18:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是你爸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.60,0:18:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧 我像垃圾一样…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.47,0:18:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.87,0:19:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.02,0:19:07.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野…脑袋晕晕乎乎的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.25,0:19:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.07,0:19:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也太夸张了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.40,0:19:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 为什么要做那样的事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.94,0:19:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得不像是你的作风
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.71,0:19:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.21,0:19:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎你在樱守祭上和美绪两个人玩得很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.22,0:19:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.49,0:19:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后夜祭…也在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.09,0:19:33.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想 太郎是不是喜欢像美绪那样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.56,0:19:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为超越美绪的超S
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.94,0:19:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.99,0:19:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看 太郎你不是超M吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.13,0:19:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是喜欢上超S的美绪的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.15,0:19:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超M就会加速 会变得很危险
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.72,0:19:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以想把超M成分给分担一点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.18,0:19:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 比不上美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.38,0:19:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以让由美来帮助我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.64,0:19:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.57,0:20:00.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没想到会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.13,0:20:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不是说喜欢超S的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.40,0:20:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人 那么你和美绪…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.68,0:20:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱守祭上和学姐在一起也只是形势使然
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.71,0:20:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你很担心我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.82,0:20:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你要是变成和石动学姐一样的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.19,0:20:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得会很可惜的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.47,0:20:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.44,0:20:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以变回平常的你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.35,0:20:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 喜欢看到平常的我？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.82,0:20:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我喜欢平常的结野
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.97,0:20:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜 喜 喜 喜欢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.97,0:20:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被说喜欢了 被说喜欢了 被说喜欢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.96,0:20:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.86,0:20:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 既然太郎你这么说了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.84,0:20:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会照办的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.53,0:20:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没事了 回活动室吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.48,0:20:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪说今天可以回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.23,0:20:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是考虑到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.18,0:20:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.89,0:20:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 什么事都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.44,0:20:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.33,0:21:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.02,0:21:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.32,0:21:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.78,0:21:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.32,0:21:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.43,0:21:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结 结野？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.41,0:21:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,su su…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.02,0:21:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.88,0:21:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常害怕男人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.15,0:21:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一拳就飞出去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.06,0:21:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢款待…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.06,0:21:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 我做便当来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.81,0:21:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.74,0:21:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有美绪的那份哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.49,0:21:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢啦 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.56,0:21:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,努力做的 来尝尝看吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.44,0:21:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道又是像石头一样的面包？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.01,0:21:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.88,0:21:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 你说只要保持平常的我就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.77,0:21:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样说的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.24,0:22:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.10,0:23:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真宫流按摩术精髓
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.05,0:23:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时刻磨练你的技艺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.93,0:23:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞬间看透穴位
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.90,0:23:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给予美少女无上的快感
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.55,0:23:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以啊 岚子 让我按摩吧~
Dialogue: 2,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 1,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,452,848,453)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,453,848,454)}{\1c&HFAF7FD&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,454,848,455)}{\1c&HF6F0FC&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,455,848,456)}{\1c&HF2E9FB&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,456,848,457)}{\1c&HEEE1FA&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,457,848,458)}{\1c&HEADAF9&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,458,848,459)}{\1c&HE6D3F8&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,459,848,460)}{\1c&HE2CBF7&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,460,848,461)}{\1c&HDEC4F6&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,461,848,462)}{\1c&HD9BDF5&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,462,848,463)}{\1c&HD5B6F4&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,463,848,464)}{\1c&HD1AEF3&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,464,848,465)}{\1c&HCDA7F2&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,465,848,466)}{\1c&HC9A0F1&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,466,848,467)}{\1c&HC598F0&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,467,848,468)}{\1c&HC191EF&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,468,848,469)}{\1c&HBD8AEE&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 3,0:03:04.64,0:03:06.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,469,848,470)}{\1c&HB983ED&}虐待成性的岚子小姐
Dialogue: 2,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 1,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,26,848,27)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,27,848,28)}{\1c&HFBF8FE&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,28,848,29)}{\1c&HF7F1FD&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,29,848,30)}{\1c&HF3EBFC&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,30,848,31)}{\1c&HF0E4FB&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,31,848,32)}{\1c&HECDEFA&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,32,848,33)}{\1c&HE8D7F9&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,33,848,34)}{\1c&HE5D1F8&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,34,848,35)}{\1c&HE1CAF7&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,35,848,36)}{\1c&HDDC4F6&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,36,848,37)}{\1c&HDABDF5&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,37,848,38)}{\1c&HD6B7F4&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,38,848,39)}{\1c&HD2B0F3&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,39,848,40)}{\1c&HCFAAF2&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,40,848,41)}{\1c&HCBA3F1&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,41,848,42)}{\1c&HC79DF0&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,42,848,43)}{\1c&HC496EF&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,43,848,44)}{\1c&HC090EE&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,44,848,45)}{\1c&HBC89ED&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.16,0:23:51.87,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,45,848,46)}{\1c&HB983ED&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.95,0:01:23.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.54,0:01:27.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.15,0:01:32.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.62,0:01:39.06,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこの迷えるオマエ　悲状感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.24,0:01:44.25,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーガないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.43,0:01:48.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.07,0:01:54.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.21,0:01:57.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.80,0:01:59.84,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.86,0:02:02.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.27,0:02:06.67,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.89,0:02:11.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.59,0:02:13.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.92,0:02:16.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.16,0:02:20.83,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to ヘ·ブン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.05,0:02:25.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.61,0:02:29.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.52,0:02:33.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.15,0:02:38.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.95,0:02:43.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.29,0:02:48.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.39,0:02:50.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.95,0:01:23.48,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.54,0:01:27.99,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.15,0:01:32.60,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.62,0:01:39.06,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里迷惘着的你 满是悲壮感的face
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.24,0:01:44.25,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢弃救命稻草吧 这也是没办法的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.43,0:01:48.91,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命运现在也（迷走）在坏心眼（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.07,0:01:54.41,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少让我 成为你的同伴为你做些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.21,0:01:57.60,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.80,0:01:59.84,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.86,0:02:02.11,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.27,0:02:06.67,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧绷的神经没有用 破坏掉的话就什么都没了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.89,0:02:11.57,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顽固的DNA 勉强是禁止的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.59,0:02:13.91,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强制停止5秒前（近在咫尺）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.92,0:02:16.15,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像要重生一样的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.15,0:02:20.83,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实主义复活的话Go to天堂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.05,0:02:25.38,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说可否 在那双手这双手中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.61,0:02:29.33,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在马上给你修正
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.52,0:02:33.94,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点存在感但还未陷入爱河
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.15,0:02:38.76,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摆出一副可怜的表情没法让人放着不管
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.95,0:02:43.08,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为想要改变人生观一样的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.29,0:02:48.22,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就这样吧 放任逐流就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.39,0:02:50.74,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要H!E!L!P!你！

Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.60,0:22:09.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.85,0:22:12.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.01,0:22:15.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.63,0:22:17.59,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.77,0:22:22.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.13,0:22:23.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.45,0:22:24.73,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.90,0:22:26.01,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.20,0:22:28.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.85,0:22:31.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.47,0:22:33.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.66,0:22:34.00,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.06,0:22:35.29,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.48,0:22:36.58,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.74,0:22:37.94,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.13,0:22:39.19,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.38,0:22:40.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋には緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.74,0:22:41.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.12,0:22:44.07,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.28,0:22:46.57,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.79,0:22:50.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.75,0:22:56.50,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.39,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.40,0:23:03.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.97,0:23:06.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.87,0:23:09.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.23,0:23:11.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ 胸、痛い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.94,0:23:17.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちがとまらない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.60,0:23:19.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.79,0:23:22.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.86,0:23:25.41,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.57,0:23:27.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.67,0:23:32.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.03,0:23:34.76,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.60,0:22:09.68,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.85,0:22:12.82,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成就算是硬来？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.01,0:22:15.47,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气吐气之后是告白的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.63,0:22:17.59,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法安下心来的我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.77,0:22:22.13,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是特别的这是特别的…万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.13,0:22:23.39,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.45,0:22:24.73,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想靠的太近…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.90,0:22:26.01,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者是…可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.20,0:22:28.66,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近又远离 背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.85,0:22:31.27,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和欢笑可能是很相似的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.47,0:22:33.52,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想接近你喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.66,0:22:34.00,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.06,0:22:35.29,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我哪边都不擅长
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.48,0:22:36.58,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单行道是单方面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.74,0:22:37.94,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商谈枪弹 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.13,0:22:39.19,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.38,0:22:40.57,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是爱还是恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.74,0:22:41.93,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情文物让她们对立吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.12,0:22:44.07,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.28,0:22:46.57,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想看到梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.79,0:22:50.53,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.75,0:22:56.50,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我眼中你闪耀着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.30,0:23:01.39,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？对了…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.40,0:23:03.79,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要好好决定好哦 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.97,0:23:06.65,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席位只有一个所以就算硬来！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.87,0:23:09.03,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.23,0:23:11.74,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成 胸口 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.94,0:23:17.38,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之感情停不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.60,0:23:19.61,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好决定啊 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.79,0:23:22.71,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也想要挑战一下 想要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.86,0:23:25.41,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这次是承诺的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.57,0:23:27.48,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让你让我安心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.67,0:23:32.02,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为特别你是特别的…按下去！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.03,0:23:34.76,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!


