[Script Info]
Title:清雨
Original Script:清雨
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.8,0.4,2,10,10,8,134
Style: staff,黑体,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00860BF4,&H64860BF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,128
Style: OPCH,华康圆体W5(P),24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0000,&H64FF0000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正大黑简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.37,0:00:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.54,0:00:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.20,0:00:05.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.73,0:00:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.76,0:00:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 由美 不要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.09,0:00:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要啦 由美真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.68,0:00:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子的身体抱起来真舒服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.81,0:00:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 太郎还看着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.95,0:00:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎？ 之前在电话里提到的狗就是他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.67,0:00:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次见面上来就叫别人狗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.10,0:00:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,间宫由美 是我的好友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.69,0:00:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 好像是从前和辰吉交往过的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.97,0:00:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说是传说中的中学时候的超M大变态砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.56,0:00:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和这种家伙在一起 也就是说那个已经治好了？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.39,0:00:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那个还没好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.29,0:00:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.13,0:00:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在同一个班 而且也是同一个社团的 只是只狗而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.12,0:01:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.13,0:01:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 管你是狗还是别的什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.59,0:01:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别接近岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.02,0:01:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 由美
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.83,0:01:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.68,0:01:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算想接近也没用 岚子要转入我那的女校了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.47,0:01:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.90,0:03:03.78,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由极影字幕社(bbs.ktxp.com)制作 仅供交流试看 喜爱本作品请支持Z版
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.90,0:03:03.78,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译: 神代辰弥  雲端の翼   特效: W-BOY   后期: 清雨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.68,0:03:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好烫 烫烫烫 我很快就能被烤的很好吃了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.09,0:03:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么享受还能算是治疗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.47,0:03:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你难道就不稍微担心点岚子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.03,0:03:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.99,0:03:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子转学了也不要紧吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.51,0:03:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 还以为你稍微有些优点的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.19,0:03:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还稍微有点刮目相看了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.18,0:03:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交换邮箱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.23,0:03:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.00,0:03:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子的事就交给你了 给我好好点干
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.82,0:03:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.58,0:04:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算说是交给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.00,0:04:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从吉冈前辈的那件事之后 我就开始特别害怕男生了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.88,0:04:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擦肩而过的陌生男人 好可怕 怕的不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.10,0:04:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过最痛苦的是学校的大家都变了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.57,0:04:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.07,0:04:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉冈学长谣传我是个淫贱的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.16,0:04:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从那之后大家都对我白眼相对
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.31,0:04:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来过来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.75,0:04:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.00,0:04:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不信任人类吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.98,0:04:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.81,0:04:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.71,0:04:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来接你了哦 一起回家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.69,0:05:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美真是强硬啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.94,0:05:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明天会来看你的社团活动哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.11,0:05:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想见见传说中的美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.40,0:05:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别自说自话决定下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.30,0:05:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事啦没事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.90,0:05:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是美绪？ 太可爱了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.31,0:05:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.80,0:05:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然这么可爱 能让我摸一下吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.61,0:05:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.61,0:05:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你周围怪人真多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.80,0:05:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这是结野的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.98,0:05:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.91,0:05:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子没有错哦 都是因为这个恶心蠢猪在这里啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.68,0:05:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在罗里吧嗦些什么呢 你真让人恶心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.26,0:05:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想给你按摩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.66,0:05:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.16,0:06:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是很硬呢 来做些特别爽的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.67,0:06:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.82,0:06:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 由美
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.77,0:06:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个按摩 不简单呐
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.38,0:06:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美是间宫流按摩的继承人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.28,0:06:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被称为是十年一遇的天才
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.11,0:06:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成那样 就算我也阻止不了了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.59,0:06:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.71,0:06:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.04,0:06:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这人已经没救了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.34,0:06:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很爽吧 非常爽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.28,0:06:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不爽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.38,0:06:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能让你更爽哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.68,0:06:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.85,0:06:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然美少女就是有按摩的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.12,0:06:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎 快来救我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.76,0:07:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我？为什么是我 前辈都说了不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.74,0:07:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别妨碍我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.18,0:07:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样不也好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.19,0:07:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 男生真可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.53,0:07:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的左手 啊 好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.33,0:07:28.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 太郎 我真是的 又…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.99,0:07:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到可爱的女孩就忍不住
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.58,0:07:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不是岚子的朋友 我早缝你个十五针了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.04,0:07:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你到底是来干什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.95,0:07:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子如果转学的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.85,0:07:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也要退出第二义工社 我是想来好好打个招呼的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.72,0:07:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生恐惧症的事就交给我们吧 肯定会治好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.35,0:07:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果留在这里的话 岚子的伤口只会越来越深
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.81,0:08:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且竟然跟这样的变态在一起 开什么玩笑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.68,0:08:06.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为如果转学就全都能解决了？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.57,0:08:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 这样的话对岚子来说也是幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.84,0:08:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.71,0:08:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在这里才能做到的事也是有的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.47,0:08:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.91,0:08:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 只有在这个第二义工社里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.00,0:08:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.31,0:08:39.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.90,0:08:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我选哪边都决定不下来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.70,0:08:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对不起 啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.92,0:09:06.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野无故缺席 还真是少见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.57,0:09:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么在意结野啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.01,0:09:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 不是这样的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.27,0:09:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是感冒了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.87,0:09:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 昨晚回家的时候有看到她哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.91,0:09:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看不出像是身体不好的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.27,0:09:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子到底怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.69,0:09:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您所拨打的电话现在在圈外或者…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.97,0:09:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子真是的 感冒的话我们都能帮她治
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.48,0:09:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用这身打扮吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.14,0:09:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 不行啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.41,0:09:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先从形式上来 这不是很重要的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.16,0:09:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 不觉得奇怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.47,0:09:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想说不合适？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.47,0:10:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在说结野的事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.21,0:10:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试着发过几次短信了 但是完全没有回应
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.10,0:10:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是讨厌你而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.90,0:10:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我也很在意多次打了电话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.35,0:10:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次也没接
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.37,0:10:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满姐也是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.89,0:10:19.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.18,0:10:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再打一次电话试试
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.40,0:10:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您所拨打的电话…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.13,0:10:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来 昨晚回家的时候有看到她哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.94,0:10:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已关机…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.85,0:10:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈 稍微有点在意的事 我去确认下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.27,0:10:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.93,0:10:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的事？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.21,0:10:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 有看到她和一个男的在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.26,0:10:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是中学的时候的高一年的前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.34,0:10:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会记着你的大恩的 辰吉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.76,0:10:50.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该早点反应过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.68,0:10:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野 你在的吧 我打开门咯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.41,0:11:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野 大家很担心你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.16,0:11:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要过来 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.92,0:11:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.53,0:11:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要过来 请不要过来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.92,0:11:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.00,0:11:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 不要再打我了 不要不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.78,0:11:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我啊 太郎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.39,0:11:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要过来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.98,0:11:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.28,0:11:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好咯 把这根棒取回来 去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.57,0:11:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 不好好把棒子捡回来不行哦 惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.10,0:11:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多更多 岚子大人请你更多的鞭挞我这狗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.16,0:11:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,汪汪 我是大人您的狗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.07,0:12:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 原来如此 你是M的大变态呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.17,0:12:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使被女生揍了也不会想揍还的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.96,0:12:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错啊 我是专门被揍的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.02,0:12:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.92,0:12:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.90,0:12:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶然和吉冈学长碰上了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.05,0:12:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他叫住
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.39,0:12:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到家之后又打来了好几次电话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.76,0:12:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了「不要把中学的事情说出来」之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.83,0:12:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很害怕 害怕的不行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.34,0:12:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的做了那么十恶不赦的事情了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.24,0:12:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要遇到这样的事情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.00,0:12:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.52,0:12:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想活下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.79,0:12:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 结野在家里
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.04,0:12:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么回事 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.58,0:13:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你在听吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.59,0:13:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.14,0:13:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是狗之太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.72,0:13:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.27,0:13:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是吉冈吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.05,0:13:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.92,0:13:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野岚子 你认识吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.49,0:13:48.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 那有什么问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.13,0:13:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你有打过威胁骚扰电话吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.12,0:13:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不知道你在说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.27,0:13:55.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装蒜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.26,0:13:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是全部从结野那里听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.55,0:14:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 那个婊子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.52,0:14:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.39,0:14:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她老老实实呆在家里的话我就平安无事了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.52,0:14:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太差劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.13,0:14:15.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个婊子竟然弄伤我的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.32,0:14:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想起来就让人火大
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.71,0:14:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.85,0:14:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.58,0:14:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯独只有你绝对…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.25,0:14:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.79,0:14:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.58,0:14:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微来陪你玩会儿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.65,0:14:35.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.82,0:14:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 外行人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.25,0:14:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我是拳击部的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.13,0:14:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.06,0:14:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真开心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.51,0:14:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底会发出怎样的哀嚎呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.42,0:14:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会有人来救你的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.37,0:15:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.30,0:15:04.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没用 没用 吃我一招
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.87,0:15:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔也要用用脚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.30,0:15:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.06,0:15:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差得远 还差得远
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.01,0:15:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是缠人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.28,0:15:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.92,0:15:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒下 给我倒下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.09,0:15:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.44,0:15:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然疼的要命
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.80,0:15:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那家伙的痛苦是我的这个没法比的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.06,0:15:32.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混账东西
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.21,0:15:44.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点程度 怎么可倒下
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.89,0:16:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么回事啊 你这个家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.75,0:16:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是真正的M
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.88,0:16:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是美少女的拳头的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.65,0:16:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比这重百倍的我都能承受
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.01,0:16:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体的构造不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.79,0:16:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你这种人相比
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.91,0:16:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知所云
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.20,0:16:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野又算什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.80,0:16:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正不过是别人的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.82,0:16:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管好自己的事情不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.78,0:16:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想活下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.83,0:16:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.83,0:16:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚成为高中生的女孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.40,0:16:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然说不想活了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.45,0:16:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把结野的痛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.32,0:16:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传递吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.30,0:16:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.54,0:17:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你记住！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.45,0:17:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.58,0:17:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然打人一点都不会爽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.88,0:17:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒球棒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.30,0:17:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐 为什么在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.99,0:17:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗憾的是看来我晚了一步
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.59,0:17:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是学姐救我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.95,0:17:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是个被女生打会很爽的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.60,0:17:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然会去找男人去干架
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.45,0:17:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我想立刻来帮你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.99,0:18:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你们这么认真
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.00,0:18:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我不应该出场的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.26,0:18:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.30,0:18:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又想稍微帮一点忙也好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.51,0:18:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那果然是神明的加护吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.28,0:18:23.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变得这么遍体鳞伤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.19,0:18:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了岚子而去努力了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.39,0:18:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那么点帅气哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.04,0:18:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要倒下还稍微早了些
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.17,0:18:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岚子还在等着你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.49,0:18:45.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.33,0:18:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满老师 间宫同学
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.08,0:18:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全像个爷们了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.93,0:18:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是被你干掉的？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.26,0:19:00.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户太郎该出手的时候还是有几把刷子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.87,0:19:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然拍男人很无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.65,0:19:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉冈 我绝对不会饶恕你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.73,0:19:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做好觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.50,0:19:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我 太郎 开门了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.85,0:19:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 你的脸…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.88,0:19:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在意 只是擦伤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.34,0:19:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说这个了 有个礼物要给你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.86,0:19:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.60,0:19:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让那个家伙立下誓言
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.56,0:19:41.87,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}天诛     反省     变态
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.56,0:19:41.87,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(414,380)}我做了坏事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.40,0:19:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今后绝对不会再接近你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.99,0:19:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电话也不会打了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.55,0:19:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不遵守的话 就把他的照片公之于众
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.28,0:19:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以已经没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.54,0:19:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 你的伤是因为…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.89,0:19:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.14,0:19:59.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘛…别在意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.47,0:20:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.83,0:20:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.46,0:20:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太那个啥了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.06,0:20:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能够做到的就只有这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.10,0:20:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.98,0:20:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.06,0:20:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一句就足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.42,0:20:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是给你们添了麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.07,0:20:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美也是 为我操心真是太谢谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.13,0:20:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原本以为能够和岚子一起去读女校的说…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.73,0:20:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是对不起了 由美
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.82,0:20:44.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害怕男生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.06,0:20:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是并不是说想去没有男人的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.94,0:20:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 这里有
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.61,0:20:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 美绪 还有满老师
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.13,0:20:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都很照顾我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.74,0:21:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我想了解大家更多
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.59,0:21:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.36,0:21:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 岚子 你改变了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.58,0:21:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.91,0:21:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再离我远一点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.62,0:21:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.76,0:21:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次离得太远了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.72,0:21:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 我不是按照你说的去做了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.19,0:21:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然敢对饲主顶嘴？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.70,0:21:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样 在这里感觉爽了的话
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.92,0:21:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就看太郎你自己了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.47,0:21:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关系好的可以嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.33,0:21:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.93,0:21:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.92,0:21:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这副打扮是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.43,0:21:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我转校过来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.57,0:21:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然岚子要我陪在身边呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.01,0:21:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.54,0:21:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 我可不认同你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.04,0:21:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,间宫流按摩术
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.52,0:22:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接招
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.86,0:22:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,指压力量太强了…好舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.80,0:23:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治愈每日操劳的心灵
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.81,0:23:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,称作美少女的绿洲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.05,0:23:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不试试这件吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.85,0:23:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了使这曲线显得更美
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.35,0:23:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害怕只是一开始
Dialogue: 2,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 1,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,452,848,453)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,453,848,454)}{\1c&HFAF7FD&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,454,848,455)}{\1c&HF6F0FC&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,455,848,456)}{\1c&HF2E9FB&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,456,848,457)}{\1c&HEEE1FA&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,457,848,458)}{\1c&HEADAF9&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,458,848,459)}{\1c&HE6D3F8&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,459,848,460)}{\1c&HE2CBF7&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,460,848,461)}{\1c&HDEC4F6&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,461,848,462)}{\1c&HD9BDF5&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,462,848,463)}{\1c&HD5B6F4&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,463,848,464)}{\1c&HD1AEF3&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,464,848,465)}{\1c&HCDA7F2&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,465,848,466)}{\1c&HC9A0F1&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,466,848,467)}{\1c&HC598F0&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,467,848,468)}{\1c&HC191EF&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,468,848,469)}{\1c&HBD8AEE&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 3,0:03:06.54,0:03:08.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,469,848,470)}{\1c&HB983ED&}为了你的缠斗
Dialogue: 2,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 1,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,26,848,27)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,27,848,28)}{\1c&HFBF8FE&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,28,848,29)}{\1c&HF7F1FD&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,29,848,30)}{\1c&HF3EBFC&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,30,848,31)}{\1c&HF0E4FB&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,31,848,32)}{\1c&HECDEFA&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,32,848,33)}{\1c&HE8D7F9&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,33,848,34)}{\1c&HE5D1F8&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,34,848,35)}{\1c&HE1CAF7&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,35,848,36)}{\1c&HDDC4F6&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,36,848,37)}{\1c&HDABDF5&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,37,848,38)}{\1c&HD6B7F4&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,38,848,39)}{\1c&HD2B0F3&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,39,848,40)}{\1c&HCFAAF2&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,40,848,41)}{\1c&HCBA3F1&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,41,848,42)}{\1c&HC79DF0&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,42,848,43)}{\1c&HC496EF&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,43,848,44)}{\1c&HC090EE&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,44,848,45)}{\1c&HBC89ED&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 3,0:23:46.97,0:23:49.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,45,848,46)}{\1c&HB983ED&}这样那样 情侣 笨蛋情侣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.94,0:01:25.40,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.50,0:01:29.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.12,0:01:34.64,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.52,0:01:40.91,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこの迷えるオマエ 惰性感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.10,0:01:46.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すがるワラを探して　他力本願バンザイ？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.47,0:01:50.93,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここに来ただけ（相当）お利口ねボウヤ（上等）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.96,0:01:56.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞いてあげるわ　早くゲロっていっそGo to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.18,0:01:59.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.82,0:02:01.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神の仕事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.80,0:02:04.12,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.15,0:02:08.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試行錯誤のevery day　いくら足騒いたトコで無駄
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.84,0:02:13.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神に従ってれば　万事OKでしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.59,0:02:15.87,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身の程わきまえて、さあ（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.88,0:02:18.15,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逆らうヤツらはお仕置きよ（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.16,0:02:22.86,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果主義更生させなくちゃGo to Hell→Deaaaath!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.95,0:02:31.28,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絶対的で革新的な　チカラ見せつけてあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.46,0:02:35.92,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと存在感異常のイカレタ趣味くらいノープロブレム
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.08,0:02:40.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこにひざまずいて教えを請いなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.04,0:02:45.03,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生観変えるような出会いになるから
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.22,0:02:50.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなビビってないで　全部あずけりゃいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.31,0:02:52.82,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.94,0:01:25.40,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.50,0:01:29.96,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.12,0:01:34.64,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu…YES!!Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.52,0:01:40.91,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里迷惘着的你　惰性感满载的face
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.10,0:01:46.28,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找着救命稻草 坐享其成万岁？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.47,0:01:50.93,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够到达这里（相当）真聪明啊男孩（很好）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.96,0:01:56.95,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就听你说说 快点全说出来干脆Go to Heaven
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.18,0:01:59.63,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.82,0:02:01.79,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.80,0:02:04.12,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES!! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.15,0:02:08.65,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不断摸索的every day 不管怎么挣扎都是没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.84,0:02:13.43,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺从神明的话 就万事OK了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.59,0:02:15.87,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看清自己的斤两（呆然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.88,0:02:18.15,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反抗的家伙都要调教哦（当然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.16,0:02:22.86,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须让结果注意复兴Go to Hell→Deaaaath!!!!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.95,0:02:31.28,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你见识见识绝对的革新的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.46,0:02:35.92,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着稍微存在感异常的奇怪兴趣而已No problem
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.08,0:02:40.88,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪在那里请求我的教导吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.04,0:02:45.03,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为会成为改变人生观的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.22,0:02:50.14,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那么害怕 全部交给我就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.31,0:02:52.82,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要H!E!L!P!你！

Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.55,0:22:07.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.80,0:22:10.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.96,0:22:13.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.58,0:22:15.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.72,0:22:20.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.08,0:22:21.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.40,0:22:22.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.85,0:22:23.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.15,0:22:26.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.80,0:22:29.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.42,0:22:31.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:31.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.01,0:22:33.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.43,0:22:34.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.69,0:22:35.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.08,0:22:37.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.33,0:22:38.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋には緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.69,0:22:39.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.07,0:22:42.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.23,0:22:44.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.74,0:22:48.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.70,0:22:54.45,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.25,0:22:59.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.35,0:23:01.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.92,0:23:04.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.82,0:23:06.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:09.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ 胸、痛い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.89,0:23:15.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちがとまらない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.55,0:23:17.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.74,0:23:20.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.81,0:23:23.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.52,0:23:25.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.62,0:23:29.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.98,0:23:32.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.55,0:22:07.63,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.80,0:22:10.77,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成就算是硬来？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.96,0:22:13.42,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气吐气之后是告白的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.58,0:22:15.54,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法安下心来的我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.72,0:22:20.08,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是特别的这是特别的…万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.08,0:22:21.34,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.40,0:22:22.68,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想靠的太近…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.85,0:22:23.96,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者是…可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.15,0:22:26.61,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近又远离 背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.80,0:22:29.22,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和欢笑可能是很相似的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.42,0:22:31.47,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想接近你喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.61,0:22:31.95,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.01,0:22:33.24,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我哪边都不擅长
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.43,0:22:34.53,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单行道是单方面的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.69,0:22:35.89,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商谈枪弹 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.08,0:22:37.14,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.33,0:22:38.52,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是爱还是恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.69,0:22:39.88,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情文物让她们对立吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.07,0:22:42.02,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.23,0:22:44.52,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想看到梦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.74,0:22:48.48,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.70,0:22:54.45,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我眼中你闪耀着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.25,0:22:59.34,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？对了…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.35,0:23:01.74,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要好好决定好哦 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.92,0:23:04.60,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席位只有一个所以就算硬来！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.82,0:23:06.98,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:09.69,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成 胸口 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.89,0:23:15.33,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之感情停不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.55,0:23:17.56,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好决定啊 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.74,0:23:20.66,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也想要挑战一下 想要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.81,0:23:23.36,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这次是承诺的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.52,0:23:25.43,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让你让我安心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.62,0:23:29.97,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为特别你是特别的…按下去！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.98,0:23:32.71,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!


