[Script Info]
Title:清雨
Original Script:清雨
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.8,0.4,2,10,10,8,134
Style: staff,黑体,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: title,方正大黑简体,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: a,方正准圆_GBK,31,&H000F0F0F,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF640064,0,0,0,0,100,105,1,0.00,1,0,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OPJP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00860BF4,&H64860BF4,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,128
Style: OPCH,华康圆体W5(P),24,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0000,&H64FF0000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00F7EEFF,&HF0000000,&H00FF0080,&H00640064,-1,0,0,0,100,105,1,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.05,0:00:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这人类失格
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.66,0:00:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出生在这个世上 真是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.12,0:00:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是假装一本正经那样让人恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.96,0:00:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态劣等性的你 要施与你灼热的教育
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.25,0:00:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由我Great Teacher 美绪大人来执行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.10,0:00:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.30,0:00:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有变态性是满分的你
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.87,0:00:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要称作教育的严格管教
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.68,0:00:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱的SM授课
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.61,0:00:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这家伙 别给我变爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.90,0:00:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和螃蟹一样的你 给我抓金枪鱼来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.90,0:00:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是好棒啊 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.22,0:00:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不如烂橘子 烂掉的变态
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.73,0:00:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鞋跟戳的我好爽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.68,0:00:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人恶心的垃圾学生啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.17,0:00:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过美绪老师就算是像你这样的垃圾也不会放弃的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.37,0:00:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 朝着晚霞奔跑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.03,0:00:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在看哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.88,0:01:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了水色
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.21,0:01:06.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在…在看哪里啊 你这大变态
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.44,0:01:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多来点 再多调教我点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.16,0:01:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也太得意了 你这不及格的 教育性指导你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.26,0:01:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情的爱的…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.23,0:01:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.14,0:01:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.27,0:01:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.77,0:01:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 振作点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.60,0:01:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脑袋不疼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.31,0:01:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去保健室吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.80,0:01:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的话就快点给我起来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.75,0:01:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为你有什么事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.91,0:01:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼 那个…你们是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.23,0:01:51.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.92,0:03:31.90,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fad(300,300)}本字幕由极影字幕社(bbs.ktxp.com)制作 仅供交流试看 喜爱本作品请支持Z版
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.92,0:03:31.90,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}翻译: 神代辰弥  雲端の翼   特效: W-BOY   后期: 清雨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.03,0:03:41.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 美绪 果然是记忆丧失
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.01,0:03:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说是撞到脑袋是原因
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.89,0:03:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.92,0:03:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.29,0:03:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.16,0:03:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.26,0:03:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 回去了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.06,0:03:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会送你的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.60,0:03:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.06,0:04:01.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直是你送我 这种时候该轮到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.38,0:04:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.77,0:04:04.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是碍事了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.05,0:04:07.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没这回事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.50,0:04:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.12,0:04:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是笨蛋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.77,0:04:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.10,0:04:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记忆丧失
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.81,0:04:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有忘记姐姐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.90,0:04:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于妈妈的事也是从出生到现在都记得吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.16,0:04:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.93,0:04:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据医院所说 这是一时的症状
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.91,0:04:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.61,0:04:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.00,0:04:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过两三天记忆就会恢复的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.59,0:04:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.52,0:04:46.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能够回到原来的太郎了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.98,0:04:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 不用花太多时间
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.08,0:04:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.57,0:04:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.69,0:04:58.04,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}结野岚子\N晚上好\N明天一起去学校吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.64,0:05:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野同学
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.24,0:05:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以进来吗 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.85,0:05:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.76,0:05:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.86,0:05:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直是叫我老姐的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.13,0:05:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.41,0:05:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 不要紧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.25,0:05:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 马上就不是叫老姐而是叫静香了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.31,0:05:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.38,0:05:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 在我肚子里有太郎的孩子了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.48,0:05:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.70,0:05:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 叫我静香
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.16,0:05:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又偷跑抢先了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.53,0:05:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是已经是即将要生了 的说…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.20,0:05:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连老妈也…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.69,0:05:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在想什么呢 静香 太郎明明在痛苦着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.04,0:05:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈才是 制造生米煮成熟饭的情况 这可不行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.92,0:05:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这家伙 对家人做了些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.03,0:06:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太差劲了 砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.47,0:06:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.05,0:06:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.19,0:06:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.81,0:06:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护身符 昨天做的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.66,0:06:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让太郎快点恢复记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.45,0:06:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是狗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.66,0:06:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果想着这个的话就会回忆起来的 各种事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.46,0:06:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于我的事肯定也能…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.41,0:06:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.15,0:06:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.10,0:06:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和结野同学是什么样的关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.68,0:06:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 那个是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.19,0:06:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带我去医院 还为我做护身符
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.56,0:06:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 是恋人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.67,0:06:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 恋…恋人？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.47,0:06:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.76,0:06:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么温柔可爱的女生怎么可能是我女朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.20,0:06:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.78,0:06:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.31,0:06:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是恋人的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.42,0:07:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然 是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.10,0:07:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好高兴啊 我竟然有这样的恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.85,0:07:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊 对不起 岚子撒了个弥天大谎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.86,0:07:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 对血亲都那样 女朋友不可能会没事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.17,0:07:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砂户太郎 你对结野做过些什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.67,0:07:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野同学
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.45,0:07:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.65,0:07:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你有怀着我的孩子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.44,0:07:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 太…太郎的孩子？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.26,0:07:37.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用隐藏 我会负起责任的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.16,0:07:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,责任…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.43,0:07:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野同学
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.48,0:07:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男生果然好可怕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.93,0:07:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这疼痛感 隐约的酸酸甜甜的感觉是？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.03,0:07:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神啊 对不起 岚子是个坏孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.50,0:08:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 真是太差劲了 砂户太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.36,0:08:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.16,0:08:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉非常的讨厌自己
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.79,0:08:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随时都可以来依靠我啊 我是你的好朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.61,0:08:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叶山同学
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.75,0:08:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太见外了 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.07,0:08:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感谢了 真的是太感谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.93,0:08:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.58,0:08:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要对我的辰吉做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.56,0:08:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了 这个痛并快乐着的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.36,0:08:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么呢 由美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.17,0:08:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会又变成BL属性了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.48,0:08:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.75,0:08:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装傻了啊 明明说过爱着辰吉的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.23,0:08:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.23,0:08:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由美
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.54,0:08:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,推倒他 明明连辰吉的纯洁都夺走了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.99,0:08:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叶山同学 刚才她说的是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.36,0:08:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那个啥…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.38,0:08:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会 不只是女性 对好友都出手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.79,0:09:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狩猎范围太宽泛了吧 我这家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.58,0:09:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经什么都不敢相信自己了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.96,0:09:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微休息一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.97,0:09:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.00,0:09:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我想在床上休息一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.03,0:09:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请随意吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.08,0:09:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶 那个 不要紧吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.98,0:09:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了 说了随你便了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.51,0:09:33.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这些照片是？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.88,0:09:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以往拍的那些照片
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.10,0:09:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进行分类 在整理中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.23,0:09:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈…都是女学生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.45,0:09:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？这是？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.33,0:09:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 拍的不错的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.69,0:09:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我喜欢的一张哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.32,0:09:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么感觉看着好熟啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.30,0:09:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.48,0:09:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.44,0:09:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照片上的人就是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.65,0:09:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.42,0:10:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是穿着女装的你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.38,0:10:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.32,0:10:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能不记得了 不过你有穿过女装哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.08,0:10:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女装…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.21,0:10:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.78,0:10:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对血亲出手 对女朋友出手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.49,0:10:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对好朋友都出手 而且还是女装变态
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.92,0:10:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经回不去了 家里也好 教室也好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.19,0:10:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下去到底该怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.45,0:10:35.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.38,0:10:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野同学
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.51,0:10:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找你好久了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.46,0:10:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.70,0:10:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.70,0:10:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.12,0:10:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的太郎明明连我有男生恐惧症都忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.93,0:10:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会 我不是也连孩子…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.01,0:10:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有的啊 孩…孩子还没有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.67,0:10:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗 太好了 结野同学没事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.20,0:11:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 那个 去动物园吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.28,0:11:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.15,0:11:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 去动物园吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.11,0:11:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就去？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.36,0:11:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 还有课程呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.54,0:11:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔也两个人翘一下课吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.07,0:11:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一手嘛 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.87,0:11:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么看 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.05,0:11:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yahoo 大象 你好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.01,0:11:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.45,0:11:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翘课这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.55,0:11:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.31,0:11:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真是大胆呢 结野同学
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.71,0:11:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平时是不这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.52,0:11:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 想让你回忆起来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.46,0:12:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里从前和太郎一起来过哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.97,0:12:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.99,0:12:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有想起来什么吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.26,0:12:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.88,0:12:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.00,0:12:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.63,0:12:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野同学 这个非常让我感到安心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.06,0:12:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.46,0:12:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得有种如释重负的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.71,0:12:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许因为是和结野同学你在一起的缘故吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.89,0:12:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会努力回想起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.20,0:12:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然也包括结野同学你的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.67,0:12:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.37,0:12:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.98,0:12:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以这样 砂户同学
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.91,0:12:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这个女人勾走
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.62,0:12:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柊学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.34,0:12:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来真的是丧失记忆了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.26,0:12:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.37,0:12:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚会来治愈你的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.29,0:13:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.56,0:13:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就开始治疗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.67,0:13:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将崭新的砂户君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.44,0:13:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,献给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.56,0:13:11.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不是太郎的记忆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.39,0:13:14.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦 我想起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.31,0:13:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.65,0:13:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚是砂户君的恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.83,0:13:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是成人意味满载的情人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.33,0:13:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在乱七八糟地给他灌输什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.63,0:13:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚 情人 小小的恋人…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.08,0:13:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能量不够了 日村！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.21,0:13:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啦 LOLILOLI…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.91,0:13:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再使劲一点
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.67,0:13:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了诺亚和砂户君的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.71,0:13:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样 这回再加把劲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.02,0:13:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你在看哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.20,0:13:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.21,0:13:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去就是犯罪啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.77,0:13:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.78,0:13:58.16,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}(为了将猪太郎的记忆恢复过来…！？)
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.94,0:14:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是让人吓了一跳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.32,0:14:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 真的很乱来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.21,0:14:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于笑了呢 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.34,0:14:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴 就感觉像是变回了平常你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.91,0:14:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记着吗 看那边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.46,0:14:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是呢 太郎就自说自话的把邮箱给我了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.02,0:14:42.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.14,0:14:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一点点也想不起来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.19,0:14:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.62,0:14:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渐渐开始冷起来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.73,0:14:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 快点回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.04,0:15:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.25,0:15:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 今天真的很感谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.73,0:15:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得你为我做了那么多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.95,0:15:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回去的路认识吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.39,0:15:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天不能一起回去了 对不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.66,0:15:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么回到了这里呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.26,0:15:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二义工社…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.90,0:15:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.44,0:15:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金属棒 这里都在进行些什么社团活动啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.97,0:15:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了 这凉飕飕的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.81,0:15:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是又感觉相当的怀念…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.07,0:15:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到 第二义工社
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.57,0:15:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？ 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.75,0:15:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.52,0:16:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常对不起 自说自话地就进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.07,0:16:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有回忆起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.86,0:16:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚麻色的头发
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.93,0:16:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白皙的肌肤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.59,0:16:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樱桃般的小嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.79,0:16:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想起这个人的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.19,0:16:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在直勾勾的盯着哪里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.98,0:16:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个 真是对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.98,0:16:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是个猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.31,0:16:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然用看陌生人的眼神看着我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.44,0:16:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太让人生气了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.70,0:16:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的下仆
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.62,0:16:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么会忘记美绪大人我的话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.19,0:16:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我想起来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.54,0:16:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.41,0:16:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算只想起我也好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.51,0:16:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在马上！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.43,0:16:47.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太强人所难了啊 那样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.61,0:16:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.40,0:16:52.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被美少女攻 感觉相当爽啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.64,0:16:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要跟我说你连自己是超M的这件事都忘了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.71,0:16:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个无可救药的超M混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.07,0:17:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球上最糟糕最可恶的变态啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.57,0:17:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.07,0:17:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我要治愈你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.16,0:17:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陷入深深困苦的我真是个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.69,0:17:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答案就在眼前
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.70,0:17:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 我可以坐在这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.20,0:17:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在太郎的位子上看是这样一幅景致啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.32,0:17:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真希望他能够回想起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.62,0:17:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我站起来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.16,0:17:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.04,0:17:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 想起来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.92,0:17:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个纯正的变态这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.57,0:17:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.83,0:17:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 做好觉悟吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.20,0:17:56.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请停手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.42,0:17:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野同学？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.29,0:18:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别阻碍我 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.09,0:18:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是为了取回他的记忆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.90,0:18:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样太危险了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.85,0:18:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才想到的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.23,0:18:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要他把我的事情全部想起来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.01,0:18:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 过来吧 太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.55,0:18:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.50,0:18:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开 岚子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.95,0:18:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不让
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.82,0:18:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪你才是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.18,0:18:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪你到底对太郎是什么想法
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.00,0:18:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么想法…也没啥特别的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.58,0:18:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的美绪有些奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.04,0:18:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不能够说的很清楚 但是对待太郎的态度不一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.74,0:18:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷不丁地说啥呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.75,0:18:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.04,0:18:41.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢太郎！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.66,0:18:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.90,0:18:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说出了我最真实的想法
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.39,0:18:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下轮到美绪你了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.77,0:18:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.13,0:18:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到这家伙心里就毛得不行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.36,0:18:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的仅仅如此吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.18,0:18:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是当然的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.02,0:19:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对太郎什么的…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.31,0:19:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.18,0:19:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的爱 已经完全传达到我的心了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.99,0:19:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的爱着失去记忆前的我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.88,0:19:17.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被结野同学你的温柔所打动
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.45,0:19:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石动美绪同学 你的思念也传递到我的心了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.47,0:19:26.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 不要再为我而争斗了…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.70,0:19:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得手了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.35,0:19:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被美少女把玩 真是赛高~
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.11,0:19:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.64,0:19:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.74,0:19:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太郎 没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.30,0:19:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个人慌慌张张的干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.78,0:19:55.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊咧 不是应该在活动室里吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.72,0:19:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说记忆…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.95,0:20:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记忆？ 你指什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.39,0:20:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记忆丧失那段时间的事情不记得了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.36,0:20:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？记忆丧失？我？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.48,0:20:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不记得了吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.91,0:20:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 太郎变回了原来的太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.47,0:20:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点就足够了…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.25,0:20:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 这个变态老是让人操心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.63,0:20:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野 我是不是做了什么很糟糕的事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.49,0:20:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 是我说了很过分的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.73,0:20:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结野
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.76,0:20:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.60,0:20:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.81,0:20:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石动学姐？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.66,0:20:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.55,0:20:48.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再次忘记我了 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.86,0:20:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.44,0:20:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.62,0:20:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是总觉得你太欠揍了 这到底是为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.16,0:21:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,油然而生的感觉啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.58,0:22:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想起来了吗 你这个超M混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.19,0:22:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.49,0:22:45.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您的这身打扮让我刻骨铭心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.53,0:22:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就看着吧 美绪大人我一定会治好你的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.90,0:22:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.79,0:22:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.03,0:22:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.37,0:22:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.55,0:22:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把太郎恢复过来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.21,0:23:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没啥啦 不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.20,0:23:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我可不会认输的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.04,0:23:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对太郎真实的想法是什么？ 美绪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.24,0:23:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是当然的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.87,0:23:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪太郎是我美绪大人的下仆
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.91,0:23:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美绪大人的超S解除全开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.34,0:23:33.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 今天也打起精神吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.89,0:23:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这头猪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.90,0:23:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是跟你说了别想得美
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.30,0:23:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么吗 这副被雨淋湿小猪般的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.46,0:23:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的超M体质 本美绪大人一定会治好的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.97,0:23:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的眼中只看着我就好了
Dialogue: 2,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 1,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,452,848,453)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,453,848,454)}{\1c&HFAF7FD&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,454,848,455)}{\1c&HF6F0FC&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,455,848,456)}{\1c&HF2E9FB&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,456,848,457)}{\1c&HEEE1FA&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,457,848,458)}{\1c&HEADAF9&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,458,848,459)}{\1c&HE6D3F8&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,459,848,460)}{\1c&HE2CBF7&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,460,848,461)}{\1c&HDEC4F6&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,461,848,462)}{\1c&HD9BDF5&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,462,848,463)}{\1c&HD5B6F4&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,463,848,464)}{\1c&HD1AEF3&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,464,848,465)}{\1c&HCDA7F2&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,465,848,466)}{\1c&HC9A0F1&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,466,848,467)}{\1c&HC598F0&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,467,848,468)}{\1c&HC191EF&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,468,848,469)}{\1c&HBD8AEE&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 3,0:03:34.63,0:03:36.88,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,470)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,469,848,470)}{\1c&HB983ED&}失去的记忆
Dialogue: 2,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord3\3cH&H781218&H}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 1,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord4\3cH&HFFFFFF&H}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord5\3cH&H781218&H}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,26,848,27)}{\1c&HFFFFFF&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,27,848,28)}{\1c&HFBF8FE&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,28,848,29)}{\1c&HF7F1FD&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,29,848,30)}{\1c&HF3EBFC&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,30,848,31)}{\1c&HF0E4FB&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,31,848,32)}{\1c&HECDEFA&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,32,848,33)}{\1c&HE8D7F9&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,33,848,34)}{\1c&HE5D1F8&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,34,848,35)}{\1c&HE1CAF7&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,35,848,36)}{\1c&HDDC4F6&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,36,848,37)}{\1c&HDABDF5&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,37,848,38)}{\1c&HD6B7F4&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,38,848,39)}{\1c&HD2B0F3&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,39,848,40)}{\1c&HCFAAF2&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,40,848,41)}{\1c&HCBA3F1&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,41,848,42)}{\1c&HC79DF0&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,42,848,43)}{\1c&HC496EF&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,43,848,44)}{\1c&HC090EE&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,44,848,45)}{\1c&HBC89ED&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 3,0:23:49.97,0:23:51.92,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(424,46)}{\fsp4\bord0\3cH&H781218&H}{\clip(0,45,848,46)}{\1c&HB983ED&}圣诞节的愿望
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.00,0:01:53.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.59,0:01:58.04,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.20,0:02:02.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.67,0:02:09.11,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこの迷えるオマエ　悲状感満載のface
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.29,0:02:14.30,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すがるワラも見捨てりゃ　それもしょーガないか？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.48,0:02:18.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運命は今日も（迷走）イジワルだから（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.12,0:02:24.46,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめてわたしが　味方してたい何かできるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.26,0:02:27.65,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.85,0:02:29.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まかせてみて
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.91,0:02:32.16,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.32,0:02:36.72,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ギリギリの線じゃヌルい　破滅しちゃってゼロってそんで？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.94,0:02:41.62,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,かたくななDNA　ムリは禁物
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.64,0:02:43.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強制終了5秒前（寸前）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.97,0:02:46.20,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生まれかわれそうな予感？（全然）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.21,0:02:50.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現場主義更生させちゃえばGo to ヘ·ブン
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.10,0:02:55.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウムを言わさず　あの手この手で
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.66,0:02:59.38,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今すぐ正してあげるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.57,0:03:03.99,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと存在感以上に気になるフォーリンラブ未満が
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.20,0:03:08.81,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情けない顔してほっとけないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:13.13,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人生観変えるような出会いしたんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.34,0:03:18.27,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あとはされるがまま　流されちゃえばいいのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.44,0:03:20.79,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へ！ル！プ！いくよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.00,0:01:53.53,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Help!!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.59,0:01:58.04,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.20,0:02:02.65,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu… YES!! Help U
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.67,0:02:09.11,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里迷惘着的你 满是悲壮感的face
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.29,0:02:14.30,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢弃救命稻草吧 这也是没办法的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.48,0:02:18.96,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命运现在也（迷走）在坏心眼（暴走）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.12,0:02:24.46,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少让我 成为你的同伴为你做些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.26,0:02:27.65,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（NO!! Jesus crtsis! Oh my god!）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.85,0:02:29.89,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.91,0:02:32.16,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（YES! Chu-ru-Chu-Chu-Chu Help U）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.32,0:02:36.72,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧绷的神经没有用 破坏掉的话就什么都没了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.94,0:02:41.62,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顽固的DNA 勉强是禁止的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.64,0:02:43.96,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强制停止5秒前（近在咫尺）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.97,0:02:46.20,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像要重生一样的预感？（完全没有）
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.20,0:02:50.88,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实主义复活的话Go to天堂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.10,0:02:55.43,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说可否 在那双手这双手中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.66,0:02:59.38,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在马上给你修正
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.57,0:03:03.99,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点存在感但还未陷入爱河
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.20,0:03:08.81,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摆出一副可怜的表情没法让人放着不管
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.00,0:03:13.13,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为想要改变人生观一样的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.34,0:03:18.27,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来就这样吧 放任逐流就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.44,0:03:20.79,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要H!E!L!P!你！

Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.55,0:21:06.63,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.80,0:21:09.77,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ無理矢理？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.96,0:21:12.42,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って吐いたら告白日和
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.58,0:21:14.54,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心されない私がいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.72,0:21:19.08,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと特別それは特別…バンザイ！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.08,0:21:20.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.40,0:21:21.68,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,近くてやだ…なの？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.85,0:21:22.96,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それとも…いいの？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.15,0:21:25.61,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってさがって後ろの正面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.80,0:21:28.22,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖と笑いは似ているかもね
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.42,0:21:30.47,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よってたかって好きです
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.61,0:21:30.95,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.01,0:21:32.24,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛して恋してどっちも苦手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.43,0:21:33.53,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情片道一方的な
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.69,0:21:34.89,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相談銃弾 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.08,0:21:36.14,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ！そうだ！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.33,0:21:37.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛には恋には緊張必要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.69,0:21:38.88,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,純情文武両立させて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.07,0:21:41.02,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.23,0:21:43.52,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢が見たい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.74,0:21:47.48,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌われもしょうがないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.70,0:21:53.45,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私の目にはキミがきらきら
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.25,0:21:58.34,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうして？そうだ…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.35,0:22:00.74,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもしっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.92,0:22:03.60,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席は一個だけだから無理矢理！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.82,0:22:05.98,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり足りない love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.18,0:22:08.69,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて達成しなくちゃ 胸、痛い
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.89,0:22:14.33,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とにかく気持ちがとまらない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.55,0:22:16.56,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかり決めてよ love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.74,0:22:19.66,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せめて挑戦したいよ したいよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.81,0:22:22.36,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸って今度は承諾日和
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.52,0:22:24.43,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安心させたい私にしてよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.62,0:22:28.97,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって特別キミは特別…押して！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.98,0:22:31.71,OPJP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.55,0:21:06.63,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.80,0:21:09.77,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成就算是硬来？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.96,0:21:12.42,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气吐气之后是告白的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.58,0:21:14.54,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法安下心来的我在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.72,0:21:19.08,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是特别的这是特别的…万岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.08,0:21:20.34,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.40,0:21:21.68,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想靠的太近…吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.85,0:21:22.96,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又或者是…可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.15,0:21:25.61,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠近又远离 背后的正面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.80,0:21:28.22,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖和欢笑可能是很相似的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.42,0:21:30.47,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好想接近你喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.61,0:21:30.95,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.01,0:21:32.24,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱和恋我哪边都不擅长
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.43,0:21:33.53,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情单行道是单方面的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.69,0:21:34.89,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商谈枪弹 da-dan-da down load
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.08,0:21:36.14,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.33,0:21:37.52,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是爱还是恋都需要紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.69,0:21:38.88,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纯情文物让她们对立吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.07,0:21:41.02,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,insert insert insert
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.23,0:21:43.52,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想看到梦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.74,0:21:47.48,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被讨厌也没办法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.70,0:21:53.45,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我眼中你闪耀着
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.25,0:21:58.34,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？对了…Teach me please
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.35,0:22:00.74,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要好好决定好哦 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.92,0:22:03.60,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席位只有一个所以就算硬来！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.82,0:22:05.98,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还不够 love me love me
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.18,0:22:08.69,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也要达成 胸口 好痛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.89,0:22:14.33,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之感情停不下来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.55,0:22:16.56,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好决定啊 love you love you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.74,0:22:19.66,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少也想要挑战一下 想要啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.81,0:22:22.36,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吸气这次是承诺的好日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.52,0:22:24.43,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让你让我安心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.62,0:22:28.97,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为特别你是特别的…按下去！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.98,0:22:31.71,OPCH,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,yeah-yeah-yeah-yeah!!


