[Script Info]
Title: Jormungand - Perfect Order - 08
Original Script: 动漫花园枫组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,苹方-简,50,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,0.6,2,0,0,12,1
Style: STAFF,方正小标宋_GBK,46,&H00FFFFFF,&HFFFFFFFF,&H00000000,&HFF000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,0,0,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.65,0:00:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我承认你是我独一无二的好友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.12,0:00:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要对我心存感激啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.45,0:00:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那至今为止都算啥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.55,0:00:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脑子进水了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.30,0:00:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还刚抓完蝴蝶呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.72,0:00:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一看你就没啥朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.99,0:00:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的朋友也很少啊 基本为零
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.15,0:00:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 你肯跟我做朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.10,0:00:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴啊 蔻蔻
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.04,0:00:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是从未见过的新品种…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.67,0:00:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找死啊喂
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.06,0:00:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I can flyyyyyy
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.06,0:00:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（这是某部著名神经病杀人片里的著名台词）
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.85,0:00:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能飞的话 蝴蝶什么的统统手到擒来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.21,0:00:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天空对于人类来说太遥远 不该涉足啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.32,0:00:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那绝对是新品种
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.15,0:00:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔻蔻 我们两个超天才的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.98,0:00:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南你应该是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.95,0:00:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不算天才
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.21,0:00:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是个军火商
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.30,0:01:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你耍啥小性子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.70,0:01:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在陈述事实嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.24,0:01:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算你是世界海运王的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.18,0:01:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就能让军队和政府官僚买你的帐买你的东西啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.77,0:01:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就凭你这小毛孩子 跑到他们面前欢蹦乱跳地一阵推销？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.04,0:01:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我说呀 蔻蔻你有使人信服的才能
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.80,0:01:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个百年大计
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.07,0:01:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要以我的头脑和蔻蔻的商才来成就
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.04,0:01:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音太大
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.06,0:01:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个计划只能是你知我知
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.40,0:01:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保密防谍 不可不知
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.23,0:01:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要找人倾诉 那就请你找个死人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.12,0:01:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也想看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.36,0:01:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所说明的新世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.89,0:01:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.15,0:01:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.38,0:01:40.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个美丽新世界！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.42,0:01:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到之前我是不会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.98,0:01:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个新世界是你我二人一起创造的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.98,0:01:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 你可别给我下绊儿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.43,0:01:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最讨厌半途而废了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.07,0:01:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是清醒还是沉睡 把这个计划装在脑里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.24,0:01:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好去思考他的理论与实践吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.82,0:01:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是一样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.33,0:02:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要花钱找我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.40,0:02:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实报实销
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.93,0:02:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.79,0:02:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只都没抓到 下山去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.20,0:02:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦对了 我最讨厌人家催我了 我是拖延症
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.93,0:02:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.68,0:02:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是逼急了我呀 我就逃！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.06,0:02:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这人真太任性了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.57,0:04:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜童话公司第二制作所成功落成！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个工厂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.83,0:04:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是本人蔻蔻·海克梅迪亚全资出资
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.32,0:04:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由天田南博士为主导的玩具和机器人研发中心
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.05,0:04:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,附温泉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.12,0:04:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然擅自改动设计图啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.89,0:04:30.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你呀 身是菩提树 心是明镜台
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.99,0:04:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时时勤拂拭 勿使惹尘埃啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.31,0:04:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南 你这个人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.16,0:04:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这可能要糟糕…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.28,0:04:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有话快说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.82,0:04:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥 巧克力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.22,0:04:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还问我为啥去英国
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.02,0:04:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷也有活要干 很忙的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.73,0:04:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎可能一年到头都跟着那帮疯丫头转悠
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.10,0:04:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当我傻的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.25,0:04:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么有啥事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.16,0:05:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 你上次说的那个童话公司新厂落成典礼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.87,0:05:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是海克梅迪亚来剪彩的？？！！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.07,0:05:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊对啊 全明星阵容到齐了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.61,0:05:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下子真的搞大了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.45,0:05:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要录音
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.67,0:05:11.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.72,0:05:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都是临时来的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.55,0:05:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪有可能现在跑去装设备啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.29,0:05:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给那个小鬼约拿吃个糖
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.44,0:05:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁机在他身上装窃听器不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.92,0:05:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啥呢你真傻啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.70,0:05:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个死女人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.91,0:05:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么打起了玩具工厂的主意 到底怎么一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.71,0:05:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来了 那里真的这么单纯？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.74,0:05:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 你给我去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.09,0:05:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我去问清楚这里是干啥的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.14,0:05:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她对你还不错 肯定没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.94,0:05:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当我真傻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.35,0:05:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.48,0:05:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下子老湿
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.51,0:05:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦不 学者老师分分秒秒给我电话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.32,0:05:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔻蔻·海克梅迪亚怎么去了那个新工厂？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.94,0:05:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.83,0:05:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她前不久还在法国啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.35,0:05:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位小姐最喜欢给我们搞突然袭击了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.60,0:05:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以决不能对她掉以轻心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.42,0:06:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 稻草人同志
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.49,0:06:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在伦敦吧现在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.49,0:06:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南非那个新的研究所 内幕情况如何
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.38,0:06:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布莱克科长 我可不是在你下面给你报告的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.24,0:06:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要管这么多了 告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.41,0:06:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是真不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.69,0:06:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且今天海克梅迪亚手下的兵都到齐了的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.97,0:06:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他进出的好像只有天田博士
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.27,0:06:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除外还有几名PMC在戒备
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.87,0:06:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为玩具开发 这的确搞得戒备森严
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.23,0:06:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但目前也没有进一步的材料了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.47,0:06:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然我们要继续深挖下去的 您就看好了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.86,0:06:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这简直是迈阿密博士的一座城池啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.01,0:06:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.33,0:06:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还活着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.81,0:06:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.14,0:06:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发射火箭的时候你也在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.23,0:06:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在在迈阿密博士手下？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.19,0:06:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.83,0:07:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩具工厂…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.97,0:07:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐想啥呢 想不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.08,0:07:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀 南人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.95,0:07:08.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.49,0:07:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 这样不会不妥吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.46,0:07:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧不要紧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.00,0:07:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿同学是男孩子 一直看着个工厂多无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.93,0:07:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天气这么冷 还去抓蝴蝶？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.98,0:07:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵呵 真的和蔻蔻说的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.82,0:07:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一句话都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.07,0:07:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样还跟着你默默地走 真可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.71,0:07:28.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无口的可莲
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.13,0:07:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无口的约拿弟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.50,0:07:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩刚才说了些啥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.83,0:07:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是往事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.97,0:07:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开枪射过可莲
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.30,0:07:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在意你就输了啊 约拿弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.46,0:07:42.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可莲啊 可耐打了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.77,0:07:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一条虫都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.91,0:07:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也在意料之中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.58,0:07:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去散步吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.82,0:07:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想把你们俩带出来转转
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.76,0:07:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈阿密博士
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.09,0:07:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想请教一件事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.32,0:07:58.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以啊可以啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.04,0:08:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便问随便问
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.58,0:08:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了一个问题以外
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.90,0:08:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全都可以回答你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.21,0:08:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和蔻蔻两个人 究竟想要干什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.25,0:08:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗憾啊 约拿弟弟 你就是踩到了这个地雷
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.74,0:08:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是我和蔻蔻两个人的约定啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.21,0:08:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能告诉你 不好意思啊 约拿弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.06,0:08:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不要紧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.46,0:08:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿 再来玩啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.39,0:08:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.37,0:08:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.72,0:08:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.70,0:08:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.72,0:08:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话 把他放我这里说不定也好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.33,0:08:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好什么好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.75,0:08:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就怕你跟他待久了被他的可爱感化了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.60,0:08:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反而就失去了你的本质啊 蔻蔻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.26,0:08:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啥表情啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.07,0:08:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这是真心吓了一跳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.39,0:08:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到南的大脑里 也有一些感性的区域啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.50,0:08:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只关心硬件的你关心起别人的软件来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.55,0:08:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是好事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.40,0:08:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对计划认真思考过后
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.92,0:08:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沉浸在计划其中的现实感里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.81,0:09:00.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猛回头
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.52,0:09:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周围的情景岂能不让你心生畏惧呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.38,0:09:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你不需要害怕 南
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.89,0:09:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为计划已经进展到最终阶段了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.00,0:09:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只差你的最终部件
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.64,0:09:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它就可以运作了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.44,0:09:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是不可逆的潮流
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.42,0:09:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敏锐的人 或许已经看出了它的端倪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.72,0:09:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何 对于我们的大业
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.35,0:09:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人乐见 也有人不乐见 这也正常
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.68,0:09:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也正因如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.09,0:09:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你看好 南
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.58,0:09:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不会有人出手干涉的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.20,0:09:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵呵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.75,0:09:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.98,0:09:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能确实如此吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.50,0:09:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.61,0:09:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对是如此 天田博士
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.53,0:09:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到点了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.87,0:09:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们撤啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.12,0:09:48.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我好好地干啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.29,0:09:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羡慕嫉妒恨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.39,0:09:50.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个看上去手感超好的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.85,0:09:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 那家伙 做个恶德商人越来越得心应手了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.77,0:09:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士 我话说在前头
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.60,0:10:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不可能会让你随心所欲地揉的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.65,0:10:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世事难预料哟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.19,0:10:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.43,0:10:06.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔻蔻
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.82,0:10:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不能一直不给那玩意起个名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.99,0:10:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起个名字吧你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.78,0:10:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就叫世界蛇了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.45,0:10:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么定了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.86,0:10:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1984 phase.1
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.00,0:10:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南非 伊莉莎白港
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.77,0:10:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还敢叫世界蛇
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.47,0:10:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙 真是个天生讽刺大师
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.72,0:10:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵呵
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.97,0:10:33.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啥开心的事嘛 天田博士
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.76,0:10:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思呀 卡利社长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.17,0:10:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这里刚想起个特别好笑的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.66,0:10:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是社长啊 虽然你请我吃大餐我是很开心啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.97,0:10:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对于你来说 可能一点用都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.75,0:10:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要找我帮你造武器那可是找错人了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.04,0:10:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且看你这么精明 怎么可能打这么蠢的算盘
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.19,0:10:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.70,0:10:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实社长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.94,0:10:59.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于博士和博士的好友 蔻蔻最近的动向很关注啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.23,0:11:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔻蔻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.25,0:11:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们跟她关系不也不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.98,0:11:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米尔特 你给我闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.80,0:11:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.23,0:11:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我部下多嘴了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.47,0:11:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我绝不可能对此毫无关注
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.64,0:11:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我不认为博士这样聪明的人会简单对我们说实话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.98,0:11:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你到南非来干啥啊 度假啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.75,0:11:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.82,0:11:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个人想什么都藏不住
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.43,0:11:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想向您请教
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.20,0:11:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我们这样的中坚军火商 今后该何去何从
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.71,0:11:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,敏锐的人 或许已经看出了它的端倪…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.62,0:11:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.40,0:11:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道我们公司不妙了吗 社长
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.00,0:11:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Currie's Company Aerial Transport
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.00,0:11:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（到这里我们可以确信CCAT是在影射Cobham plc）
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.93,0:11:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡利社长曾是英国空军的优秀飞行员
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.60,0:11:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退役之后买了架二手运输机
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.18,0:11:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始跑业务
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.94,0:11:55.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然知道是些什么业务
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.73,0:11:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是军方相关人士还是转让了运输机和相关文件 大开绿灯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.76,0:12:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈 真是不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.63,0:12:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是什么光彩的事迹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.71,0:12:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还真亏您调查清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.63,0:12:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会啊 这是蔻蔻说给我听的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.78,0:12:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器生意难做吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.34,0:12:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2000年以后起 从某个固定时间点开始
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.03,0:12:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵司擅长的轻武器运输费用开始飞涨
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.44,0:12:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在冷战遗留武器堆上建立起来的 社长的敌对企业们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.76,0:12:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一夜之间 仿佛失去了作用
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.99,0:12:27.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都给CIA扫进了历史的牢笼去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.87,0:12:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从战争中得益的人群
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.79,0:12:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎一夜之间成为了上流阶级
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.06,0:12:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大抵这样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.54,0:12:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社长怎可能被抓啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.28,0:12:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米尔特
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.32,0:12:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.42,0:12:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年某些机关特别厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.65,0:12:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.66,0:12:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点想扁迈阿密博士了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.30,0:12:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米尔特！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.72,0:12:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以用武器啊 可莲
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.72,0:12:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女人要用拳头说话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.73,0:12:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的 博士
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.08,0:12:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.37,0:12:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被法尔梅干翻了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.79,0:12:58.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废话少说
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.46,0:13:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按照蔻蔻的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.58,0:13:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人类自觉战争的本质之时 便开始将其导向民营化
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.99,0:13:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,营业方法 营业人员 那是千变万化 不一而足
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.16,0:13:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果就是燃烧弹投到泥泞的密林
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.09,0:13:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石油在热砂的沙漠中燃烧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.27,0:13:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诸如此类的传统战场已经渐渐淡出
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.12,0:13:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取而代之的则是贫穷的债权人为了还债而开战
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.12,0:13:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（1991年伊拉克入侵科威特即为此例 至于欠了谁的钱嘛…）
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.37,0:13:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,士兵们脑子里满是问号赶赴战场
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.25,0:13:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高官们在会议室里一边喝咖啡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.95,0:13:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边按下按钮 无人机发射导弹 这样战争就画上句号
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.75,0:13:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战争就变成了这样一个四不像了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.29,0:13:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先不论它的好坏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.39,0:13:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社长您所熟悉的战争形式已经一去不复返了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.33,0:13:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使如此 您还要吃这碗战争饭吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.01,0:13:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到底呀 卡利社长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.88,0:13:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当您这样的达人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.25,0:13:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来找我这个局外人来讨说法的这一刻起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.37,0:13:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结论不就已经摆在那里了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.85,0:14:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开业界的事 还是跟蔻蔻商量比较好哟
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.33,0:14:06.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.42,0:14:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博士您真是快人快语
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.16,0:14:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这种话怎么可以跟海克梅迪亚说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.73,0:14:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞得我好像跟她认输了一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.59,0:14:18.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 接下来去干哪一行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.99,0:14:20.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去开个餐厅吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.78,0:14:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对做菜很有信心 老板
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.80,0:14:24.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陆啊 你也来帮把手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.70,0:14:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.70,0:14:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打了 我认输了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.70,0:14:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板 偶也要帮忙开惨听
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.74,0:14:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦我知道了 你快坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.74,0:14:42.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安分点待着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.97,0:14:43.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.18,0:14:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃得饱 喝得好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.71,0:14:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是满足啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.82,0:14:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可莲你真的好厉害啊 手不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.02,0:14:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为对方也不是来真的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.00,0:14:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特地来听人教训自己说一个时代结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.79,0:15:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还特意来讨了一顿打
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.37,0:15:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军火商一个个性格怎么都那么扭曲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.13,0:15:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没法子 卖的东西就不一般啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.65,0:15:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿 你看你看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.68,0:15:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜景好看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.58,0:15:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是这车好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.49,0:15:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能还回来真太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.89,0:15:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡戈同志高兴地手舞足蹈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.54,0:15:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得怀念吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.81,0:15:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让人想起我们俩相遇的那天吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.41,0:15:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是这辆车
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.55,0:15:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是这样的夜里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.56,0:15:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是我们两个单独出来兜风
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.84,0:15:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.32,0:15:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的和那天一模一样啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.56,0:15:48.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（怎么看怎么像波兰家的幻影2000D）
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.90,0:15:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿约拿
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.01,0:16:01.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿乖～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.96,0:16:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔻蔻
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.83,0:16:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿成这样我很难保护你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.82,0:16:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 约拿的感觉回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.33,0:16:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔻蔻 你是不是太粘约拿弟弟了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.01,0:16:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.22,0:16:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿弟弟怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.35,0:16:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀蔻蔻
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.65,0:16:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想死你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.59,0:16:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞得我都想加入你们HCLI了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.87,0:16:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好久不见了 托娅霍夫斯基小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.72,0:16:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海克梅迪亚和托娅霍夫斯基两个人见面了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.14,0:16:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都认识
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.47,0:16:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小姐不见小 大妈不服老啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.92,0:16:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她呀 好像是从Eurocopter买了三架上一代UAV 雇了操作人员
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.13,0:16:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是拿去非洲高价出租吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.08,0:16:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟 现在连抵抗组织都会用这玩意啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.84,0:17:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.91,0:17:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稻草人同志 你人在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.47,0:17:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚到南非啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.72,0:17:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去干啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.02,0:17:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好意思问我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.49,0:17:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是去调查天田博士的资金流向
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.13,0:17:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好去查探那个新工厂内部的虚实啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.46,0:17:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.49,0:17:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再联系
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.38,0:17:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还跟我扯这有的没的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.05,0:17:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老子不是你手下啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.80,0:17:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是老湿啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.92,0:17:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你烦死了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.80,0:17:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你终于也被人差来差去了 你也有这天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.23,0:17:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.43,0:17:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵呵嘻嘻嘻吼吼吼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.05,0:17:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学者啊 你来会议室吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.45,0:17:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡士柏要开始大演讲了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.81,0:17:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.74,0:17:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,HCLI最近有点势头太劲啊 没问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.96,0:17:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别把船搞沉了就好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.12,0:17:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,2012就要到了 你们难得给我船票 就算贼船我岂能不上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.06,0:17:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔻蔻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.99,0:17:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对着天空来个V
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.31,0:17:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,V～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.76,0:17:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是静止摄影模式下的成像
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.57,0:17:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是在肉眼观测不到的高度拍摄的啊 精度真是惊人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.13,0:18:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看吧 这个型号卖点就在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.90,0:18:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且某企业把太阳能电池板装置在这个型号上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.82,0:18:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在气象条件可忽略不计的高高度上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.07,0:18:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白天充电夜晚使用 居然达成了24小时不间断飞行的伟业
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.40,0:18:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经进一步在这个半永久性飞行平台上安装此类探测器
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.79,0:18:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开发新型号了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.44,0:18:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿梅利亚小姐 打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.78,0:18:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡士柏·海克梅迪亚在菲律宾的发表会就要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.01,0:18:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对喔 不好意思 能帮我录下来吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.60,0:18:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.45,0:18:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不看没问题？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.66,0:18:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.62,0:18:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哥哥据说要在这次展会上发表新的业务领域
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.87,0:18:39.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对此事我当然很是关心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.22,0:18:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定和你们发射上去的那一百来颗卫星有关吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.23,0:18:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 物流领域就要掀起革命了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.09,0:18:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定是一件大事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.63,0:18:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战争的形态也会为之改变
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.60,0:18:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军火商的存在形态也会随之产生变化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.89,0:18:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我还是以为
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.70,0:18:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起去附和这些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.31,0:19:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不如现在跟蔻蔻好好谈谈 搞好关系来得有前途呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.35,0:19:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲律宾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.77,0:19:21.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 今晚欢迎世界各国军政要人齐聚一堂
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.51,0:19:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是卡士柏·海克梅迪亚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.73,0:19:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家别那么拘谨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.39,0:19:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞不好说到一半会睡着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.00,0:19:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信曾与我合作过的各位自不用说了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.21,0:19:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家应该都有数 我不过是中间商
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.05,0:19:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是本次发表的发言人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.99,0:19:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如对内容有任何问题 请参照手边资料
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.72,0:19:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者请致电总公司谘询
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.56,0:19:50.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这发言人超脱力的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.37,0:19:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说兄妹俩都一个样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.55,0:19:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一言以蔽之
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.78,0:19:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（Global Grid）
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.78,0:19:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本次发表的Hek～GG
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.44,0:20:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用了HCLI构筑起来的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.40,0:20:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集装箱海运全球网络
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.02,0:20:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及发射的126颗全球定位卫星来构建
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.00,0:20:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一套民营承包制的兵站运营及配套通讯指挥解决方案
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.07,0:20:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自古以来 军事离不开补给 军队离不开兵站
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.44,0:20:22.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军队就给补给线这条铁链拴住
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.51,0:20:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却不得不依赖它求得生存
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.81,0:20:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军队配置 物资配置 通信整备
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.60,0:20:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,系统构建
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.27,0:20:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有以上这些 任您天兵天将也难动分毫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.47,0:20:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且这一整套方案非常费时费力费金钱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.58,0:20:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我举个例子 剩余物资堆积如山
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.45,0:20:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前线士兵却饿肚子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.18,0:20:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那让我们把这样的浪费杜绝掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.80,0:20:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本Hek～GG将视战事大小 规模 需时
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.08,0:20:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来为您提供全套合适有效的兵站整备和指挥通信业务
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.12,0:20:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要使用本公司系统
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.90,0:20:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论何种军队 都能以合理的成本开展海外兵力投送业务了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.13,0:21:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是已经拥有此项能力的军事力量
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.36,0:21:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信对于节约其预算 也有相当的效果吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.91,0:21:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,英语中物流一词 似乎来源于古希腊语里精于算计之人的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.91,0:21:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}（你错了 就我所知是来自法语的logistique 原意是住宿）
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.27,0:21:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现代兵站学实际上可称得上是应用数学
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.41,0:21:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而拥有最多识见的却并非经验丰富的各国军方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.40,0:21:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是我们私人企业
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.07,0:21:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们仅是在试着开发武装冲突的民营化侧面而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.82,0:21:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到效率高
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.57,0:21:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡是要扯上钱这个字的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.15,0:21:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,军队怎么可能胜过私企呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.82,0:21:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是有趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.92,0:21:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日野木 看来有必要让这家伙懂一下了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.19,0:21:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将军 我认为现在还是先静观其变的好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.99,0:21:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贵军随时随地都有主动权啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.72,0:21:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真扯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.00,0:21:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙想要支配战争吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.21,0:21:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞得像是某阴谋论电影里出现的反派老大一样了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.67,0:22:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡士柏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.27,0:22:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿先生
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.15,0:22:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您认识卡士柏先生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.49,0:22:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不算熟
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.45,0:22:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在刚才 HCLI发表了不少惊人的消息
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.82,0:22:11.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是现场视频
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.13,0:22:14.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真有这么重大
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.87,0:22:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么为什么蔻蔻还在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.75,0:22:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电视的话她连看都不看
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.13,0:22:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔻蔻 我对你心里藏着的那件事很感兴趣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.78,0:22:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能让我插一脚呢 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.04,0:22:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要钱的话我多少都给
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.24,0:22:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您 您这是怎么了 托娅霍夫斯基小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.48,0:22:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,HCLI刚发布了Hek～GG这个新的物流解决方案
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.06,0:22:46.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信对于您的生意也会带来新的…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.40,0:22:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那事
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.39,0:22:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概你也很困惑吧 一下给人说到
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.57,0:22:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 今天我就不问了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.14,0:22:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不代表我放弃了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.89,0:22:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是要我参股 随时打电话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.76,0:23:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说啊 啥事嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.99,0:23:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 多谢惠顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.67,0:23:07.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再见吧 蔻蔻
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.86,0:23:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和军火商正在旅途
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.77,0:23:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是细细想来 我对蔻蔻却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.03,0:23:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,约拿 咱散步去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.74,0:23:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 天凉好个秋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.31,0:23:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明近在咫尺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.55,0:23:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却相隔天涯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.04,0:23:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是蔻蔻·海克梅迪亚这个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.75,0:23:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 1984 phase.2
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,【STAFF】
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.90,0:04:00.88,STAFF,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻译：g喵　时间：夜月　后期：史努比NF　译制：动漫花园枫组


